{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.387476, "sourceDate": 1585352964.387476, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.387477, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965d3a0c-7085-11ea-82e8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f5f8c-7085-11ea-9e0b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f609a-7085-11ea-9a70-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can I be infected", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can I be infected", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4016042, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4016042, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4016042, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f61b4-7085-11ea-9647-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f6202-7085-11ea-a7de-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f623e-7085-11ea-aaea-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What drugs can I take to reduce the risk of contracting it ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What drugs can I take to reduce the risk of contracting it?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40163, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40163, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4016309, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f62b6-7085-11ea-9444-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f62fa-7085-11ea-b64a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f6338-7085-11ea-a0ea-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I wash my hands , can I protect myself from covid19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I wash my hands, can I protect myself from covid19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4016519, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4016519, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4016519, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f6388-7085-11ea-aba2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f63c6-7085-11ea-944e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f63f6-7085-11ea-9b43-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where is the nearest hospital ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where is the nearest hospital?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.401671, "sourceDate": 1585352964.401671, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.401671, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f6446-7085-11ea-bf38-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f6482-7085-11ea-8364-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f64b4-7085-11ea-9789-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of corona virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of corona virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.401688, "sourceDate": 1585352964.401688, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.401688, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f64fa-7085-11ea-8786-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f652c-7085-11ea-84ba-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f6568-7085-11ea-b5f9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "So I have been having a weird feeling around my throat / neck region my question is am I supposed to be worried or go get tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "So I have been having a weird feeling around my throat / neck region my question is am I supposed to be worried or go get tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.401707, "sourceDate": 1585352964.401707, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.401707, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f65ae-7085-11ea-904f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f6608-7085-11ea-8c37-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f663a-7085-11ea-91ef-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it safe to handle delivered packages ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it safe to handle delivered packages?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.401727, "sourceDate": 1585352964.401727, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.401727, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f6676-7085-11ea-a35e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f66b4-7085-11ea-8108-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f6752-7085-11ea-bc13-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "if I do atchum is it serious ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "if I do atchum is it serious?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4017909, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4017909, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4017909, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f690a-7085-11ea-9419-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f69d2-7085-11ea-b6e1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f6a2c-7085-11ea-9b2a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Get I get infected from a dog ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Get I get infected from a dog?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.401836, "sourceDate": 1585352964.401836, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.401836, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f6ac2-7085-11ea-ba04-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f6b26-7085-11ea-bc71-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f6b62-7085-11ea-9ee5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can I protect myself from the covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can I protect myself from the covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.401865, "sourceDate": 1585352964.401865, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.401866, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f6be4-7085-11ea-a6c8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f6c48-7085-11ea-963d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f6c98-7085-11ea-9fed-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do we have any idea how long public / private places ( ex : CrossFit gyms )", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do we have any idea how long public / private places (ex: CrossFit gyms)", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4018922, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4018922, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4018922, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f6cf4-7085-11ea-9c6d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f6d38-7085-11ea-932d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f6d88-7085-11ea-9c66-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long can the virus live ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long can the virus live?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.401917, "sourceDate": 1585352964.401917, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.401917, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f6dec-7085-11ea-acac-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f6e28-7085-11ea-8496-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f6e5a-7085-11ea-a890-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can a 5 year old get Coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can a 5 year old get Coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4019399, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4019399, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4019399, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f6ec8-7085-11ea-abb9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f6f06-7085-11ea-997a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f6f54-7085-11ea-ace5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have a bit of nausea and headache . Do i have covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have a bit of nausea and headache. Do i have covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4019608, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4019608, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4019608, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f6f9a-7085-11ea-998a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f6fd8-7085-11ea-a1fa-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f7008-7085-11ea-a179-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "In parallel with covid-19 how many cases of influenza have killed people", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "In parallel with covid-19 how many cases of influenza have killed people", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.401978, "sourceDate": 1585352964.401979, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.401979, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f7062-7085-11ea-a9fa-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f70ba-7085-11ea-b8e1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f7102-7085-11ea-b416-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the minimum distance that must be kept between two people ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the minimum distance that must be kept between two people?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402005, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402005, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402005, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f715c-7085-11ea-b848-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f71ac-7085-11ea-a121-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f71de-7085-11ea-a9ca-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why name it Corona ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why name it Corona?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402027, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402027, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402027, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f722e-7085-11ea-aadc-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f7268-7085-11ea-985f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f729c-7085-11ea-abdc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it really worth doing these containment measures ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it really worth doing these containment measures?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4020429, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4020438, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4020438, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f72d8-7085-11ea-82c7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f7314-7085-11ea-abef-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f7346-7085-11ea-bd53-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have gastroenteritis and have a fever , should I take a test", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have gastroenteritis and have a fever, should I take a test", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4020622, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4020622, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4020622, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f7398-7085-11ea-9de9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f73d2-7085-11ea-af4e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f7406-7085-11ea-b034-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the main mode of transmission of COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the main mode of transmission of COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402081, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402081, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402081, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f7454-7085-11ea-9ea3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f7490-7085-11ea-98d4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f74c2-7085-11ea-839e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will the suspension of school networks delay my entry to the University ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will the suspension of school networks delay my entry to the University?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402098, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402099, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402099, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f74fe-7085-11ea-a428-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f7530-7085-11ea-968d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f7562-7085-11ea-8d97-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Who are you", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Who are you", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402115, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402115, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402115, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f75a8-7085-11ea-a3fd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f75ee-7085-11ea-bd0c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f761e-7085-11ea-9bf6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how many people died so far ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how many people died so far?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402136, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402136, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402136, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f7670-7085-11ea-8dc4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f76ac-7085-11ea-b60b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f76de-7085-11ea-a9f8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of covid", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of covid", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402155, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402155, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402155, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f772e-7085-11ea-b512-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f7768-7085-11ea-9294-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f779c-7085-11ea-a389-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to protect myself on a plane", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to protect myself on a plane", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4021719, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4021719, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4021719, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f77d8-7085-11ea-ae06-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f780a-7085-11ea-8273-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f7846-7085-11ea-9973-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What to do in case of negative test", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What to do in case of negative test", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402189, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402189, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402189, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f7882-7085-11ea-97f4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f78be-7085-11ea-838c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f78f0-7085-11ea-b13d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I am feeling sick", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I am feeling sick", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402206, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402206, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402206, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f792c-7085-11ea-aef3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f7968-7085-11ea-af45-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f799a-7085-11ea-89c5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What would be the impact of a medication that cures Covid symptoms more quickly ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What would be the impact of a medication that cures Covid symptoms more quickly?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402237, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402237, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402237, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f7a6c-7085-11ea-bb06-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f7aa8-7085-11ea-90ef-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f7ae4-7085-11ea-afad-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I use NSAIDs ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I use NSAIDs?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402258, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402258, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402258, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f7b3e-7085-11ea-8b89-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f7b70-7085-11ea-9667-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f7bac-7085-11ea-8d10-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When should I get tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When should I get tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402275, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402275, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402276, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f7be8-7085-11ea-b1b7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f7c2e-7085-11ea-a5c1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f7c68-7085-11ea-8caf-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Am I safe ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Am I safe?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402295, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402295, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402296, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f7cc6-7085-11ea-84a6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f7d00-7085-11ea-9661-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f7d34-7085-11ea-a1bd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can drinking alcohol helps COVID19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can drinking alcohol helps COVID19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402316, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402316, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402316, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f7d82-7085-11ea-ad19-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f7db4-7085-11ea-8304-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f7de6-7085-11ea-b7c1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When will the drug for CoViD 19 be ready ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When will the drug for CoViD 19 be ready?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402333, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402333, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402333, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f7e2c-7085-11ea-951b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f7e7a-7085-11ea-a0e3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f7eae-7085-11ea-8014-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to disinfect surfaces", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to disinfect surfaces", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4023528, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4023528, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402354, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f7ef4-7085-11ea-900a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f7f46-7085-11ea-9efe-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f7f76-7085-11ea-b9d5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What will happen to my job ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What will happen to my job?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402375, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402375, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402375, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f7fd0-7085-11ea-b229-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f8002-7085-11ea-8b59-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f803e-7085-11ea-b03f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When will the pandemic end ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When will the pandemic end?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402394, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4023948, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4023948, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f808c-7085-11ea-8d3a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f80ca-7085-11ea-b904-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f80fa-7085-11ea-880d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is sitting on the seat of a public toilet dangerous ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is sitting on the seat of a public toilet dangerous?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402412, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402412, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402412, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f8138-7085-11ea-a369-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f8168-7085-11ea-b654-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f819c-7085-11ea-981b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How mild are most cases", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How mild are most cases", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402428, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402428, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402428, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f81e2-7085-11ea-a6e4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f8214-7085-11ea-a1fe-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f8246-7085-11ea-8149-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many patients and how many deaths in Quebec ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many patients and how many deaths in Quebec?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402445, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402445, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402445, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f82d2-7085-11ea-b176-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f83c2-7085-11ea-99ae-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f841c-7085-11ea-84b9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is the virus dangerous ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is the virus dangerous?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402501, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402501, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402501, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f84ba-7085-11ea-a1f8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f8502-7085-11ea-983c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f8534-7085-11ea-890a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will NHS workers be even more isolated because they are exposed to the virus on a daily basis ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will NHS workers be even more isolated because they are exposed to the virus on a daily basis?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4025211, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4025211, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4025211, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f857a-7085-11ea-86cf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f85b6-7085-11ea-a947-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f85e8-7085-11ea-ad08-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "corona", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "corona", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402538, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402538, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402538, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f862e-7085-11ea-921f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f8662-7085-11ea-9e77-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f8692-7085-11ea-95e3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can we have COVID-19 2 times ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can we have COVID-19 2 times?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402555, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402555, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402555, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f86d8-7085-11ea-94c9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f870a-7085-11ea-8f29-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f873a-7085-11ea-9d90-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are the main symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are the main symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402575, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402575, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402575, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f8798-7085-11ea-8d91-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f87f0-7085-11ea-b667-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f882c-7085-11ea-aa58-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is Covid-19 virus ? )", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is Covid-19 virus?)", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402596, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402596, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402596, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f8868-7085-11ea-8e13-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f88ae-7085-11ea-b9bf-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f88f4-7085-11ea-95b6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I 'm sneezing , should I get tested for corona virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I'm sneezing, should I get tested for corona virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402617, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402617, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402617, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f8946-7085-11ea-b3f7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f8976-7085-11ea-b7b2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f89a8-7085-11ea-b859-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is corona virus and COVID19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is corona virus and COVID19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4026382, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4026382, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4026382, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f8a18-7085-11ea-90de-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f8a52-7085-11ea-8f2e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f8a86-7085-11ea-a3a1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can i infect my pet with corona", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can i infect my pet with corona", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402658, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402658, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402658, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f8ad4-7085-11ea-9dce-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f8b10-7085-11ea-9211-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f8b42-7085-11ea-8db3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do I need to be quarantined from my family in my home", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do I need to be quarantined from my family in my home", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402675, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402675, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402675, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f8b88-7085-11ea-bee8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f8bba-7085-11ea-bef3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f8bec-7085-11ea-91c5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is clearing your throat a disturbing symptom ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is clearing your throat a disturbing symptom?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402692, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402692, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402692, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f8c34-7085-11ea-ba0d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f8c64-7085-11ea-aef0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f8c98-7085-11ea-bbfd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the risks that I have of spreading the covid-19 virus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the risks that I have of spreading the covid-19 virus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402709, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402709, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402709, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f8cd2-7085-11ea-8444-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f8d22-7085-11ea-8957-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f8d54-7085-11ea-8382-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there really a risk of contagion when I go grocery shopping ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there really a risk of contagion when I go grocery shopping?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4027278, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4027278, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4027278, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f8d90-7085-11ea-ba9f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f8dcc-7085-11ea-85c8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f8dfe-7085-11ea-8257-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When can we travel abroad again ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When can we travel abroad again?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402745, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4027462, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4027462, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f8e46-7085-11ea-b219-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f8f70-7085-11ea-b0cf-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f8fd4-7085-11ea-8c89-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have a headache .", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have a headache.", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4027991, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4027991, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4027991, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f9062-7085-11ea-9fc1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f909c-7085-11ea-b831-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f90d8-7085-11ea-8762-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are 5 foods to keep your immune system strong", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are 5 foods to keep your immune system strong", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402818, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402818, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402818, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f911e-7085-11ea-8e40-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f915a-7085-11ea-84ed-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f918c-7085-11ea-a1ae-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does putting on a mask protect me well from the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does putting on a mask protect me well from the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402839, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402839, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402839, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f91e6-7085-11ea-bc60-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f9222-7085-11ea-b05c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f9254-7085-11ea-a2a9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does covid-19 survive in the cold ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does covid-19 survive in the cold?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4028559, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4028559, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4028559, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f929a-7085-11ea-b90b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f92e8-7085-11ea-b5e4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f931c-7085-11ea-a72a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "is there a way to help ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "is there a way to help?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402876, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402876, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402876, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f9358-7085-11ea-a645-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f9394-7085-11ea-ac77-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f93c6-7085-11ea-b860-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I wear a mask ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I wear a mask?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402893, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402893, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402893, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f9402-7085-11ea-a7e0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f9434-7085-11ea-93e0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f9486-7085-11ea-905e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have asthma . If I take COVID-19 , am I more likely to get seriously ill", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have asthma. If I take COVID-19, am I more likely to get seriously ill", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402912, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402912, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402912, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f94ca-7085-11ea-a37c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f9510-7085-11ea-bc91-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f9542-7085-11ea-8e84-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can it survives on food ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can it survives on food?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402932, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402932, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402932, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f9588-7085-11ea-b9c6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f95ba-7085-11ea-b167-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f95ec-7085-11ea-8bff-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have a cold , I am afraid of presenting myself in a clinic", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have a cold, I am afraid of presenting myself in a clinic", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4029498, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402951, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402951, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f9646-7085-11ea-a322-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f9698-7085-11ea-be67-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f96c8-7085-11ea-8956-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is covid-19 same as sars ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is covid-19 same as sars?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40297, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40297, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40297, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f9706-7085-11ea-b8b1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f9740-7085-11ea-9959-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f9774-7085-11ea-9a9d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long are we going to be sick", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long are we going to be sick", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.402987, "sourceDate": 1585352964.402987, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.402987, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f97ae-7085-11ea-bab2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f97e2-7085-11ea-9459-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f9812-7085-11ea-b293-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the level of contagion of the virus presently in Quebec ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the level of contagion of the virus presently in Quebec?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403003, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403003, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403003, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f9858-7085-11ea-8a64-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f988a-7085-11ea-9c36-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f98ba-7085-11ea-8c11-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I stay on my balcony ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I stay on my balcony?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403021, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403021, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403021, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f990c-7085-11ea-85f1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f993e-7085-11ea-910d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f9970-7085-11ea-a958-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there a cure for corona virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there a cure for corona virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403038, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403038, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403038, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f99b6-7085-11ea-af3d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f99e8-7085-11ea-b6a3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f9a1a-7085-11ea-8b40-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I live with an elderly person , what are the usual precautions for their toilet", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I live with an elderly person, what are the usual precautions for their toilet", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4030561, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4030561, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4030561, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f9a68-7085-11ea-a2dc-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f9a9c-7085-11ea-b7aa-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f9acc-7085-11ea-9974-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What actions can I take to help companies get out of the crisis ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What actions can I take to help companies get out of the crisis?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403075, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403075, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403075, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f9b28-7085-11ea-9915-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f9b5a-7085-11ea-9e3c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f9c5e-7085-11ea-ba53-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is covid-19 airborne ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is covid-19 airborne?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403126, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403127, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403127, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f9d30-7085-11ea-b5d5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f9d80-7085-11ea-94e4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f9dba-7085-11ea-9f45-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus stay on fruits and vegetables ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus stay on fruits and vegetables?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403148, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403148, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403148, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f9e02-7085-11ea-91cd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f9e3e-7085-11ea-a466-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f9e70-7085-11ea-90c3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What types of experimental treatment could help reduce the inflammation caused by COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What types of experimental treatment could help reduce the inflammation caused by COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403166, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403166, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403166, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f9eac-7085-11ea-8620-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f9ee8-7085-11ea-8f22-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f9f1a-7085-11ea-898e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "test for covid 19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "test for covid 19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4031842, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4031842, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403185, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965f9f68-7085-11ea-b79e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965f9f9c-7085-11ea-a0cb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965f9fcc-7085-11ea-b70e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the instructions for municipal employees ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the instructions for municipal employees?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403201, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403201, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403201, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fa014-7085-11ea-9a06-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fa046-7085-11ea-88aa-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fa078-7085-11ea-ae5c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Nigeria Covid-19 stat", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Nigeria Covid-19 stat", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403223, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403223, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403223, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fa0e6-7085-11ea-9399-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fa12c-7085-11ea-8257-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fa15e-7085-11ea-9138-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it true that COVID-19 can survive up to a few days on hard surfaces ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it true that COVID-19 can survive up to a few days on hard surfaces?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403243, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403243, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403243, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fa1b8-7085-11ea-8a50-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fa1e8-7085-11ea-a2ce-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fa230-7085-11ea-b98b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I run outside", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I run outside", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403264, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403264, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403264, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fa280-7085-11ea-a2aa-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fa2c6-7085-11ea-bf51-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fa2f8-7085-11ea-935d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I cough", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I cough", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403282, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403282, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403282, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fa33e-7085-11ea-8fcd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fa370-7085-11ea-b283-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fa3a2-7085-11ea-bfe7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does the virus live on raw fruits and vegetables", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does the virus live on raw fruits and vegetables", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403299, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403299, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403299, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fa3de-7085-11ea-aba9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fa41a-7085-11ea-ba3e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fa44c-7085-11ea-8181-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does it last once infected ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does it last once infected?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4033148, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4033148, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403316, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fa488-7085-11ea-9970-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fa4ba-7085-11ea-aa4d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fa4ec-7085-11ea-9798-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Am I gon na die", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Am I gonna die", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403332, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403332, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403332, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fa534-7085-11ea-aba9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fa578-7085-11ea-acb8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fa5b4-7085-11ea-8ddc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many people are infected in Montreal ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many people are infected in Montreal?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403352, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403352, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403352, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fa5fa-7085-11ea-ab74-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fa62c-7085-11ea-a74a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fa668-7085-11ea-8b72-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Who is most at risk ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Who is most at risk?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403372, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403372, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403372, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fa6b8-7085-11ea-93b7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fa6f4-7085-11ea-88ba-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fa726-7085-11ea-9696-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is diarrhea really a harbinger of covid ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is diarrhea really a harbinger of covid?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403389, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403389, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403389, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fa762-7085-11ea-b95f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fa794-7085-11ea-811b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fa7e4-7085-11ea-9582-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I 'm coming from a trip", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I'm coming from a trip", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4034078, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4034078, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4034078, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fa81e-7085-11ea-bebd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fa852-7085-11ea-93a0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fa88c-7085-11ea-93c7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it always advisable to go out for exercise ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it always advisable to go out for exercise?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403426, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403426, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4034271, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fa8de-7085-11ea-a837-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fa9e2-7085-11ea-8321-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965faa6e-7085-11ea-a8f4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how to disinfect the grocery store ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how to disinfect the grocery store?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403477, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403477, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403477, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fab0c-7085-11ea-82d5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fab54-7085-11ea-becd-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fab90-7085-11ea-9530-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are hot or cold regions more at risk ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are hot or cold regions more at risk?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403502, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403502, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403502, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fabd8-7085-11ea-b83a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fac08-7085-11ea-a8f2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fac3a-7085-11ea-ab14-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how are you", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how are you", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40352, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40352, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40352, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fac8a-7085-11ea-8357-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965facba-7085-11ea-ac82-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965facee-7085-11ea-ada9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I have the Covid 19 once ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I have the Covid 19 once?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4035368, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4035368, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4035368, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fad34-7085-11ea-a31d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fad98-7085-11ea-aa1a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fadd4-7085-11ea-a87e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How do I treat coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How do I treat coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403559, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40356, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40356, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fae10-7085-11ea-bb66-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fae42-7085-11ea-8237-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fae74-7085-11ea-910e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can I protect myself", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can I protect myself", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4035761, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4035761, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4035761, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965faeb0-7085-11ea-8146-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965faeec-7085-11ea-9653-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965faf1e-7085-11ea-b047-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are we immune if we catch covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are we immune if we catch covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403596, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403596, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403596, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965faf82-7085-11ea-8ac9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fafbe-7085-11ea-846f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965faffa-7085-11ea-9642-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are you intelligent", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are you intelligent", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403617, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403617, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403617, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fb04a-7085-11ea-b305-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fb086-7085-11ea-a25a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fb0b8-7085-11ea-b995-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I get sick with COVID-19 , how long before I feel better", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I get sick with COVID-19, how long before I feel better", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4036338, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4036338, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4036338, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fb0f4-7085-11ea-a729-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fb126-7085-11ea-9c9b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fb162-7085-11ea-98b7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "LP test question", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "LP test question", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40365, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40365, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40365, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fb19e-7085-11ea-8fb4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fb1d0-7085-11ea-9a4f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fb202-7085-11ea-a1f6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I die ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I die?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403667, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403667, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403667, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fb23e-7085-11ea-9c14-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fb27a-7085-11ea-bb39-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fb2ac-7085-11ea-b8e6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is covid", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is covid", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403685, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403685, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403685, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fb2f4-7085-11ea-aaa1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fb32e-7085-11ea-9d70-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fb362-7085-11ea-8dcf-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does it take between when someone is exposed to the virus and when they start to show symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does it take between when someone is exposed to the virus and when they start to show symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403702, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403702, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403702, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fb3a6-7085-11ea-9658-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fb3d8-7085-11ea-8942-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fb40a-7085-11ea-ab73-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I wear gloves in public ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I wear gloves in public?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4037209, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4037209, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403722, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fb464-7085-11ea-b05d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fb49e-7085-11ea-b5cb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fb4d2-7085-11ea-855b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I am pregnant , do I have more risk ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I am pregnant, do I have more risk?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403739, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403739, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403739, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fb50c-7085-11ea-b819-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fb540-7085-11ea-9b26-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fb57a-7085-11ea-b5c5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long do we need social distanciation for the virus to be less of a threat ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long do we need social distanciation for the virus to be less of a threat?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403755, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403755, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403755, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fb5b8-7085-11ea-a3cf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fb5e8-7085-11ea-adbf-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fb61c-7085-11ea-a954-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "am I at risk of losing my job", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "am I at risk of losing my job", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403774, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403774, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403774, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fb66c-7085-11ea-9496-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fb6b4-7085-11ea-8964-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fb6e4-7085-11ea-92f1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should we stop shared custody ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should we stop shared custody?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403792, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403792, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403792, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fb71e-7085-11ea-83b3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fb752-7085-11ea-85c5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fb786-7085-11ea-91df-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can you die from contracting covid ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can you die from contracting covid?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403808, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403808, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403808, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fb7ca-7085-11ea-ab59-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fb81a-7085-11ea-9fab-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fb868-7085-11ea-92c5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will there be any changes in PGWP ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will there be any changes in PGWP?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403831, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403831, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403831, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fb8a6-7085-11ea-b698-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fb8d8-7085-11ea-a033-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fb914-7085-11ea-8f14-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How contagious is covid 19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How contagious is covid 19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403851, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403851, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403851, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fb96e-7085-11ea-af2a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fb9a8-7085-11ea-a8a9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fb9dc-7085-11ea-85ce-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have flown in Canada , should I quarantine myself and call the covid line at the slightest symptom ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have flown in Canada, should I quarantine myself and call the covid line at the slightest symptom ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403868, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403868, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403868, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fba22-7085-11ea-b725-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fba54-7085-11ea-8d89-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fba86-7085-11ea-b9a8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "is diarrhea a symptom of covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "is diarrhea a symptom of covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4038851, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4038851, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4038851, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fbacc-7085-11ea-a78d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fbafe-7085-11ea-8cfa-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fbb30-7085-11ea-8b2d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "From the infected worldwide population what is the ratio that will need medical attention ( eg . ICU or ventilators ) ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "From the infected worldwide population what is the ratio that will need medical attention (eg. ICU or ventilators)?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403902, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403902, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403902, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fbb6c-7085-11ea-ae43-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fbba8-7085-11ea-856d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fbbda-7085-11ea-a90f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the probability of dying ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the probability of dying?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.403954, "sourceDate": 1585352964.403955, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.403955, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fbd92-7085-11ea-b095-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fbe50-7085-11ea-a8e5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fbea8-7085-11ea-8c5b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What to do when i gave cough", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What to do when i gave cough", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4039948, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4039948, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4039948, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fbf18-7085-11ea-be07-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fbf54-7085-11ea-8334-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fbf90-7085-11ea-9f96-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I got the flu two weeks ago and are getting symptoms again", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I got the flu two weeks ago and are getting symptoms again", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404014, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404014, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404014, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fbfcc-7085-11ea-90ad-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fc008-7085-11ea-a79a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fc03a-7085-11ea-b8d5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many new cases of coronavirus were reported yesterday", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many new cases of coronavirus were reported yesterday", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404031, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404031, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404031, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fc076-7085-11ea-9c66-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fc0b4-7085-11ea-aa5c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fc0e4-7085-11ea-b210-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I feel a little sick , with fewer , must I go to the hospital ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I feel a little sick, with fewer, must I go to the hospital?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404048, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404048, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404048, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fc11e-7085-11ea-b11d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fc15c-7085-11ea-b2c4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fc1ac-7085-11ea-b324-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I receive COVID-19 following a blood transfusion", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I receive COVID-19 following a blood transfusion", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404072, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404073, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404073, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fc224-7085-11ea-b549-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fc27e-7085-11ea-abf1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fc2d8-7085-11ea-9543-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What 's COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What's COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404107, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404107, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404107, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fc378-7085-11ea-b74b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fc3b4-7085-11ea-9df4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fc3e6-7085-11ea-824f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is covid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is covid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404125, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404125, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404125, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fc42c-7085-11ea-972d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fc47a-7085-11ea-8bd2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fc4ae-7085-11ea-b9e1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to know if a covid-19 vaccine is likely to work", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to know if a covid-19 vaccine is likely to work", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404145, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404145, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404145, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fc4f4-7085-11ea-a312-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fc526-7085-11ea-8f9c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fc558-7085-11ea-9b9b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "is migraines a symptom ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "is migraines a symptom?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404162, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404162, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404162, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fc59e-7085-11ea-ba4b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fc5d0-7085-11ea-bf9e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fc602-7085-11ea-993f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus stay airborne ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus stay airborne?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404182, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404182, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404182, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fc666-7085-11ea-8219-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fc6ca-7085-11ea-8590-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fc72e-7085-11ea-9752-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does an infection like a conjunctiva , a stye or a chalazion have a link with COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does an infection like a conjunctiva, a stye or a chalazion have a link with COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404214, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404214, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404214, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fc7a6-7085-11ea-a3d7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fc800-7085-11ea-b8a1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fc864-7085-11ea-8966-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do I have the right to go out in public places ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do I have the right to go out in public places?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404244, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404244, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404244, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fc8d2-7085-11ea-9cb8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fc936-7085-11ea-afbc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fc97a-7085-11ea-b2d7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "mental health", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "mental health", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4042702, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4042711, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4042711, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fc9d8-7085-11ea-8bc8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fca12-7085-11ea-8a97-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fca46-7085-11ea-a447-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the% of the population affected by each province in Canada ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the% of the population affected by each province in Canada?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4042869, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404288, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404288, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fca80-7085-11ea-b2a8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fcab4-7085-11ea-975a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fcae4-7085-11ea-a409-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can we wash fruits and vegetables with water only ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can we wash fruits and vegetables with water only?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4043038, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4043038, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4043038, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fcb1e-7085-11ea-a675-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fcb5c-7085-11ea-b957-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fcb8c-7085-11ea-8b4d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can self - medication help overcome the disease ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can self-medication help overcome the disease?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404325, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404325, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404326, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fcbfa-7085-11ea-a51c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fcc68-7085-11ea-90ba-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fccc6-7085-11ea-aec8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When do symptoms like short breath shows up", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When do symptoms like short breath shows up", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404356, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404356, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404356, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fcd34-7085-11ea-a5ec-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fcda8-7085-11ea-b303-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fcde6-7085-11ea-aed2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "is the grocery open ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "is the grocery open?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404383, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404383, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404383, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fce36-7085-11ea-a1d0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fce90-7085-11ea-9758-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fcec2-7085-11ea-be5c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the number of cases in Quebec ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the number of cases in Quebec?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404403, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404403, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404403, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fcefe-7085-11ea-9062-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fcf3a-7085-11ea-8572-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fcf6c-7085-11ea-9684-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I wonder if it would be better to stop work for home isolation ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I wonder if it would be better to stop work for home isolation?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404421, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4044218, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4044218, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fcfba-7085-11ea-b1e0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fcff8-7085-11ea-93b0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fd028-7085-11ea-b7c9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can I do my food shopping safely ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can I do my food shopping safely?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404439, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404439, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404439, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fd066-7085-11ea-ad92-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fd0a2-7085-11ea-9702-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fd0fa-7085-11ea-958d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Then I get vaccinated against the virus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Then I get vaccinated against the virus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404472, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404472, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404472, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fd1ba-7085-11ea-878d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fd21e-7085-11ea-b68d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fd278-7085-11ea-b136-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will suicide rates go up ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will suicide rates go up?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404502, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404502, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404503, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fd2e6-7085-11ea-bdc4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fd354-7085-11ea-a089-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fd390-7085-11ea-aa7f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When should I go see my doctor ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When should I go see my doctor?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404526, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4045272, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4045272, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fd3d8-7085-11ea-b5ae-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fd408-7085-11ea-9628-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fd446-7085-11ea-8d99-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How will covid-19 end ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How will covid-19 end?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404546, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404546, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404546, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fd494-7085-11ea-87d0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fd4e4-7085-11ea-b618-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fd51e-7085-11ea-be21-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are covid-19 outcomes worse for those who are infected and suffer from asthma ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are covid-19 outcomes worse for those who are infected and suffer from asthma?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404566, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404566, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404566, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fd55c-7085-11ea-9b1d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fd598-7085-11ea-8890-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fd5ca-7085-11ea-99cf-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have symptoms , what should I do ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have symptoms, what should I do?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404585, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404585, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404585, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fd624-7085-11ea-ba4c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fd658-7085-11ea-891c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fd6a6-7085-11ea-94d2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why is it called Corona virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why is it called Corona virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4046102, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4046102, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4046102, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fd71e-7085-11ea-9b6c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fd778-7085-11ea-bdb6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fd7d2-7085-11ea-8d9d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do I have the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do I have the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404639, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40464, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40464, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fd840-7085-11ea-96f6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fd87a-7085-11ea-864c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fd8ae-7085-11ea-a96c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will health insurance be valid outside the province ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will health insurance be valid outside the province?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404657, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404657, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404657, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fd8e8-7085-11ea-96e7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fd926-7085-11ea-ba9a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fd958-7085-11ea-ab88-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I contract the virus , does wearing a mask prevent others getting infected ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I contract the virus, does wearing a mask prevent others getting infected?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404675, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404675, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404675, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fd9a8-7085-11ea-a091-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fd9da-7085-11ea-a8a2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fda0c-7085-11ea-b551-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "After symptoms disappear , how long does a person stay contagious ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "After symptoms disappear, how long does a person stay contagious?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404692, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404692, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404692, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fda66-7085-11ea-aa1e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fdaa2-7085-11ea-9612-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fdaf4-7085-11ea-a133-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Death rate", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Death rate", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404719, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404719, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40472, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fdb62-7085-11ea-8e74-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fdbc6-7085-11ea-b04b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fdc1e-7085-11ea-81d8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the chances of getting the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the chances of getting the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404753, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404753, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404753, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fdcb4-7085-11ea-943b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fdd0c-7085-11ea-8a5c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fdd40-7085-11ea-99a1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have to go every week to have samples taken for close monitoring of my ( cardiac ) health . Do I have to go to the collection center as usual or are there new instructions ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have to go every week to have samples taken for close monitoring of my (cardiac) health. Do I have to go to the collection center as usual or are there new instructions?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404774, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404774, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404774, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fdd7a-7085-11ea-98c9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fddd8-7085-11ea-b1d8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fde08-7085-11ea-9078-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is sneezing a symptom ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is sneezing a symptom?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4047942, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4047942, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4047942, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fde46-7085-11ea-a9a7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fde76-7085-11ea-be0e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fdeb4-7085-11ea-bc88-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do we have any idea how soon public / private places ( ex : Crossfit gyms , stores ) will reopen ? directives of course .", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do we have any idea how soon public / private places (ex: Crossfit gyms, stores) will reopen? directives of course.", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40481, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40481, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40481, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fdeee-7085-11ea-bc67-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fdf1e-7085-11ea-b2d4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fdf52-7085-11ea-9ae2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are corona virus symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are corona virus symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4048278, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4048278, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4048278, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fdf98-7085-11ea-bace-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fdfca-7085-11ea-ac1b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fe010-7085-11ea-92a3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What can I do to prevent myself from getting COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What can I do to prevent myself from getting COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40485, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40485, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40485, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fe07e-7085-11ea-b340-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fe0e2-7085-11ea-93f4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fe13a-7085-11ea-813c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do you have a recipe for Portuguese pancakes ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do you have a recipe for Portuguese pancakes?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404881, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404881, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404881, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fe1b4-7085-11ea-85a8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fe1f0-7085-11ea-a194-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fe240-7085-11ea-86f7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will a vaccine against covid-19 be mandatory ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will a vaccine against covid-19 be mandatory?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404903, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404904, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404904, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fe290-7085-11ea-a2af-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fe2cc-7085-11ea-8aae-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fe2fe-7085-11ea-a3fc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the signs / symptoms and risk factors for COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the signs / symptoms and risk factors for COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404923, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404923, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404923, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fe34c-7085-11ea-9c50-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fe39e-7085-11ea-8a9c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fe3d0-7085-11ea-869c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long should a person in quarantine remain after being cured of covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long should a person in quarantine remain after being cured of covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404942, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404942, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.404943, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fe418-7085-11ea-b620-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fe448-7085-11ea-a9dd-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fe48c-7085-11ea-a84b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I had an asthma attack when I was young , but did n't have an episode for over 15 years . Am I still at risk ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I had an asthma attack when I was young, but didn't have an episode for over 15 years. Am I still at risk?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4049652, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4049659, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4049659, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fe4fa-7085-11ea-be03-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fe562-7085-11ea-90af-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fe5c6-7085-11ea-b687-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How do I clean my mobile phone ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How do I clean my mobile phone?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.404995, "sourceDate": 1585352964.404995, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4049962, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fe628-7085-11ea-b516-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fe682-7085-11ea-95ff-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fe6dc-7085-11ea-92ee-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "should I worry about covid 19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "should I worry about covid 19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405021, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405021, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405021, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fe722-7085-11ea-966b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fe75e-7085-11ea-9973-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fe790-7085-11ea-b2bc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can you transmit the virus without being sick ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can you transmit the virus without being sick?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4050372, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4050372, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405038, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fe7cc-7085-11ea-a3c3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fe7fe-7085-11ea-b91c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fe830-7085-11ea-b8bb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus stay alive on a surface such as a metro bar ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus stay alive on a surface such as a metro bar?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4050539, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4050539, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4050539, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fe86c-7085-11ea-b4c8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fe89e-7085-11ea-9e1f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fe8d0-7085-11ea-a6aa-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to prevent the transmission of the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to prevent the transmission of the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405073, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405073, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405073, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fe928-7085-11ea-aedb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fe98c-7085-11ea-b9ed-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fe9e8-7085-11ea-9d85-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I am 24 years old . What is my risk of having severe symptoms of the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I am 24 years old. What is my risk of having severe symptoms of the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405102, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4051032, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4051032, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fea62-7085-11ea-af35-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965feac6-7085-11ea-a32c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965feb0a-7085-11ea-a1ad-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there a vaccine for corona virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there a vaccine for corona virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4051268, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4051268, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4051268, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965feb50-7085-11ea-b67d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965feb82-7085-11ea-9e27-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965febb4-7085-11ea-b710-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My cat remains free from these movements , can he bring the virus home ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My cat remains free from these movements, can he bring the virus home?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405143, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405144, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405144, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965febf0-7085-11ea-92e6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fec22-7085-11ea-a21b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fec54-7085-11ea-96c8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Lp test", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Lp test", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40516, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40516, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40516, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fec9a-7085-11ea-8490-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965feccc-7085-11ea-ba07-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fecfe-7085-11ea-85cd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of covid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of covid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405177, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405177, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405177, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fed46-7085-11ea-871c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fed76-7085-11ea-9241-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965feda8-7085-11ea-8902-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many days does it take to see the symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many days does it take to see the symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405194, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405194, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405194, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fede4-7085-11ea-a7fd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fee18-7085-11ea-b380-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fee52-7085-11ea-baed-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have the symptoms of a cold , can I just put myself in isolation without getting tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have the symptoms of a cold, can I just put myself in isolation without getting tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4052212, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4052212, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4052212, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965feefa-7085-11ea-8448-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fef68-7085-11ea-a90f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fefcc-7085-11ea-8df3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the mortality rate for those aged 50 and under ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the mortality rate for those aged 50 and under?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405252, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405252, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4052532, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965ff034-7085-11ea-8846-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965ff098-7085-11ea-975b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965ff0dc-7085-11ea-9cc3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What can I do to keep my immune system strong", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What can I do to keep my immune system strong", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4052758, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4052758, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405277, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965ff122-7085-11ea-b705-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965ff154-7085-11ea-ac81-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965ff186-7085-11ea-9006-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long do we have ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long do we have?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405293, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405293, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405293, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965ff1cc-7085-11ea-83d2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965ff1fe-7085-11ea-b23a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965ff230-7085-11ea-b88c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How 's the shortness of breath ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How's the shortness of breath?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40531, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40531, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40531, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965ff276-7085-11ea-ac0d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965ff2a8-7085-11ea-814c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965ff2da-7085-11ea-94b6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many cases are there in the Mauricie region", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many cases are there in the Mauricie region", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405327, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405327, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405327, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965ff318-7085-11ea-9a9b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965ff348-7085-11ea-b440-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965ff37a-7085-11ea-9b8a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long will social distancing measures last ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long will social distancing measures last?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405343, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405343, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405343, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965ff3c0-7085-11ea-bd1d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965ff406-7085-11ea-b9ba-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965ff462-7085-11ea-a934-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "To get an idea of \u200b\u200bhow widespread the virus is , why do n't we simply test a random sample of people ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "To get an idea of \u200b\u200bhow widespread the virus is, why don't we simply test a random sample of people?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405374, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405374, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405374, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965ff4f6-7085-11ea-984e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965ff546-7085-11ea-ab75-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965ff578-7085-11ea-922e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If my son if suppose to get tested tomorrow , but just starting to feel better . Can I cancel or should we still go ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If my son if suppose to get tested tomorrow, but just starting to feel better. Can I cancel or should we still go?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4053938, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4053938, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4053938, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965ff5b4-7085-11ea-ace1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965ff5e6-7085-11ea-bd69-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965ff618-7085-11ea-81cc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where can I go to be tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where can I go to be tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40541, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40541, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40541, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965ff65e-7085-11ea-a09d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965ff690-7085-11ea-a6fb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965ff6c2-7085-11ea-9645-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will I die if I get covid 19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will I die if I get covid 19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405427, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405427, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405427, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965ff6fe-7085-11ea-9af6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965ff758-7085-11ea-bfcc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965ff794-7085-11ea-9708-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Could teachers be taken to help in daycares ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Could teachers be taken to help in daycares?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405447, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405447, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405448, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965ff7d0-7085-11ea-92f9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965ff802-7085-11ea-8fd9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965ff834-7085-11ea-8f7c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it possible to receive the screening test at home", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it possible to receive the screening test at home", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4054642, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4054642, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4054642, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965ff87a-7085-11ea-9718-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965ff8ac-7085-11ea-8d66-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965ff8de-7085-11ea-9df8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how long does the virus survive on surfaces ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how long does the virus survive on surfaces?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4054852, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4054852, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4054852, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965ff94c-7085-11ea-9181-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965ff9a6-7085-11ea-ab07-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965ffa0a-7085-11ea-9bdc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have to return home urgently , are the airports safe places ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have to return home urgently, are the airports safe places?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405548, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405565, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405565, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965ffc6c-7085-11ea-bd81-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965ffcc6-7085-11ea-a4c6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965ffd02-7085-11ea-912a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the main symptoms of the disease related to new coronavirus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the main symptoms of the disease related to new coronavirus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405589, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405589, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405589, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965ffd5c-7085-11ea-8136-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965ffdb6-7085-11ea-ae78-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965ffde8-7085-11ea-8da5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What to take to relieve our symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What to take to relieve our symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40561, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40561, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40561, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965ffe2e-7085-11ea-af75-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965ffe62-7085-11ea-8ffe-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965ffe92-7085-11ea-9692-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "can I send covid-21 to someone if I come back from a trip ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "can I send covid-21 to someone if I come back from a trip?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4056268, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4056268, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4056268, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965ffecc-7085-11ea-aaba-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965fff0a-7085-11ea-a558-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "965fff3a-7085-11ea-80ca-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is the death rate of the new corona virus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is the death rate of the new corona virus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405649, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405649, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405649, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "965fffa8-7085-11ea-ab50-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "965ffff0-7085-11ea-916d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660002c-7085-11ea-8e01-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is self isolation ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is self isolation?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405667, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405667, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405667, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96600068-7085-11ea-acaa-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660009a-7085-11ea-bf6c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966000d8-7085-11ea-81de-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are effective immunity boosters ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are effective immunity boosters?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405684, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405684, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405685, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96600112-7085-11ea-9678-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96600146-7085-11ea-949a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96600176-7085-11ea-9234-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can a simple sore throat be associated with COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can a simple sore throat be associated with COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4057012, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4057012, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4057012, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966001ba-7085-11ea-ba6c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966001ee-7085-11ea-9aa0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660021e-7085-11ea-8a08-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many cases in Quebec ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many cases in Quebec?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405718, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405718, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405718, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660025c-7085-11ea-a0db-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96600298-7085-11ea-a652-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966002ca-7085-11ea-8d76-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I am laid off , will I be paid ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I am laid off, will I be paid?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4057338, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405735, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405735, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96600306-7085-11ea-9bff-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96600338-7085-11ea-bc35-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96600368-7085-11ea-98ac-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many cases are we in ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many cases are we in?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405751, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405751, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405751, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966003b0-7085-11ea-9749-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966003e2-7085-11ea-ba16-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96600414-7085-11ea-9622-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What risks do I run when going outside ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What risks do I run when going outside?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405772, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405772, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405772, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96600482-7085-11ea-ab36-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966004b4-7085-11ea-aa07-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966004e6-7085-11ea-b564-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I still see my friends ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I still see my friends?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405789, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405789, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405789, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660052c-7085-11ea-9450-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660055e-7085-11ea-8062-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96600590-7085-11ea-9323-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have seen someone who has been in contact with someone who has tested positive for covid , that they are my chances of getting it ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have seen someone who has been in contact with someone who has tested positive for covid, that they are my chances of getting it?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405807, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405807, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405807, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660064c-7085-11ea-aeb7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96600728-7085-11ea-9b9b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96600786-7085-11ea-8fcb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have a dry cough . What do I do ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have a dry cough. What do I do?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4058619, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4058619, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4058619, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96600806-7085-11ea-8dcf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96600842-7085-11ea-ace4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660087e-7085-11ea-b3a2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the places to treat covid-19 in Montreal ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the places to treat covid-19 in Montreal?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4058812, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4058812, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4058821, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966008c6-7085-11ea-a750-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96600900-7085-11ea-ab75-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96600934-7085-11ea-be19-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are we contagious if we do n't have symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are we contagious if we don't have symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405899, "sourceDate": 1585352964.405899, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.405899, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660096e-7085-11ea-92e1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966009a8-7085-11ea-8a09-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96600a06-7085-11ea-9959-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the main means of transmission ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the main means of transmission?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.405922, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4059231, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4059231, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96600a5e-7085-11ea-b0d7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96600a9a-7085-11ea-bfa3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96600acc-7085-11ea-b20b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are adolescents at risk of developing complications ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are adolescents at risk of developing complications?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40594, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40594, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40594, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96600b26-7085-11ea-b9e3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96600b62-7085-11ea-9c99-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96600b94-7085-11ea-845c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Were there documented cases before January 2020 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Were there documented cases before January 2020?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4059598, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4059598, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4059598, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96600bd0-7085-11ea-8832-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96600c18-7085-11ea-ab2a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96600c52-7085-11ea-a23a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What s corona", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Whats corona", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4059799, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4059799, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4059799, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96600c98-7085-11ea-9d08-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96600ce8-7085-11ea-8794-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96600d1a-7085-11ea-a08d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many people are infected in Canada ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many people are infected in Canada?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4060001, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4060001, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4060001, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96600d62-7085-11ea-93d6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96600db0-7085-11ea-ad32-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96600dec-7085-11ea-aa9b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus remain on surfaces , such as countertops etc ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus remain on surfaces, such as countertops etc?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406019, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406019, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4060202, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96600e28-7085-11ea-9cc3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96600e5a-7085-11ea-ba50-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96600e8c-7085-11ea-91fe-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is the virus infectious during incubation period ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is the virus infectious during incubation period?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406036, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406036, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406036, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96600ec8-7085-11ea-bab8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96600f06-7085-11ea-a866-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96600f36-7085-11ea-a0d9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many new cases are listed in Quebec today ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many new cases are listed in Quebec today?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4060538, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4060538, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4060538, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96600f86-7085-11ea-aba6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96600fc2-7085-11ea-a4e0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96600ff4-7085-11ea-b6c2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have diabetes am I at risk ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have diabetes am I at risk?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406071, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406071, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406071, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96601030-7085-11ea-bba7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96601062-7085-11ea-9796-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96601094-7085-11ea-abca-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What can i do to protect myself from corona", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What can i do to protect myself from corona", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4060879, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4060879, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4060879, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966010da-7085-11ea-a118-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660110c-7085-11ea-89c7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660113e-7085-11ea-b55e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Whatbare the symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Whatbare the symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406105, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406105, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406105, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660117a-7085-11ea-afe1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966011b6-7085-11ea-9318-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966011e8-7085-11ea-af6c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long will quarantine last", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long will quarantine last", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406122, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406122, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406123, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660122e-7085-11ea-893c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96601274-7085-11ea-b80d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966012b0-7085-11ea-8c9e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is social distancing", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is social distancing", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406142, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406142, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406142, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966012f6-7085-11ea-beee-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96601328-7085-11ea-a35c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660135a-7085-11ea-b93f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Comparison coronavirus and flu", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Comparison coronavirus and flu", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4061592, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4061592, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4061592, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96601398-7085-11ea-83f2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966013c8-7085-11ea-80a7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96601406-7085-11ea-ac94-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many cases in Montreal ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many cases in Montreal?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406178, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406178, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406178, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660145e-7085-11ea-8eff-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96601490-7085-11ea-ad63-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966014cc-7085-11ea-a00e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many days since Switzerland closed schools ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many days since Switzerland closed schools?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406198, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406198, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406198, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96601526-7085-11ea-9e64-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96601558-7085-11ea-b2a6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660158a-7085-11ea-9736-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to get tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to get tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406215, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406215, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406215, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966015c6-7085-11ea-a3a8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96601602-7085-11ea-b938-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96601634-7085-11ea-adc8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is covid-19 contagious ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is covid-19 contagious?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406231, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406231, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406231, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96601670-7085-11ea-af3e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966016a2-7085-11ea-a92d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966016d4-7085-11ea-b316-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "hello", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "hello", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406247, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4062479, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4062479, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96601710-7085-11ea-bfe1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96601742-7085-11ea-8e42-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96601774-7085-11ea-9136-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how can I prevent myself from getting sick ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how can I prevent myself from getting sick?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406264, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406264, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406264, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966017b0-7085-11ea-8954-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966017ec-7085-11ea-95a7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660181e-7085-11ea-87a8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are the symptoms of covid-19 by day of infection ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are the symptoms of covid-19 by day of infection?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40628, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40628, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40628, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660185a-7085-11ea-b8a8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660189e-7085-11ea-a14e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966018d2-7085-11ea-9784-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How do people get infected with Coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How do people get infected with Coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4062998, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4062998, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4062998, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96601922-7085-11ea-bc0d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96601954-7085-11ea-ac4a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96601986-7085-11ea-9140-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "One of the symptoms of COVID-19 is shortness of breath . What does that mean", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "One of the symptoms of COVID-19 is shortness of breath. What does that mean", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4063191, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4063191, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4063191, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966019e2-7085-11ea-a9e7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96601a1c-7085-11ea-9d1d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96601a4c-7085-11ea-8336-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus survive on a dry surface ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus survive on a dry surface?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406336, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406337, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406337, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96601a8a-7085-11ea-886c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96601aba-7085-11ea-a3d5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96601aee-7085-11ea-8920-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many hours do I have to isolate ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many hours do I have to isolate?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406353, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406353, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406353, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96601b34-7085-11ea-a253-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96601b66-7085-11ea-9ef2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96601b98-7085-11ea-9195-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long can the coronavirus that causes COVID-19 survive on surfaces", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long can the coronavirus that causes COVID-19 survive on surfaces", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4063702, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4063702, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4063702, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96601bd4-7085-11ea-9268-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96601c10-7085-11ea-b9eb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96601c42-7085-11ea-9500-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "We are a family of four whose members returned from abroad on different days", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "We are a family of four whose members returned from abroad on different days", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4063869, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4063869, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4063869, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96601c7e-7085-11ea-a326-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96601cba-7085-11ea-b008-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96601cec-7085-11ea-8a82-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is a virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is a virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406403, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406403, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406403, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96601d28-7085-11ea-bd56-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96601d78-7085-11ea-ab13-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96601da8-7085-11ea-8ab0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how many people have recovered from coronavirus in Quebec since the start of the pandemic ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how many people have recovered from coronavirus in Quebec since the start of the pandemic?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406423, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406423, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406423, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96601de6-7085-11ea-b3a9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96601e22-7085-11ea-890b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96601e54-7085-11ea-bfe8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Could we reach a situation like in Italy ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Could we reach a situation like in Italy?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406442, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406442, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406443, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96601eae-7085-11ea-912c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96601ee8-7085-11ea-acac-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96601f26-7085-11ea-b3d0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long will the COVID-19 epidemic last ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long will the COVID-19 epidemic last?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406461, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406461, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406461, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96601f62-7085-11ea-a573-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96601fb4-7085-11ea-8eb4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96601fe4-7085-11ea-b302-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are there any cases near me ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are there any cases near me?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4064798, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4064798, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4064798, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96602028-7085-11ea-bc67-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660205c-7085-11ea-be8f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660208c-7085-11ea-bf9c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I take daily walks but keep a 6 ft distance when I talk to someone . Is that OK ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I take daily walks but keep a 6 ft distance when I talk to someone. Is that OK?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406497, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406497, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406497, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966020ca-7085-11ea-bd45-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660211a-7085-11ea-8aa1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660214c-7085-11ea-ad8f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can rubbing alcohol replace Purel type gels ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can rubbing alcohol replace Purel type gels?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406516, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406516, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406516, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96602188-7085-11ea-97c1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966021c6-7085-11ea-af72-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966021f6-7085-11ea-a57c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "if i have symptoms should i go to the ER or should I call a doctor ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "if i have symptoms should i go to the ER or should I call a doctor?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406533, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406533, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406533, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96602234-7085-11ea-8278-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660226e-7085-11ea-8e7a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660229e-7085-11ea-bf31-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can you have corvida-19 without having all the symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can you have corvida-19 without having all the symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406549, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406549, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406549, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966022dc-7085-11ea-8afd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660230c-7085-11ea-9612-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96602340-7085-11ea-82a3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Wich are Covid-19 synthoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Wich are Covid-19 synthoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406574, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406574, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406574, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966023d8-7085-11ea-ab4f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96602412-7085-11ea-81c8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96602446-7085-11ea-ba7d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Am I going to be sick ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Am I going to be sick?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406592, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406592, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406592, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660248a-7085-11ea-a04d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966024ba-7085-11ea-bea2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966024ee-7085-11ea-964c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many tests are performed per day in Quebec ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many tests are performed per day in Quebec?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4066079, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4066088, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4066088, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96602528-7085-11ea-80cf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96602658-7085-11ea-8b05-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966026cc-7085-11ea-92fc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the statistics from Quebec ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the statistics from Quebec?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40666, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40666, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40666, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96602734-7085-11ea-8ddb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660276e-7085-11ea-bcdc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966027a8-7085-11ea-9098-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "i cough is what i got the corona virus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "i cough is what i got the corona virus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4066792, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4066792, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4066792, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966027f0-7085-11ea-ac91-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96602822-7085-11ea-a0bc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96602854-7085-11ea-b3f9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do I need a mask ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do I need a mask?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4066958, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4066958, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4066958, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660289a-7085-11ea-9bc5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966028cc-7085-11ea-a346-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966028fe-7085-11ea-b51d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many case in montreal", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many case in montreal", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406713, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406713, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406713, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660293a-7085-11ea-9052-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660298a-7085-11ea-a0f8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966029ba-7085-11ea-ae34-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it easy to get tested if we have the symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it easy to get tested if we have the symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40675, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406751, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406751, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96602ab6-7085-11ea-96f8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96602ae8-7085-11ea-a8e3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96602b1a-7085-11ea-874e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are covid symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are covid symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4067662, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4067662, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4067662, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96602b4c-7085-11ea-8b08-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660318c-7085-11ea-9b32-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966031be-7085-11ea-b7a6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "will I die", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "will I die", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406938, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4069388, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4069388, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660320c-7085-11ea-8afe-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96603240-7085-11ea-98a6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96603290-7085-11ea-af8d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If my daughter has been in contact with someone with covid-19 , should I give up going to work for the time isolation ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If my daughter has been in contact with someone with covid-19, should I give up going to work for the time isolation?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4069571, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4069571, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4069571, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966032cc-7085-11ea-8e75-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966032fe-7085-11ea-ac0a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96603326-7085-11ea-959b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is covid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is covid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406972, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406972, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406972, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96603362-7085-11ea-b437-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660338a-7085-11ea-87d8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966033ba-7085-11ea-9c4e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are we all going to die ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are we all going to die?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.406987, "sourceDate": 1585352964.406987, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.406987, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966033ee-7085-11ea-8dc7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660341e-7085-11ea-935c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96603452-7085-11ea-9002-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My son is flying from Kansas to England on the 30th April . He is flying into Heathrow and then traveling home to Manchester by train", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My son is flying from Kansas to England on the 30th April. He is flying into Heathrow and then traveling home to Manchester by train", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407001, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4070022, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4070022, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96603486-7085-11ea-8e5e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966034c0-7085-11ea-8937-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966034f4-7085-11ea-b8ca-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how is covid 19 spread ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how is covid 19 spread?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407018, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407018, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407018, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96603524-7085-11ea-9d07-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96603558-7085-11ea-9f04-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96603588-7085-11ea-9828-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I eat banana ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I eat banana?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4070342, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4070342, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4070349, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966035cc-7085-11ea-b878-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660360a-7085-11ea-b820-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96603646-7085-11ea-90de-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many people have it in my town ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many people have it in my town?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407052, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407052, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407052, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96603682-7085-11ea-bf29-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966036b4-7085-11ea-9cae-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966036e6-7085-11ea-859a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have a gastro , I am afraid of presenting myself in a clinic", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have a gastro, I am afraid of presenting myself in a clinic", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407068, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407068, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407068, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96603718-7085-11ea-88da-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660374a-7085-11ea-9fd2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96603774-7085-11ea-be6c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What can we do to protect ourselves from COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What can we do to protect ourselves from COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407082, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407082, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407082, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966037ae-7085-11ea-af8b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966037f4-7085-11ea-bf94-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96603826-7085-11ea-b6a8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how many people have died", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how many people have died", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4070988, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4071, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4071, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96603858-7085-11ea-9775-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660388a-7085-11ea-a2f1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966038b4-7085-11ea-92d2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Sorry e. It 's finish ! Thank you", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Sorry e. It's finish! Thank you", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407114, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407114, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407114, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966038e4-7085-11ea-a4d4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96603918-7085-11ea-89b9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96603948-7085-11ea-b637-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do I need to wear mask ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do I need to wear mask?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407128, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407129, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407129, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966039c0-7085-11ea-b154-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966039fa-7085-11ea-a4e4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96603a24-7085-11ea-8673-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the criteria that will allow you to lift the state of health emergency and the containment instructions ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the criteria that will allow you to lift the state of health emergency and the containment instructions?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407153, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407153, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407153, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96603a74-7085-11ea-a67b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96603aa6-7085-11ea-a488-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96603ae2-7085-11ea-9ea5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I visit my parents ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I visit my parents?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40717, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40717, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40717, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96603b14-7085-11ea-a91c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96603b46-7085-11ea-aa55-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96603b6e-7085-11ea-b6af-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Map of co vid cases in Montreal", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Map of co vid cases in Montreal", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407184, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407184, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407184, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96603ba8-7085-11ea-93f5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96603bd2-7085-11ea-b218-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96603c06-7085-11ea-9dbd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many people died of covid-19 in Canada ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many people died of covid-19 in Canada?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407201, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407201, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407201, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96603c54-7085-11ea-851e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96603d3a-7085-11ea-8850-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96603da8-7085-11ea-8f47-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do you have any information to pass on to foreign workers ( in Spanish )", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do you have any information to pass on to foreign workers (in Spanish)", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407244, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407244, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407244, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96603e02-7085-11ea-b3fb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96603e3e-7085-11ea-a205-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96603e66-7085-11ea-914f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I go out if my family member who lives with me has coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I go out if my family member who lives with me has coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40726, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407261, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407261, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96603ea2-7085-11ea-8fcb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96603ed4-7085-11ea-bf2d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96603efa-7085-11ea-877a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "From what temperature should we go to the emergency room ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "From what temperature should we go to the emergency room?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407275, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407275, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407275, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96603f38-7085-11ea-8ac0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96603f88-7085-11ea-9cd6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96603fba-7085-11ea-94cd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "In addition my spouse is an airplane pilot and continues to carry out repatriation flights to London in England .... Should I also be in prolonged isolation when he returns !", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "In addition my spouse is an airplane pilot and continues to carry out repatriation flights to London in England .... Should I also be in prolonged isolation when he returns!", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407294, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407294, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407294, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96603fec-7085-11ea-a85e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660401e-7085-11ea-92f3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96604046-7085-11ea-87cc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms ? Is vomiting one of them ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms? Is vomiting one of them?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4073112, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4073112, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4073112, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96604098-7085-11ea-84ed-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966040c8-7085-11ea-81ec-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966040fa-7085-11ea-810c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the death rate in South Carolina ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the death rate in South Carolina?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407325, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407326, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407326, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660412c-7085-11ea-9c32-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660415e-7085-11ea-86d5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96604186-7085-11ea-9d65-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can the virus mutate ? If so , what are the consequences of the mutation ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can the virus mutate? If so, what are the consequences of the mutation?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40734, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40734, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40734, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966041b8-7085-11ea-aff3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966041e8-7085-11ea-85de-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96604212-7085-11ea-841d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "age wise statistics for covid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "age wise statistics for covid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407354, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407354, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407354, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96604246-7085-11ea-9cfd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96604276-7085-11ea-b7f5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660429e-7085-11ea-8cde-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How Covid-19 started ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How Covid-19 started?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40737, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407371, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407371, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966042ee-7085-11ea-aa63-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660431e-7085-11ea-ac4a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660435c-7085-11ea-be24-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My parents are older , which puts them more at risk for COVID-19 , and they do n't live nearby . How can i help them if they get sick", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My parents are older, which puts them more at risk for COVID-19, and they don't live nearby. How can i help them if they get sick", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4073868, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407388, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407388, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96604398-7085-11ea-b48b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966043ca-7085-11ea-91fb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966043f4-7085-11ea-9519-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of a person infected with a coronavirus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of a person infected with a coronavirus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407402, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407402, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407402, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660442e-7085-11ea-b10e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96604458-7085-11ea-a9f0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96604488-7085-11ea-aa99-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "After how long the symptoms start to appear", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "After how long the symptoms start to appear", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407418, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407418, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407418, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966044cc-7085-11ea-9892-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966044f6-7085-11ea-b892-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96604528-7085-11ea-9618-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How is the virus transmitted ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How is the virus transmitted?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407433, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407433, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407433, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660455a-7085-11ea-adf8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660458c-7085-11ea-a89c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966045b4-7085-11ea-ab8e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I visit my parents at home ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I visit my parents at home?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407447, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407447, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407447, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966045e6-7085-11ea-9f9e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660460c-7085-11ea-bd5b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96604640-7085-11ea-a0c4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many people have dies", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many people have dies", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4074612, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4074612, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4074612, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96604674-7085-11ea-8af0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966046b8-7085-11ea-9e22-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966046e8-7085-11ea-af62-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the nearest hospital to go to if I have a COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the nearest hospital to go to if I have a COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407478, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407478, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407478, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660471c-7085-11ea-bb99-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660474c-7085-11ea-b496-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96604776-7085-11ea-9968-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long will an infected person be sick ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long will an infected person be sick?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4074922, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4074922, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4074922, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966047a8-7085-11ea-a983-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966047ee-7085-11ea-ab28-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96604818-7085-11ea-84c3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When should I go to the hospital", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When should I go to the hospital", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407508, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407508, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407508, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96604852-7085-11ea-9850-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660487a-7085-11ea-a9d0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966048ac-7085-11ea-b816-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How do you protect yourself from covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How do you protect yourself from covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407524, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407524, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407524, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966048f4-7085-11ea-8530-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96604924-7085-11ea-ad9f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660494c-7085-11ea-8e35-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What should we store ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What should we store?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407563, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407563, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407563, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96604a78-7085-11ea-b19f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96604ac8-7085-11ea-ba76-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96604afa-7085-11ea-b0fa-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I Travel ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I Travel?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407583, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407583, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407583, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96604b40-7085-11ea-81f0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96604b74-7085-11ea-82dd-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96604b9a-7085-11ea-8469-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can we do a quarantine rather than a screening ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can we do a quarantine rather than a screening?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407598, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407598, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407598, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96604bd8-7085-11ea-927e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96604bfe-7085-11ea-b189-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96604c30-7085-11ea-9827-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there a remedy to cure faster or prevent covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there a remedy to cure faster or prevent covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4076118, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407613, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407613, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96604c62-7085-11ea-a791-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96604c94-7085-11ea-9980-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96604cba-7085-11ea-b36d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Origin of virus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Origin of virus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4076312, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4076312, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4076312, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96604d18-7085-11ea-8fff-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96604d48-7085-11ea-8f6c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96604d7a-7085-11ea-9e90-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Updates", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Updates", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407646, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407646, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407646, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96604dc0-7085-11ea-bce4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96604df4-7085-11ea-a668-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96604e1a-7085-11ea-85a3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where do we get the test for COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where do we get the test for COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4076622, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4076622, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4076622, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96604e58-7085-11ea-ae29-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96604e7e-7085-11ea-88a3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96604eb0-7085-11ea-a959-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "are my birds likely to catch covid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "are my birds likely to catch covid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407677, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407677, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407677, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96604ee2-7085-11ea-bb0a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96604f1e-7085-11ea-933e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96604f5a-7085-11ea-b64a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is Covid 19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is Covid 19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407694, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407694, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407694, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96604f98-7085-11ea-b601-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96604fc8-7085-11ea-9587-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96604ffa-7085-11ea-a44a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can you smoke cannabis during Covid ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can you smoke cannabis during Covid?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407709, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407709, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407709, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660502c-7085-11ea-a50f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96605054-7085-11ea-9a60-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605086-7085-11ea-9b60-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there currently an effective drug against Covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there currently an effective drug against Covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407723, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4077241, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4077241, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966050b8-7085-11ea-9390-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966050e8-7085-11ea-a76d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605126-7085-11ea-a49c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have flu like symptoms , at what point should I go to the hospital ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have flu like symptoms, at what point should I go to the hospital?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407742, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407742, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407742, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96605176-7085-11ea-819c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966051ba-7085-11ea-9cce-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966051e4-7085-11ea-a9fd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there any possibility of infected corona virus twice ( second time ) ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there any possibility of infected corona virus twice (second time)?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4077592, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4077592, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4077592, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660521e-7085-11ea-8d09-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96605248-7085-11ea-965d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660527a-7085-11ea-9821-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should we absolutely do the test if we have the symptoms ? Or should we just stay at home in quarantine ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should we absolutely do the test if we have the symptoms? Or should we just stay at home in quarantine?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407773, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407773, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407773, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966052ac-7085-11ea-b51d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966052d4-7085-11ea-bba6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605306-7085-11ea-bce4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "risk of dying ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "risk of dying?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407787, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407788, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407788, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96605338-7085-11ea-a6e7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96605368-7085-11ea-bcc3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605392-7085-11ea-beca-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Hello , how are you ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Hello, how are you?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4078028, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4078028, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4078028, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966053d8-7085-11ea-b610-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96605400-7085-11ea-b562-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605434-7085-11ea-8c42-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Hey", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Hey", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407818, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407818, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407818, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96605464-7085-11ea-8c41-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96605498-7085-11ea-a378-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966054be-7085-11ea-885a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How does Covid-19 spread ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How does Covid-19 spread?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4078321, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4078321, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4078321, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966054f0-7085-11ea-b5f1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96605522-7085-11ea-a664-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605554-7085-11ea-8720-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long has the virus been active on different surfaces ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long has the virus been active on different surfaces?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407865, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407866, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407866, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660564c-7085-11ea-be3e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966056c6-7085-11ea-9266-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605702-7085-11ea-963a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When should I go to the hospital ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When should I go to the hospital?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407891, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407891, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407891, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96605748-7085-11ea-9bc4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660577a-7085-11ea-8c74-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966057a2-7085-11ea-a145-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I go outside ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I go outside?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407906, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407906, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407906, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966057de-7085-11ea-8fe1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96605806-7085-11ea-9c9f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605838-7085-11ea-9edf-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Who is more at risk of dying from the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Who is more at risk of dying from the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4079208, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4079208, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4079208, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96605874-7085-11ea-a80a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966058c6-7085-11ea-8dfe-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966058f6-7085-11ea-8da4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where did COVID-19 come from ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where did COVID-19 come from?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4079401, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4079401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4079401, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96605934-7085-11ea-a6ab-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660595a-7085-11ea-9ad8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660598c-7085-11ea-8f94-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how is covid-19 treated ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how is covid-19 treated?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407955, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407955, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407955, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966059be-7085-11ea-a37b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966059f0-7085-11ea-8f78-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605a18-7085-11ea-a049-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What can I do to protect myself and others from COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What can I do to protect myself and others from COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4079711, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4079711, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4079711, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96605a68-7085-11ea-87ac-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96605a9a-7085-11ea-91c8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605ac2-7085-11ea-b2ce-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I live with my children and my grandchildren . What can I do to reduce the risk of getting sick while caring for my grandchildren", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I live with my children and my grandchildren. What can I do to reduce the risk of getting sick while caring for my grandchildren", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.407986, "sourceDate": 1585352964.407986, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.407986, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96605af4-7085-11ea-92e8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96605b26-7085-11ea-bc2a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605b62-7085-11ea-a713-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can people 70 and over go to the grocery store and pharmacy ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can people 70 and over go to the grocery store and pharmacy?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408004, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4080052, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4080052, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96605bba-7085-11ea-b0fe-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96605be4-7085-11ea-ab83-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605c18-7085-11ea-adf2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "do I have the right to go out shopping ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "do I have the right to go out shopping?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40802, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40802, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40802, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96605c48-7085-11ea-af2c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96605c7a-7085-11ea-957e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605ca2-7085-11ea-8ee0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many days can the virus live on surfaces ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many days can the virus live on surfaces?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408034, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408034, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408034, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96605cde-7085-11ea-9030-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96605d06-7085-11ea-bf46-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605d38-7085-11ea-8dc3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "i am feeling lonely", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "i am feeling lonely", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4080482, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4080489, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4080489, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96605d68-7085-11ea-9c75-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96605d92-7085-11ea-81a8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605dc6-7085-11ea-a046-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is cover ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is cover?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408063, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408063, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408063, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96605df6-7085-11ea-8480-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96605e28-7085-11ea-844f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605e50-7085-11ea-a327-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to cure COVID ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to cure COVID?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408084, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408084, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408084, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96605ec8-7085-11ea-96d3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96605efa-7085-11ea-b03c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605f2c-7085-11ea-a68d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I get out of my house ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I get out of my house?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408098, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4080992, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4080992, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96605f74-7085-11ea-bdb8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96605fa4-7085-11ea-a05e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96605fcc-7085-11ea-8d97-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is an Asymptomatic Carrier ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is an Asymptomatic Carrier?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408115, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408115, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408115, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96605ffe-7085-11ea-9c7f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96606030-7085-11ea-b923-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96606058-7085-11ea-bbf7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long will we be confined ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long will we be confined?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408129, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408129, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408129, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660608a-7085-11ea-b744-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966060ba-7085-11ea-979e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966060e4-7085-11ea-a598-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why are death rates so different across countries ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why are death rates so different across countries?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408143, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408143, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408143, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660611e-7085-11ea-b27d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96606148-7085-11ea-b332-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96606224-7085-11ea-82a5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "To use masks it 's useful ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "To use masks it's useful?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408187, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4081879, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4081879, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966062d8-7085-11ea-9801-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96606328-7085-11ea-88fe-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660635a-7085-11ea-bdf6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why close national parks if you have to walk outside ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why close national parks if you have to walk outside?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4082072, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4082072, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4082072, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96606398-7085-11ea-a9a2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966063c8-7085-11ea-a345-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966063fa-7085-11ea-91d2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can a person relapse with COVID-19 disease ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can a person relapse with COVID-19 disease?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408224, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408224, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408224, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96606440-7085-11ea-ae58-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96606474-7085-11ea-8e55-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966064a4-7085-11ea-b599-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many people have COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many people have COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4082391, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4082391, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4082391, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966064d8-7085-11ea-bc81-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660651c-7085-11ea-b49b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660654c-7085-11ea-9c50-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I get tested even if I have n't traveled recently ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I get tested even if I haven't traveled recently?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408256, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408256, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408256, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96606580-7085-11ea-ae82-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966065b4-7085-11ea-a067-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966065ee-7085-11ea-8558-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When will the municipalities post heat maps to identify hot spots for Covid positive residents ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When will the municipalities post heat maps to identify hot spots for Covid positive residents?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408273, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408273, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408273, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96606628-7085-11ea-9a5a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96606670-7085-11ea-8275-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966066a2-7085-11ea-8d39-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is Covid19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is Covid19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4082901, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4082901, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4082901, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966066d4-7085-11ea-b186-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96606710-7085-11ea-857f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660674c-7085-11ea-aef3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why are there more people who leave the hospital in hearses than in taxis according to your statistics ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why are there more people who leave the hospital in hearses than in taxis according to your statistics?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40831, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40831, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40831, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966067a6-7085-11ea-8666-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966067d8-7085-11ea-b196-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96606800-7085-11ea-8bd5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do I need to get the flu shot to protect myself from the coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do I need to get the flu shot to protect myself from the coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4083252, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4083252, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4083252, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96606834-7085-11ea-a6e7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96606864-7085-11ea-8e52-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660688c-7085-11ea-bc56-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long are the symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long are the symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408339, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408339, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408339, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966068c8-7085-11ea-aee7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660690c-7085-11ea-8430-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96606936-7085-11ea-bdd2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I experience symptoms but they are manageable , should I still go to the hospital for testing ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I experience symptoms but they are manageable, should I still go to the hospital for testing?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4083562, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4083562, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4083562, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96606968-7085-11ea-889d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660699a-7085-11ea-9998-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966069cc-7085-11ea-b0d2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the treatments ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the treatments?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40837, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40837, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40837, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966069fe-7085-11ea-a9d7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96606a26-7085-11ea-92cc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96606a58-7085-11ea-823b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many new cases of covid-19 were reported yesterday", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many new cases of covid-19 were reported yesterday", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408385, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408385, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408385, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96606a8a-7085-11ea-bc1b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96606aba-7085-11ea-adcb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96606ae4-7085-11ea-bc60-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the coronavirus symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the coronavirus symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408399, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408399, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408399, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96606b18-7085-11ea-90b2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96606b48-7085-11ea-bfc2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96606b70-7085-11ea-9f10-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can you drink alcohol during Covid ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can you drink alcohol during Covid?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408415, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408415, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408415, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96606bb6-7085-11ea-8d5c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96606bfa-7085-11ea-9ac6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96606c24-7085-11ea-b9b8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are there confirmed cases in my neighborhood", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are there confirmed cases in my neighborhood", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408431, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408431, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408431, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96606c62-7085-11ea-956a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96606c88-7085-11ea-85c1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96606cb0-7085-11ea-a860-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do animals also carry the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do animals also carry the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408445, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408445, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408445, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96606ce2-7085-11ea-b34b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96606d14-7085-11ea-b1eb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96606d46-7085-11ea-b494-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Duration of confinement", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Duration of confinement", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408533, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408533, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408533, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96607066-7085-11ea-a9c7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966070de-7085-11ea-94e4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96607124-7085-11ea-868f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When is it going to be finished ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When is it going to be finished?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40856, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40856, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40856, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96607162-7085-11ea-b0f5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96607192-7085-11ea-b8e1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966071c6-7085-11ea-bd2b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is covid-19 ? What is covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is covid-19? What is covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408575, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408575, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408575, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966071f6-7085-11ea-846f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96607228-7085-11ea-b116-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660725a-7085-11ea-9ea8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I report the rallies I witness in my neighborhood ? If so , how ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I report the rallies I witness in my neighborhood? If so, how?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408593, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408593, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408593, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966072a8-7085-11ea-8367-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966072e6-7085-11ea-a40d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96607336-7085-11ea-a66b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is COVID-19 exactly ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is COVID-19 exactly?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408612, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408612, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408612, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660737a-7085-11ea-a9df-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966073a4-7085-11ea-902e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966073d8-7085-11ea-94be-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is coronavirus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is coronavirus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408628, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408628, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408628, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96607408-7085-11ea-8d51-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660743a-7085-11ea-b5df-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96607462-7085-11ea-a735-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I use asprin with I have the coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I use asprin with I have the coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408642, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408642, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408642, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660749e-7085-11ea-b97b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966074c6-7085-11ea-81ca-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966074f8-7085-11ea-a8f9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If a member of our contract family Covid-19 and lives alone , what should we do ? will she have help ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If a member of our contract family Covid-19 and lives alone, what should we do? will she have help?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4086568, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4086568, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4086568, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96607528-7085-11ea-abcb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660755c-7085-11ea-902c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96607586-7085-11ea-9e4f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If a person coughs in front of me and I get droplets at the turn , what can I do ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If a person coughs in front of me and I get droplets at the turn, what can I do?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408671, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408671, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408671, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966075c0-7085-11ea-9b1c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966075e8-7085-11ea-b261-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660761a-7085-11ea-9465-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does a throat feel itchy or really sore and a symptom", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does a throat feel itchy or really sore and a symptom", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408685, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4086862, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4086862, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660764c-7085-11ea-a838-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96607674-7085-11ea-9bae-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966076a6-7085-11ea-b0e5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can ibuprofen be taken to treat the symptoms of COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can ibuprofen be taken to treat the symptoms of COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4087, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4087, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4087, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966076d8-7085-11ea-ab33-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660770a-7085-11ea-852e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96607734-7085-11ea-8ab8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What 's covid19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What's covid19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408716, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408716, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4087172, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96607782-7085-11ea-b8e9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966077b4-7085-11ea-be58-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966077dc-7085-11ea-b94d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What 's the point of asking you questions if you do n't have answers", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What's the point of asking you questions if you don't have answers", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408731, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408731, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408731, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96607818-7085-11ea-91dc-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96607840-7085-11ea-88a6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96607874-7085-11ea-8918-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How do I know if I have COVID-19 or common flu", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How do I know if I have COVID-19 or common flu", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408746, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408746, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408746, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966078a4-7085-11ea-aa0d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966078d8-7085-11ea-94d2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966078fe-7085-11ea-8be5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "is it dangerous to travel", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "is it dangerous to travel", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40876, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40876, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40876, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96607930-7085-11ea-bb50-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660798a-7085-11ea-aa0a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966079ba-7085-11ea-be35-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus stay on our skin ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus stay on our skin?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408779, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408779, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408779, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966079f8-7085-11ea-9b2d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96607a1e-7085-11ea-be50-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96607a52-7085-11ea-9526-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When moving , what precautions should we take ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When moving, what precautions should we take?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4087942, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4087942, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4087942, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96607a86-7085-11ea-83c0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96607aca-7085-11ea-8949-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96607afa-7085-11ea-a399-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "From the infected worldwide population what will be the ratio of asymptomatic people", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "From the infected worldwide population what will be the ratio of asymptomatic people", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408811, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408811, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408811, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96607b2e-7085-11ea-b3f1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96607b62-7085-11ea-9a6c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96607b88-7085-11ea-b3bf-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can quarantine last until Era", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can quarantine last until Era", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4088268, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4088268, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4088268, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96607bd8-7085-11ea-8ac2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96607c0a-7085-11ea-b3d0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96607c3a-7085-11ea-85cd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can I prevent the virus from contracting", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can I prevent the virus from contracting", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4088461, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4088461, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408847, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96607c98-7085-11ea-8423-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96607cc8-7085-11ea-a9ea-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96607cfa-7085-11ea-86ac-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does drinking water frequently really help to keep the virus from getting in your throat%", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does drinking water frequently really help to keep the virus from getting in your throat%", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4088619, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4088619, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4088619, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96607d2c-7085-11ea-8249-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96607d5e-7085-11ea-a5d6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96607d86-7085-11ea-92ff-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Allo", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Allo", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408876, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408876, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408876, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96607dc2-7085-11ea-a3f9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96607de8-7085-11ea-a409-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96607e1c-7085-11ea-83e7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Hello , I have a sore throat and I am very tired but I do n't have a fever , should I get tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Hello, I have a sore throat and I am very tired but I don't have a fever, should I get tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40889, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40889, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40889, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96607e4c-7085-11ea-96fe-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96607e76-7085-11ea-8059-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96607ea8-7085-11ea-8109-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is the virus transmissible from animals to humans ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is the virus transmissible from animals to humans?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4089081, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4089081, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4089081, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96607f02-7085-11ea-a7a3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96607f34-7085-11ea-ad43-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96607f5c-7085-11ea-9ef2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Hello , can I meet with friends ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Hello, can I meet with friends?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4089248, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4089248, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4089248, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96607fa2-7085-11ea-8f31-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96607fde-7085-11ea-8b4c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96608006-7085-11ea-843b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "The incubation period is two weeks but what about the contagion period ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "The incubation period is two weeks but what about the contagion period?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408942, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408942, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408942, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608058-7085-11ea-ac8f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660807e-7085-11ea-b6f3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966080b0-7085-11ea-8fce-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408957, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408957, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408957, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966080e2-7085-11ea-8633-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96608114-7085-11ea-8b02-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660813a-7085-11ea-8748-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What 's going to happen in May ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What's going to happen in May?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.408971, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408971, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408971, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608178-7085-11ea-b8b9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660819e-7085-11ea-b5f5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966081d2-7085-11ea-b8f3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What 's the death rate for healthy US 37 year old males ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What's the death rate for healthy US 37 year old males?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4089851, "sourceDate": 1585352964.408986, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.408986, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608206-7085-11ea-af08-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660822c-7085-11ea-b74b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660825e-7085-11ea-98da-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I am negative on the screening test , can I visit my parents over 70 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I am negative on the screening test, can I visit my parents over 70?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608290-7085-11ea-beb6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966082c2-7085-11ea-8125-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966082e8-7085-11ea-9c92-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When should I visit a doctor ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When should I visit a doctor?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409014, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409014, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409014, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660831c-7085-11ea-94b9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660834c-7085-11ea-b228-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96608376-7085-11ea-8bdb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What do I do if someone with COVID-19 spotted ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What do I do if someone with COVID-19 spotted?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409028, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409028, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409028, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966083b4-7085-11ea-9dc3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966083da-7085-11ea-b68c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660840c-7085-11ea-8d33-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409046, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409046, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409046, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660845c-7085-11ea-994b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660848c-7085-11ea-a3e7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966084c0-7085-11ea-8302-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I catch the virus if my mail carrier is contaminated and it puts mail in my mailbox ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I catch the virus if my mail carrier is contaminated and it puts mail in my mailbox?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40906, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4090612, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4090612, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966084f4-7085-11ea-b063-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96608524-7085-11ea-8a1a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660854c-7085-11ea-8196-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does the virus get caught by the skin ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does the virus get caught by the skin?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409075, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409075, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409075, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608588-7085-11ea-b9c5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966085cc-7085-11ea-ae67-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660868c-7085-11ea-b79f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How do I go grocery shopping ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How do I go grocery shopping?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409119, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409119, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409119, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608768-7085-11ea-8175-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966087b8-7085-11ea-8c3c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966087e8-7085-11ea-93ad-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to shop during pandemic times ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to shop during pandemic times?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409143, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409143, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409143, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608830-7085-11ea-9f83-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96608862-7085-11ea-95b2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660888a-7085-11ea-96de-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If we have covid-19 , how long are we contagious ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If we have covid-19, how long are we contagious?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409158, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409158, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409158, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966088c6-7085-11ea-a0d1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966088ee-7085-11ea-9bad-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660891e-7085-11ea-8d78-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus stay on our clothes ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus stay on our clothes?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409172, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409173, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409173, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608952-7085-11ea-ade0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96608986-7085-11ea-83d3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966089ac-7085-11ea-8fb8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have symptoms what do I do", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have symptoms what do I do", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409191, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409191, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409191, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608a10-7085-11ea-ae57-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96608a42-7085-11ea-b86c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96608a74-7085-11ea-aea8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How is a person tested for COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How is a person tested for COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409207, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409207, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409207, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608aa6-7085-11ea-81d0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96608aec-7085-11ea-bf19-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96608b1e-7085-11ea-b55a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does the virus affect people with asthma more ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does the virus affect people with asthma more?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409225, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409225, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409225, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608b5a-7085-11ea-a6b7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96608b9e-7085-11ea-a123-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96608bc8-7085-11ea-a5ea-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is corona virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is corona virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4092422, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4092422, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4092422, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608c0c-7085-11ea-a1cb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96608c54-7085-11ea-9ea0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96608c7a-7085-11ea-a1d7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can my pharmacist screen me ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can my pharmacist screen me?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409259, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409259, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409259, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608cb8-7085-11ea-b8e0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96608ce2-7085-11ea-9e96-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96608d12-7085-11ea-90c1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "WHat is your name", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "WHat is your name", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4092731, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409274, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409274, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608d46-7085-11ea-be04-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96608d76-7085-11ea-a32b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96608d9e-7085-11ea-9967-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have pulmonary sarcoidosis , I 'm more at risk if I ever catch covid 19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have pulmonary sarcoidosis, I'm more at risk if I ever catch covid 19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409288, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409288, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409288, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608dda-7085-11ea-832a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96608e02-7085-11ea-88d4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96608e34-7085-11ea-b1bc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long can coronavirus live on a surface in the open air ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long can coronavirus live on a surface in the open air?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409305, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409305, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409305, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608e7a-7085-11ea-aa15-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96608eac-7085-11ea-9555-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96608ede-7085-11ea-b998-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "is fever a symptom of coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "is fever a symptom of coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409319, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4093199, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4093199, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608f10-7085-11ea-af43-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96608f42-7085-11ea-bfa9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96608f68-7085-11ea-a6cb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will the situation get worse in Quebec ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will the situation get worse in Quebec?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409334, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409334, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409334, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96608fa6-7085-11ea-ba97-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96608fe2-7085-11ea-ac55-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96609014-7085-11ea-8efa-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How do I clean my cell phone ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How do I clean my cell phone?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4093509, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4093509, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4093509, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96609046-7085-11ea-b6e2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96609078-7085-11ea-b489-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966090be-7085-11ea-9404-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is headache a symptom of covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is headache a symptom of covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409368, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409368, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409368, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966090fa-7085-11ea-afb2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96609122-7085-11ea-8a05-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660915e-7085-11ea-bb97-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does the Coved-19 have a movement speed ( mobility per se ) per se on a surface ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does the Coved-19 have a movement speed (mobility per se) per se on a surface?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409406, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409406, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409406, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96609276-7085-11ea-b709-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966092da-7085-11ea-9981-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660930c-7085-11ea-baca-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have a heart condition , can I go to the emergency anyway ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have a heart condition, can I go to the emergency anyway?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409428, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409428, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409428, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96609352-7085-11ea-8f82-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96609386-7085-11ea-af78-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966093ac-7085-11ea-ac49-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should we wear a mask if we have to go to the grocery store ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should we wear a mask if we have to go to the grocery store?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4094431, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4094431, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4094431, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966093e8-7085-11ea-aaf5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96609410-7085-11ea-8d3c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96609442-7085-11ea-9308-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Wear gloves for groceries ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Wear gloves for groceries?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409458, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409458, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409458, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96609474-7085-11ea-b43e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966094a6-7085-11ea-9f9b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966094cc-7085-11ea-bc83-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What should I do ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What should I do?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409476, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409476, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409476, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96609528-7085-11ea-8c70-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96609564-7085-11ea-8ae1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660958c-7085-11ea-89cd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are covid 19 symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are covid 19 symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409491, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409491, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409491, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966095c8-7085-11ea-b288-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966095f0-7085-11ea-aac8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96609622-7085-11ea-aa39-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how to protect from Covid19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how to protect from Covid19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409506, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409506, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409506, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96609654-7085-11ea-8e02-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96609686-7085-11ea-9139-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966096ae-7085-11ea-b555-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the propagation time", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the propagation time", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4095201, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4095209, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4095209, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966096f4-7085-11ea-804c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96609726-7085-11ea-b254-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96609758-7085-11ea-8ffc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can you describe the difference between dry cough and fatty cough", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can you describe the difference between dry cough and fatty cough", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409537, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409537, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409537, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96609794-7085-11ea-9b2b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966097ba-7085-11ea-b778-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966097ee-7085-11ea-81fc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the mortality rate for Covid ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the mortality rate for Covid?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4095511, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4095519, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4095519, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660981e-7085-11ea-9880-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96609852-7085-11ea-9ad4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660987a-7085-11ea-a6f4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409566, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409566, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409566, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966098ac-7085-11ea-bdf4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966098de-7085-11ea-a9d2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96609906-7085-11ea-9754-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "As of today , can we gather only 2", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "As of today, can we gather only 2", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4095821, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4095821, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4095821, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96609958-7085-11ea-9a3e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660997e-7085-11ea-81bc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966099b0-7085-11ea-bbbd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should we stay at home if we are a health worker and have only one symptom , sore throat ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should we stay at home if we are a health worker and have only one symptom, sore throat ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409597, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409597, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409597, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966099e2-7085-11ea-accb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96609a14-7085-11ea-8cb9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96609a3a-7085-11ea-9d16-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "With online orders , we receive packages . Do these packages represent a risk of contagion ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "With online orders, we receive packages. Do these packages represent a risk of contagion?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409611, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409611, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409611, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96609a6e-7085-11ea-9c94-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96609ab4-7085-11ea-9409-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96609ae6-7085-11ea-86a8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How does COVID-19 spread ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How does COVID-19 spread?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.40963, "sourceDate": 1585352964.40963, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.40963, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96609b36-7085-11ea-93fd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96609b68-7085-11ea-88aa-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96609b90-7085-11ea-a419-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Am I at risk", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Am I at risk", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409645, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409645, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409645, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96609bc2-7085-11ea-92b4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96609bf4-7085-11ea-ba30-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96609c1c-7085-11ea-85eb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409659, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409659, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409659, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96609c58-7085-11ea-a7d9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96609c80-7085-11ea-85f0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96609ca8-7085-11ea-bbda-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to wash hands", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to wash hands", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409673, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409673, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409674, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96609ce4-7085-11ea-835d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96609d0c-7085-11ea-aa73-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96609d3e-7085-11ea-a04d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long can the virus survive depending on the type of surface ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long can the virus survive depending on the type of surface?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4096901, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4096901, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4096901, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96609d86-7085-11ea-b552-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96609db6-7085-11ea-93b7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96609ea6-7085-11ea-9eca-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I go out for a walk in the park everyday ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I go out for a walk in the park everyday?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4097311, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4097311, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4097311, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96609f28-7085-11ea-9634-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96609f98-7085-11ea-8f44-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96609fc8-7085-11ea-8adf-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How should I keep my family safe during covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How should I keep my family safe during covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409754, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409754, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409754, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660a006-7085-11ea-b227-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660a036-7085-11ea-96f7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660a068-7085-11ea-af8a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are the symptoms of covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are the symptoms of covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409771, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409771, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409771, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660a0b8-7085-11ea-a6fc-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660a0e8-7085-11ea-9b63-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660a11c-7085-11ea-ab23-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How serious is COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How serious is COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4097862, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4097862, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409787, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660a14c-7085-11ea-aae2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660a180-7085-11ea-957f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660a1a8-7085-11ea-b1eb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can my morning newspaper carry the virus if the delivery man is a carrier ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can my morning newspaper carry the virus if the delivery man is a carrier?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409806, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409806, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409806, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660a20c-7085-11ea-851e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660a23e-7085-11ea-a06f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660a270-7085-11ea-89a4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the survival rate of COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the survival rate of COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4098198, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409821, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409821, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660a2a2-7085-11ea-83eb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660a2d4-7085-11ea-ae77-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660a2fa-7085-11ea-b1ae-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have a cold but do n't have a fever , should I consult ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have a cold but don't have a fever, should I consult?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409836, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409836, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409836, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660a34c-7085-11ea-9f04-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660a37e-7085-11ea-b976-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660a3b0-7085-11ea-b593-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the risk of dying from COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the risk of dying from COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409853, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409853, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409853, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660a3ec-7085-11ea-bded-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660a414-7085-11ea-a4e0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660a43a-7085-11ea-bb0e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there a treatment for corona virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there a treatment for corona virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409867, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409867, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409867, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660a478-7085-11ea-9574-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660a49e-7085-11ea-b316-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660a4d2-7085-11ea-b154-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many deaths in the world today ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many deaths in the world today?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4098828, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4098828, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4098828, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660a518-7085-11ea-a9f4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660a54a-7085-11ea-8d61-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660a574-7085-11ea-b88f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I have sex with a stranger ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I have sex with a stranger?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4099, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4099, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4099, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660a5b8-7085-11ea-b21f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660a608-7085-11ea-99e6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660a63a-7085-11ea-923e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I am in self isolation . Is it ok to let in family members who must continue to go to work ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I am in self isolation. Is it ok to let in family members who must continue to go to work?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4099169, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409918, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409918, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660a66c-7085-11ea-a9d1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660a69e-7085-11ea-9e6b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660a6c6-7085-11ea-a309-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many cases of coronavirus in Madagascar", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many cases of coronavirus in Madagascar", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4099321, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4099321, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4099321, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660a6f8-7085-11ea-8e4b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660a728-7085-11ea-b98d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660a752-7085-11ea-9ead-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Doeas the software is automatic in English because I use an English device ? If I ask in French the answer will be in French ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Doeas the software is automatic in English because I use an English device? If I ask in French the answer will be in French?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4099462, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4099462, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4099462, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660a78c-7085-11ea-81b6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660a7ca-7085-11ea-a144-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660a7f4-7085-11ea-bc5a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Which viruses have a reproduction number similar to that of covid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Which viruses have a reproduction number similar to that of covid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409962, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409962, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409962, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660a82e-7085-11ea-b9f2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660a862-7085-11ea-9922-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660a888-7085-11ea-8812-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How do you catch the Covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How do you catch the Covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4099772, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4099772, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4099772, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660a8c6-7085-11ea-b275-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660a8ec-7085-11ea-bc77-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660a928-7085-11ea-a2f8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does it take until a carrier of the virus can infect others ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does it take until a carrier of the virus can infect others?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.409994, "sourceDate": 1585352964.409994, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.409994, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660a96e-7085-11ea-843d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660a99e-7085-11ea-ac91-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660a9d2-7085-11ea-9685-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the risks for my parents ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the risks for my parents?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410013, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410013, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410013, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660aa22-7085-11ea-9645-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660aa5e-7085-11ea-a23d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660aa86-7085-11ea-937c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Info sant\u00e9 811 told us that he would call us for an appointment but they still do n't have to do it to have a screening appointment", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Info sant\u00e9 811 told us that he would call us for an appointment but they still don't have to do it to have a screening appointment", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410028, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410028, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410028, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660aab8-7085-11ea-87de-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660aafe-7085-11ea-8dd3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660ab30-7085-11ea-b2ae-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why I ca n't telecommute in the health field", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why I can't telecommute in the health field", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410045, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410045, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410045, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660ab62-7085-11ea-a512-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660ab94-7085-11ea-a84e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660abba-7085-11ea-ac8d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are you real person", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are you real person", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410059, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410059, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41006, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660abf8-7085-11ea-903f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660ac28-7085-11ea-afb5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660ac52-7085-11ea-9fdc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will I be fined if I leave my home ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will I be fined if I leave my home?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410074, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410074, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410074, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660ac98-7085-11ea-9eff-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660acca-7085-11ea-89c0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660acfa-7085-11ea-966b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Fwfegebrbrbtbtbtj", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Fwfegebrbrbtbtbtj", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410091, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410091, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410091, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660ad2e-7085-11ea-be22-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660ad62-7085-11ea-a4e6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660ad88-7085-11ea-b846-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When we receive a delivery of groceries , what should we do to disinfect the meat packaging ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When we receive a delivery of groceries, what should we do to disinfect the meat packaging?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4101062, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4101062, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4101062, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660adcc-7085-11ea-a928-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660adf6-7085-11ea-a906-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660ae28-7085-11ea-b0bd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What about the researches with respect to treatment of COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What about the researches with respect to treatment of COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410123, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410123, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410123, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660ae6e-7085-11ea-9665-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660ae9e-7085-11ea-8b2d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660aec8-7085-11ea-893d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What should I do if I do n't feel any symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What should I do if I don't feel any symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4101372, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4101381, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4101381, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660af06-7085-11ea-8dec-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660af4a-7085-11ea-bc2e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660af90-7085-11ea-8fe0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I keep going doing my sport outside ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I keep going doing my sport outside?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4101582, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4101582, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4101582, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660afcc-7085-11ea-8220-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660affe-7085-11ea-8de7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660b026-7085-11ea-815e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does everyone infected need a respirator ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does everyone infected need a respirator?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410172, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410172, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410172, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660b062-7085-11ea-95ab-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660b08a-7085-11ea-9166-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660b0b4-7085-11ea-bc56-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How effective is the new drug manufactured by Fujifilm Toyama Chemicals in treating COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How effective is the new drug manufactured by Fujifilm Toyama Chemicals in treating COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410186, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410186, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410187, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660b0ee-7085-11ea-b5ca-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660b134-7085-11ea-973c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660b166-7085-11ea-a768-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is the question , are you coming from travel still relevant ? Messeble that the spread is beyond that ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is the question, are you coming from travel still relevant? Messeble that the spread is beyond that?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410203, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410204, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410204, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660b198-7085-11ea-814a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660b1ca-7085-11ea-b62a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660b1f4-7085-11ea-8205-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long before symptoms appear ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long before symptoms appear?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410218, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410218, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410218, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660b224-7085-11ea-8fd1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660b258-7085-11ea-984d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660b27e-7085-11ea-9208-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Need help", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Need help", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4102342, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4102342, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4102342, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660b2cc-7085-11ea-b24e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660b2f6-7085-11ea-8d67-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660b328-7085-11ea-8d56-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I go for a walk ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I go for a walk?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410249, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410249, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410249, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660b35a-7085-11ea-95a4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660b38c-7085-11ea-a610-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660b3b4-7085-11ea-94e4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it OK I go out for a walk alone ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it OK I go out for a walk alone?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410263, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410263, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410263, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660b3e6-7085-11ea-9966-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660b418-7085-11ea-94c3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660b440-7085-11ea-8737-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My immune system is very weak , can I still go grocery shopping ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My immune system is very weak, can I still go grocery shopping?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4102788, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4102788, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4102788, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660b486-7085-11ea-a39f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660b4b8-7085-11ea-8a02-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660b4e2-7085-11ea-88fa-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can cats transmit the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can cats transmit the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410293, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410293, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410293, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660b51c-7085-11ea-9ab2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660b546-7085-11ea-b067-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660b576-7085-11ea-bef0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does the coronavirus survive when an infected person dies ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does the coronavirus survive when an infected person dies?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4103081, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4103081, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4103081, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660b5a8-7085-11ea-b4f1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660b634-7085-11ea-bcd9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660b6f4-7085-11ea-b9e7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many covid cases are in Quebec ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many covid cases are in Quebec?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410351, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410351, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410351, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660b762-7085-11ea-80cd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660b79c-7085-11ea-911e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660b7d8-7085-11ea-9a91-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I breathe badly , am I infected ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I breathe badly, am I infected?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410369, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410369, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410369, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660b814-7085-11ea-beaa-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660b83a-7085-11ea-a8c9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660b86e-7085-11ea-8028-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What medications can I take to treat my virus pain ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What medications can I take to treat my virus pain?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410384, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410384, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410384, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660b89e-7085-11ea-9c09-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660b8d2-7085-11ea-9ae2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660b8fa-7085-11ea-8944-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why Germany has a low death rate ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why Germany has a low death rate?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410398, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410398, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410398, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660b936-7085-11ea-b4ec-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660b95e-7085-11ea-a08f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660b990-7085-11ea-bc9d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many covid-19 deaths in the past week", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many covid-19 deaths in the past week", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4104168, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4104168, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4104168, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660b9e8-7085-11ea-b5ce-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660ba26-7085-11ea-a869-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660ba4c-7085-11ea-9766-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Testing", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Testing", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410432, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410432, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410432, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660ba80-7085-11ea-a089-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660bac6-7085-11ea-af72-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660baf8-7085-11ea-9275-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can animals transmit the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can animals transmit the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410452, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410452, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410452, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660bb48-7085-11ea-91cb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660bcec-7085-11ea-b3f0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660bd5a-7085-11ea-85bb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I got the virus and am cured , can I still spread the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I got the virus and am cured, can I still spread the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41052, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41052, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41052, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660bdfa-7085-11ea-af38-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660bed8-7085-11ea-81e8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660bf12-7085-11ea-93cb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I wash my hands every time I touch my phone ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I wash my hands every time I touch my phone?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410555, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410555, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410555, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660bf4c-7085-11ea-84a2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660bf80-7085-11ea-bb50-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660bfa8-7085-11ea-b950-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does blood type influence the ability of the virus to infect a person ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does blood type influence the ability of the virus to infect a person?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410569, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410569, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41057, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660bfe4-7085-11ea-8282-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660c018-7085-11ea-acaa-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660c03e-7085-11ea-bafd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410584, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410584, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410584, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660c07a-7085-11ea-9ffb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660c0a2-7085-11ea-adda-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660c0d4-7085-11ea-839e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "when covid 19 is going to stop ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "when covid 19 is going to stop?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410599, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410599, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410599, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660c106-7085-11ea-a548-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660c138-7085-11ea-ac54-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660c162-7085-11ea-ad0a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can my cat or dog catch covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can my cat or dog catch covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410613, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410613, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410613, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660c19c-7085-11ea-b2de-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660c1c6-7085-11ea-bae0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660c200-7085-11ea-83a7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus stay active in the air ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus stay active in the air?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410629, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410629, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410629, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660c23a-7085-11ea-8459-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660c26e-7085-11ea-a0ec-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660c298-7085-11ea-b3c1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "For how long will the containment be in place ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "For how long will the containment be in place?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4106472, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410648, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410648, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660c2f0-7085-11ea-b341-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660c322-7085-11ea-98d5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660c354-7085-11ea-8036-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long will it last ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long will it last?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410663, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410663, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410663, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660c390-7085-11ea-b314-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660c3b8-7085-11ea-ae55-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660c3e8-7085-11ea-a760-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "covid19 symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "covid19 symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410677, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410677, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410678, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660c41c-7085-11ea-8433-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660c446-7085-11ea-817f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660c476-7085-11ea-8d64-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what treatments are available for covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what treatments are available for covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4106922, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4106922, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4106922, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660c4a8-7085-11ea-8b27-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660c4da-7085-11ea-a5ef-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660c502-7085-11ea-860d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the age most sensitive to covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the age most sensitive to covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4107058, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4107058, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4107058, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660c53e-7085-11ea-a9b4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660c566-7085-11ea-af47-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660c58c-7085-11ea-bc10-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When do I expect to hear back from you ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When do I expect to hear back from you?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410721, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410721, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410721, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660c5ca-7085-11ea-87e3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660c624-7085-11ea-a27f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660c658-7085-11ea-b6f3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Tengo tos y dolor muscular que deberia hacer ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Tengo tos y dolor muscular que deberia hacer?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41074, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41074, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41074, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660c688-7085-11ea-aa82-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660c6ba-7085-11ea-88e2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660c6e2-7085-11ea-aa5f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does covid-19 spread in tropical conditions ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does covid-19 spread in tropical conditions?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410754, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410754, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410754, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660c71e-7085-11ea-a687-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660c746-7085-11ea-b07c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660c782-7085-11ea-95b1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can coronaviruses be transmitted from person to person", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can coronaviruses be transmitted from person to person", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410772, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410772, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410772, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660c7d2-7085-11ea-9747-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660c80c-7085-11ea-9b00-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660c836-7085-11ea-9ce6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long am I contagious ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long am I contagious?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410788, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410788, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410788, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660c874-7085-11ea-864a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660c89a-7085-11ea-a909-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660c8cc-7085-11ea-a2e5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it transmissible through anal sex ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it transmissible through anal sex?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4108028, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4108028, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4108028, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660c908-7085-11ea-88ce-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660c930-7085-11ea-9dc0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660c962-7085-11ea-9a2c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is COVID-19 lethal ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is COVID-19 lethal?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410818, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410818, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410818, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660c994-7085-11ea-b651-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660c9c6-7085-11ea-b06e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660c9ee-7085-11ea-a076-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I be contagious even if I do n't have symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I be contagious even if I don't have symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410832, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410832, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410832, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660ca28-7085-11ea-a4b9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660ca52-7085-11ea-812e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660ca7a-7085-11ea-b74d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there a vaccine for a new coronavirus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there a vaccine for a new coronavirus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410846, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410846, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410846, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660cab6-7085-11ea-84a5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660cade-7085-11ea-8931-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660cb10-7085-11ea-85c8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is total containment necessary for a person suffering from a respiratory disorder ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is total containment necessary for a person suffering from a respiratory disorder?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410861, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410861, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410861, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660cb42-7085-11ea-80e5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660cb74-7085-11ea-b799-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660cb9c-7085-11ea-b8fa-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My boyfriend experienced gastro intestinal symptoms and came from abroad , should he get tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My boyfriend experienced gastro intestinal symptoms and came from abroad, should he get tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410877, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410877, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410877, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660cbe2-7085-11ea-94d8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660cc28-7085-11ea-ae9b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660cc5a-7085-11ea-9f06-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can I protect my child from COVID-19 infection", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can I protect my child from COVID-19 infection", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4108942, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4108942, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4108942, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660cc8c-7085-11ea-a799-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660ccbe-7085-11ea-bffb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660cce6-7085-11ea-b48c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Could we give by region the number of hospitalizations linked to Covid-19 in intensive care and curative care compared to the number of positive tested at home ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Could we give by region the number of hospitalizations linked to Covid-19 in intensive care and curative care compared to the number of positive tested at home?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410908, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410908, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410908, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660cd22-7085-11ea-91f3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660cd4a-7085-11ea-bcd2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660cd7a-7085-11ea-93e1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can my cat get the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can my cat get the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410922, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410922, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410923, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660cdae-7085-11ea-970c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660cdd8-7085-11ea-bcdb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660ced0-7085-11ea-961c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the best ways to protect yourself from covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the best ways to protect yourself from covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410964, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410964, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410964, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660cf52-7085-11ea-8f85-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660cf8c-7085-11ea-b14b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660cfc0-7085-11ea-be30-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can you get be infected more than once ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can you get be infected more than once?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.410996, "sourceDate": 1585352964.410996, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.410996, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660d092-7085-11ea-ba12-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660d0cc-7085-11ea-866d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660d114-7085-11ea-a6f5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When will the borders open again and when will we be able to start traveling safely ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When will the borders open again and when will we be able to start traveling safely?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411016, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411016, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411016, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660d15a-7085-11ea-9740-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660d182-7085-11ea-b80b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660d1b4-7085-11ea-aad1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I get coronavirus by eating food that is manipulated or prepared by others", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I get coronavirus by eating food that is manipulated or prepared by others", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411031, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411031, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411031, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660d1e6-7085-11ea-84c7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660d218-7085-11ea-a590-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660d240-7085-11ea-80be-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long before it can be tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long before it can be tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411048, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411048, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411048, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660d29a-7085-11ea-a97e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660d2cc-7085-11ea-a624-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660d2f4-7085-11ea-b860-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does Covid-19 last when contracted by a person ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does Covid-19 last when contracted by a person?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411063, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411063, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411063, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660d326-7085-11ea-9f70-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660d358-7085-11ea-a7d9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660d380-7085-11ea-b076-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the risks for a person between 20 and 40 years old with asthma ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the risks for a person between 20 and 40 years old with asthma?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411078, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411078, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411078, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660d3c6-7085-11ea-b942-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660d40c-7085-11ea-8834-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660d434-7085-11ea-be2b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "are outdoor walks considered safe ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "are outdoor walks considered safe?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411096, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411096, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411096, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660d48c-7085-11ea-a3e2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660d4c0-7085-11ea-80ff-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660d4f4-7085-11ea-9816-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "temperature covid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "temperature covid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411115, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4111161, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4111161, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660d538-7085-11ea-bf12-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660d568-7085-11ea-8f2c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660d59c-7085-11ea-a944-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the first symptoms of Coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the first symptoms of Coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411131, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411131, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411131, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660d5cc-7085-11ea-a99f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660d600-7085-11ea-93d5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660d628-7085-11ea-9848-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how many people died ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how many people died?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411145, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411145, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411145, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660d664-7085-11ea-b4cd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660d68c-7085-11ea-87c5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660d6be-7085-11ea-ae9d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do people develop immunity to coronaviruses", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do people develop immunity to coronaviruses", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41116, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41116, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41116, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660d6f0-7085-11ea-975e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660d722-7085-11ea-825a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660d74a-7085-11ea-8f32-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I get Ovid 19 if someone pets my dog \u200b\u200band then I pet her ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I get Ovid 19 if someone pets my dog \u200b\u200band then I pet her?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4111738, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4111738, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4111738, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660d77a-7085-11ea-955d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660d7ae-7085-11ea-bdc0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660d7d8-7085-11ea-9f73-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I transmit covid 19 if I have already had it ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I transmit covid 19 if I have already had it?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411188, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411188, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411188, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660d812-7085-11ea-9cac-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660d83a-7085-11ea-9095-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660d86c-7085-11ea-9c86-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What medication is recommended if I contract covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What medication is recommended if I contract covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4112031, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4112031, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4112031, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660d89e-7085-11ea-87df-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660d8f8-7085-11ea-909b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660d91e-7085-11ea-b222-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When is the peak expected in the USA ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When is the peak expected in the USA?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411223, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411223, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411223, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660d970-7085-11ea-b1a4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660d9a2-7085-11ea-8ce7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660d9ca-7085-11ea-b599-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the evolution of the virus in Montreal ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the evolution of the virus in Montreal?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411238, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411238, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411238, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660d9fa-7085-11ea-be8d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660da2e-7085-11ea-b8bb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660da62-7085-11ea-8aa2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are we in a period of community transmission ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are we in a period of community transmission?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411257, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411257, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411257, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660dac6-7085-11ea-bde8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660db00-7085-11ea-b53e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660db28-7085-11ea-ac54-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where can I volunteer to help people in isolation in need ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where can I volunteer to help people in isolation in need?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411273, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411273, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411273, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660db5a-7085-11ea-aff8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660db9e-7085-11ea-a368-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660dbc8-7085-11ea-9ee1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the confirmed symptoms of COVID19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the confirmed symptoms of COVID19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411289, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411289, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411289, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660dc06-7085-11ea-9a17-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660dc2c-7085-11ea-b6d2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660dc5e-7085-11ea-8fb2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are are my chances of dying if I have the covid 19 virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are are my chances of dying if I have the covid 19 virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411304, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411304, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411304, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660dc90-7085-11ea-91c1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660dcd8-7085-11ea-bbbd-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660dd08-7085-11ea-8146-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Could you answer the questions of the health workers ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Could you answer the questions of the health workers?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4113212, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4113212, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4113212, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660dd46-7085-11ea-aee2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660dd6c-7085-11ea-940a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660dd9e-7085-11ea-9055-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is fever the main symptom for vivid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is fever the main symptom for vivid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411338, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411338, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411338, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660dde4-7085-11ea-9cf8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660de18-7085-11ea-9ba9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660de48-7085-11ea-b71f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how will unsubsidized family daycare be paid ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how will unsubsidized family daycare be paid?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411353, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411353, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411353, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660de7a-7085-11ea-9f41-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660deac-7085-11ea-bafe-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660ded4-7085-11ea-8204-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I go and bring food to a quarantined person ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I go and bring food to a quarantined person?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4113688, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4113688, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4113688, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660df1a-7085-11ea-b85b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660df4c-7085-11ea-8876-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660df7e-7085-11ea-9076-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How do we protect ourselves ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How do we protect ourselves?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4113832, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4113832, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411384, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660dfb0-7085-11ea-bbc8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660dfe2-7085-11ea-a918-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660e00a-7085-11ea-b202-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many days should I isolate for", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many days should I isolate for", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411399, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411399, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411399, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660e046-7085-11ea-a417-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660e12c-7085-11ea-915a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660e1a4-7085-11ea-b31e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many cases are in the US ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many cases are in the US?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4114418, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4114418, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4114418, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660e1fe-7085-11ea-b231-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660e23a-7085-11ea-9aed-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660e262-7085-11ea-a614-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I am pregnant and I have follow - ups in the hospital . Can I be accompanied ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I am pregnant and I have follow-ups in the hospital. Can I be accompanied?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411459, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411459, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411459, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660e29e-7085-11ea-a02d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660e2d0-7085-11ea-966f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660e2f8-7085-11ea-b0bb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My daughter 's spouse works in a hospital . Is it risky that she comes to visit us ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My daughter's spouse works in a hospital. Is it risky that she comes to visit us?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4114728, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4114728, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4114728, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660e334-7085-11ea-bbe6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660e35c-7085-11ea-931e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660e38c-7085-11ea-a42d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Y'a - t'il", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Y'a-t'il", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4114912, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4114912, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4114912, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660e3e8-7085-11ea-b5f8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660e41a-7085-11ea-b9fa-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660e442-7085-11ea-95ac-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "can we catch the Covid-19 more than once ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "can we catch the Covid-19 more than once?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411506, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411506, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411506, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660e47e-7085-11ea-a247-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660e4a6-7085-11ea-a859-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660e4cc-7085-11ea-8686-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are the major symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are the major symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41152, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41152, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41152, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660e50a-7085-11ea-90ad-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660e550-7085-11ea-8bc8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660e578-7085-11ea-9fa8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "who do i call", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "who do i call", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411537, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411537, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411538, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660e5b4-7085-11ea-a08c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660e5dc-7085-11ea-95f9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660e60c-7085-11ea-9f3b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What to do when you have doubts about your health", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What to do when you have doubts about your health", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411551, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411551, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411551, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660e640-7085-11ea-9f29-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660e668-7085-11ea-a978-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660e69a-7085-11ea-8c31-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long is the treatment ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long is the treatment?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411566, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4115672, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4115672, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660e6d8-7085-11ea-9115-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660e708-7085-11ea-a370-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660e73a-7085-11ea-8e8e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it safe to order food during the COVID-19 pandemic ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it safe to order food during the COVID-19 pandemic?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411582, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411582, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411582, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660e776-7085-11ea-84e2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660e79e-7085-11ea-a922-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660e7d0-7085-11ea-ba98-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Chloroquine treats COVID19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Chloroquine treats COVID19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411598, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411598, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411598, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660e818-7085-11ea-9bbe-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660e83e-7085-11ea-81ae-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660e870-7085-11ea-83f8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I cough but I do n't have a fever should I get tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I cough but I don't have a fever should I get tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411613, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411613, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411613, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660e8a2-7085-11ea-ae9e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660e8d4-7085-11ea-ac39-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660e8fa-7085-11ea-a88b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I be moving house during a pandemic ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I be moving house during a pandemic?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411627, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411627, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411627, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660e92e-7085-11ea-bf09-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660e962-7085-11ea-980b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660e988-7085-11ea-96b6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can we go running or is it better to stay at home ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can we go running or is it better to stay at home?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4116411, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4116411, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4116411, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660e9ba-7085-11ea-af6d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660e9ec-7085-11ea-bdb4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660ea14-7085-11ea-872c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "symptoms of covid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "symptoms of covid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411655, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411655, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411655, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660ea46-7085-11ea-92a9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660ea78-7085-11ea-98fe-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660ea9e-7085-11ea-ac32-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have lung disease and I am infected with covid-19 , how long will it take before pass away ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have lung disease and I am infected with covid-19, how long will it take before pass away?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411669, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411669, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411669, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660ead2-7085-11ea-8bae-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660eb18-7085-11ea-b581-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660eb4a-7085-11ea-9a83-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is fever the first symptom or sore throat ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is fever the first symptom or sore throat?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4116852, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411686, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411686, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660eb7a-7085-11ea-8d2d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660eba4-7085-11ea-b508-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660ebd8-7085-11ea-920f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of Covid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of Covid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411702, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411702, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411702, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660ec1c-7085-11ea-8adb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660ed1e-7085-11ea-bc9d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660eda2-7085-11ea-bc2a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where does the name COVID-19 come from ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where does the name COVID-19 come from?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4117491, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4117491, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4117491, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660edfa-7085-11ea-b5c6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660ee2e-7085-11ea-b1ff-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660ef9e-7085-11ea-851d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How does coronavirus spread ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How does coronavirus spread?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411797, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411797, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411798, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660efdc-7085-11ea-bdbf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660f00c-7085-11ea-bab2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660f036-7085-11ea-bace-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does COVID 19 cause stomach issues", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does COVID 19 cause stomach issues", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411815, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411815, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411815, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660f086-7085-11ea-8d32-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660f0c2-7085-11ea-a690-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660f108-7085-11ea-9375-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does it take to recover ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does it take to recover?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411833, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411833, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411834, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660f146-7085-11ea-a402-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660f18a-7085-11ea-bdbd-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660f1b4-7085-11ea-a494-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I test negative , am I immune ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I test negative, am I immune?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41185, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411851, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411851, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660f1ee-7085-11ea-a4d0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660f21e-7085-11ea-8296-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660f248-7085-11ea-90ce-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have a chronic illness which puts me at increased risk of contracting a serious illness from COVID-19 , even though I am only in my thirties . What can I do to reduce my risk", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have a chronic illness which puts me at increased risk of contracting a serious illness from COVID-19, even though I am only in my thirties. What can I do to reduce my risk", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411865, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411865, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411865, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660f286-7085-11ea-9235-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660f2ac-7085-11ea-a0ee-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660f2d4-7085-11ea-ab0d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the total number of deaths", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the total number of deaths", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411881, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411882, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411882, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660f32e-7085-11ea-bc6f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660f362-7085-11ea-8b9d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660f392-7085-11ea-b9d1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Or get tested", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Or get tested", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4118981, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4118981, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4118981, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660f3cc-7085-11ea-99fe-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660f3f6-7085-11ea-9654-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660f428-7085-11ea-8c96-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus stay on surfaces , clothes or food ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus stay on surfaces, clothes or food?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411913, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411913, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411913, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660f45a-7085-11ea-9ad8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660f48c-7085-11ea-a45f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660f4b4-7085-11ea-b424-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What to do if I have symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What to do if I have symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4119291, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4119291, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4119291, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660f506-7085-11ea-9f9d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660f536-7085-11ea-8c79-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660f55e-7085-11ea-891e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "if someone had pneumonia before , are they more at risk ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "if someone had pneumonia before, are they more at risk?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4119449, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4119449, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4119449, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660f59a-7085-11ea-80ae-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660f5d8-7085-11ea-9e82-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660f5fe-7085-11ea-a174-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does it take before the first symptoms can be detected ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does it take before the first symptoms can be detected?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4119601, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4119601, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4119601, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660f63a-7085-11ea-9fdf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660f662-7085-11ea-91b4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660f694-7085-11ea-a87f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to protect my family from COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to protect my family from COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411974, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411975, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411975, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660f6c6-7085-11ea-b257-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660f6f8-7085-11ea-95c6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660f71e-7085-11ea-aceb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how long will it last", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how long will it last", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.411989, "sourceDate": 1585352964.411989, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.411989, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660f752-7085-11ea-9881-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660f786-7085-11ea-83c9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660f7c0-7085-11ea-949d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the covid-19 symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the covid-19 symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4120052, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4120052, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4120052, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660f7fa-7085-11ea-8087-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660f824-7085-11ea-93a4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660f858-7085-11ea-8d78-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When will it be ok to go outside ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When will it be ok to go outside?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41202, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41202, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41202, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660f888-7085-11ea-a5cf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660f8ba-7085-11ea-99f6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660f8e2-7085-11ea-898f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "exists cura para virus em geral ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "exists cura para virus em geral?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4120371, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4120371, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4120371, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660f93a-7085-11ea-95c7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660f9fa-7085-11ea-a087-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660fa86-7085-11ea-9a62-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I cough what should I do ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I cough what should I do?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41208, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41208, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41208, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660fae8-7085-11ea-9d76-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660fb26-7085-11ea-83d8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660fb58-7085-11ea-903e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I work from home ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I work from home?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412102, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412102, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412102, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660fbc6-7085-11ea-8715-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660fc18-7085-11ea-8480-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660fc48-7085-11ea-b6ec-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are masks efficient to prevent the one wearing from getting infected ? What about infecting others ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are masks efficient to prevent the one wearing from getting infected? What about infecting others?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412121, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412121, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412121, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660fc86-7085-11ea-976b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660fcac-7085-11ea-b138-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660fcde-7085-11ea-9d04-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is shortness of breath part of the symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is shortness of breath part of the symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4121358, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4121358, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4121358, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660fd10-7085-11ea-8cac-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660fd42-7085-11ea-a404-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660fd68-7085-11ea-ab77-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of the disease ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of the disease?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41215, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41215, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41215, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660fd9c-7085-11ea-bd8e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660fdcc-7085-11ea-abe2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660fdf6-7085-11ea-ae64-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how many people in America ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how many people in America?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4121642, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4121642, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4121642, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660fe28-7085-11ea-9211-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660fe5a-7085-11ea-819b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660fe82-7085-11ea-a5d2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how long will the pandemic last", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how long will the pandemic last", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41218, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412181, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412181, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660fed2-7085-11ea-8eba-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660ff18-7085-11ea-986c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660ff4a-7085-11ea-ba86-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will spring reduce transmission ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will spring reduce transmission?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4121978, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4121978, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4121978, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9660ff7a-7085-11ea-adfe-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9660ffae-7085-11ea-92d1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9660ffd8-7085-11ea-8595-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do I need to get tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do I need to get tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412212, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412212, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412212, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96610012-7085-11ea-a4f4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96610062-7085-11ea-bde5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661008a-7085-11ea-906d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "could we have done better ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "could we have done better?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412231, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412231, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412231, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966100d0-7085-11ea-a8fb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966100f8-7085-11ea-b6fd-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96610128-7085-11ea-88ea-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How much longer will society need to socially isolate ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How much longer will society need to socially isolate?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412245, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412245, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412245, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661015c-7085-11ea-97f2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96610186-7085-11ea-98df-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966101b6-7085-11ea-9bac-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I work at complex g , am I at risk ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I work at complex g, am I at risk?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412259, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41226, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41226, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966101e8-7085-11ea-aaaa-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661021a-7085-11ea-bdba-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96610242-7085-11ea-9444-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there a cure for the disease ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there a cure for the disease?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412274, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412274, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412274, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96610274-7085-11ea-bee6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966102a6-7085-11ea-9bdc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966102cc-7085-11ea-884a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many deaths from coronavirus in the past week", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many deaths from coronavirus in the past week", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41229, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41229, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41229, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661031e-7085-11ea-9f70-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96610346-7085-11ea-b21e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96610378-7085-11ea-9a14-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are children immune to the virus that causes COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are children immune to the virus that causes COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412304, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4123049, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4123049, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966103a8-7085-11ea-8d85-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966103dc-7085-11ea-80c3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96610406-7085-11ea-97fc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should he self isolate when he gets here even if he feels well ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should he self isolate when he gets here even if he feels well?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412319, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412319, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412319, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96610440-7085-11ea-bce0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96610468-7085-11ea-b261-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661049a-7085-11ea-b5ef-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "should I go to the emergency room if I have symptoms of colds and fever ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "should I go to the emergency room if I have symptoms of colds and fever?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412334, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412334, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412334, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966104cc-7085-11ea-b3e0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96610512-7085-11ea-9b93-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96610546-7085-11ea-b5da-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can I get tested if I 'm asymptomatic ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can I get tested if I'm asymptomatic?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412351, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412351, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412351, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96610576-7085-11ea-bda3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966105a8-7085-11ea-8123-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966105d0-7085-11ea-a9dd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Ages at risk", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Ages at risk", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412365, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412365, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412365, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96610602-7085-11ea-8eed-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96610634-7085-11ea-a361-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661065c-7085-11ea-853e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there any possibility of infected corona virus second time ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there any possibility of infected corona virus second time?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4123788, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4123788, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4123788, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96610698-7085-11ea-872d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966106ca-7085-11ea-b847-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966106fa-7085-11ea-90a4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "am I allowed to go play in the park ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "am I allowed to go play in the park?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4123971, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4123971, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4123971, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661074c-7085-11ea-a2fd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661077e-7085-11ea-a92d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966107a6-7085-11ea-b894-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how many people have died in the US ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how many people have died in the US?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412412, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412412, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412412, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966107d8-7085-11ea-807b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661080a-7085-11ea-b786-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96610834-7085-11ea-807e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Emergency sms should be used by our leaders .", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Emergency sms should be used by our leaders.", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412426, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412426, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412426, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661086e-7085-11ea-9206-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96610898-7085-11ea-9e5a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966108c8-7085-11ea-9d12-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are the symptoms of COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are the symptoms of COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412441, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412441, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412441, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966108fa-7085-11ea-bba3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661092c-7085-11ea-a95e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96610954-7085-11ea-91b9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus remain on fruits and vegetables ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus remain on fruits and vegetables?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4124548, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4124548, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4124548, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96610990-7085-11ea-8b61-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966109b8-7085-11ea-8f84-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966109e2-7085-11ea-9af5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do I have to wear gloves and mask ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do I have to wear gloves and mask?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412469, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412469, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412469, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96610a1c-7085-11ea-b798-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96610a46-7085-11ea-976b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96610a76-7085-11ea-a8c5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long are we contagious ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long are we contagious?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4124842, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4124842, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4124842, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96610aa8-7085-11ea-be07-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96610ada-7085-11ea-96d0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96610b02-7085-11ea-af9b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When should I put on a mask ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When should I put on a mask?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412499, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4125, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4125, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96610b48-7085-11ea-a6a2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96610b86-7085-11ea-a800-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96610bb6-7085-11ea-bd00-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When would we be confined ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When would we be confined?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412516, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412516, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412516, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96610bf4-7085-11ea-ba58-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96610c1a-7085-11ea-8ec4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96610c4c-7085-11ea-a0f7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will the substitutes be entitled to financial assistance ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will the substitutes be entitled to financial assistance?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41253, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41253, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41253, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96610c7e-7085-11ea-994a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96610ca6-7085-11ea-bbd1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96610cd8-7085-11ea-997c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Even if he lives for several hours on a surface , is he as strong after 1 hour as after 1 minute .", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Even if he lives for several hours on a surface, is he as strong after 1 hour as after 1 minute.", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412544, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412544, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412545, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96610d0a-7085-11ea-be32-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96610d50-7085-11ea-84ce-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96610d78-7085-11ea-99b0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does COVID-19 spread by means of gametes ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does COVID-19 spread by means of gametes?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412561, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412561, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412561, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96610db4-7085-11ea-99f5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96610ddc-7085-11ea-9964-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96610e22-7085-11ea-9d9d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can dogs , cats catch and transmit the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can dogs, cats catch and transmit the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412578, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412578, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412578, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96610e5e-7085-11ea-9588-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96610e86-7085-11ea-a024-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96610eae-7085-11ea-8dc5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I would like to get COVID19 test , where can I get it ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I would like to get COVID19 test, where can I get it?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4125922, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4125922, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4125922, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96610ee8-7085-11ea-a048-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96610f12-7085-11ea-97c6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96610f3a-7085-11ea-9cef-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Impacts of it", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Impacts of it", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412606, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412606, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412606, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96610f76-7085-11ea-8a45-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96610f9e-7085-11ea-a52f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96610fd0-7085-11ea-bd22-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do sinusrinse treatments help prevention ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do sinusrinse treatments help prevention?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412622, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412622, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412622, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611018-7085-11ea-92f8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661103e-7085-11ea-9d1d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96611070-7085-11ea-b383-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms for COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms for COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412637, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412637, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412637, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966110a2-7085-11ea-87d0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966110e8-7085-11ea-8ea2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96611110-7085-11ea-92fd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do I have to wear a mask to get out of my house ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do I have to wear a mask to get out of my house?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412653, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412653, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412653, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611142-7085-11ea-ba14-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661117e-7085-11ea-9162-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966111b0-7085-11ea-adb8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "LP TEST question", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "LP TEST question", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412669, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412669, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412669, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966111ec-7085-11ea-8d81-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96611214-7085-11ea-a77c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96611246-7085-11ea-a45b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I wash my hands with hot water to destroy the coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I wash my hands with hot water to destroy the coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412684, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412684, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412684, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611278-7085-11ea-a81e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966112a8-7085-11ea-8c15-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966112d2-7085-11ea-84a7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When will it end ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When will it end?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412698, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412698, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412698, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611306-7085-11ea-a925-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96611336-7085-11ea-83ee-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661135e-7085-11ea-a232-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My mother is over 70 years old and she lives alone . Can I go for a walk with her ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My mother is over 70 years old and she lives alone. Can I go for a walk with her?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4127119, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4127119, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4127119, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611390-7085-11ea-87c3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966113c2-7085-11ea-abe5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966113e8-7085-11ea-a3c4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Anything else?question", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Anything else?question", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412728, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412728, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412728, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661143a-7085-11ea-a397-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96611462-7085-11ea-b0be-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96611494-7085-11ea-a0ce-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have a sore throat without any other symptoms . Do I have to worry ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have a sore throat without any other symptoms. Do I have to worry?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4127429, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4127429, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4127429, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966114c6-7085-11ea-923b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966114f8-7085-11ea-ae66-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661151e-7085-11ea-8acb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412757, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412757, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412757, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661155c-7085-11ea-a68b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96611586-7085-11ea-b5de-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966115ac-7085-11ea-9ea9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus remain on a surface ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus remain on a surface?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412771, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412771, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412771, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966115e8-7085-11ea-905c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96611610-7085-11ea-93e9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96611642-7085-11ea-9d03-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the services ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the services?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4127848, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4127848, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4127848, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611674-7085-11ea-bdc6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661169c-7085-11ea-aecf-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966116cc-7085-11ea-b7bb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can we be contagious when we do n't show symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can we be contagious when we don't show symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4128032, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4128041, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4128041, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611728-7085-11ea-b68e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661175a-7085-11ea-94aa-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96611782-7085-11ea-bea6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is a coronavirus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is a coronavirus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412818, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412818, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412818, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966117be-7085-11ea-b823-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966117e6-7085-11ea-a06a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661180c-7085-11ea-9463-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Test", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Test", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412834, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412834, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412834, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611854-7085-11ea-894e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96611886-7085-11ea-a8d0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966118ae-7085-11ea-a0dc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Who is more at risk for covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Who is more at risk for covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4128482, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4128482, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4128482, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966118e8-7085-11ea-b10b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96611912-7085-11ea-992a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96611946-7085-11ea-93dc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is itchy throat sign of covid 19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is itchy throat sign of covid 19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412862, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412863, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412863, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611976-7085-11ea-a506-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966119a8-7085-11ea-b1cc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966119d0-7085-11ea-87a8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it true that you can get the virus again even after you 've recovered", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it true that you can get the virus again even after you've recovered", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412877, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412877, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412877, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611a02-7085-11ea-b26e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96611a34-7085-11ea-9acc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96611a5c-7085-11ea-954a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What to do if I have signs ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What to do if I have signs?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412891, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412891, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412891, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611a8c-7085-11ea-9112-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96611ac0-7085-11ea-9d2d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96611ae8-7085-11ea-b475-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are there going to be ministry exams in secondary 4 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are there going to be ministry exams in secondary 4?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412905, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412905, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412905, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611b24-7085-11ea-92e2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96611b62-7085-11ea-b5f2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96611b92-7085-11ea-be0d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do family containment ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do family containment?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4129221, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4129221, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4129221, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611bc6-7085-11ea-bc42-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96611bf6-7085-11ea-b41d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96611c1e-7085-11ea-a817-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will Covid19 go away like the 1918 influenza and SARS did", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will Covid19 go away like the 1918 influenza and SARS did", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4129379, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4129379, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4129379, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611c64-7085-11ea-ba43-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96611c98-7085-11ea-a22d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96611cc8-7085-11ea-9909-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "can I go outside", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "can I go outside", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412954, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412954, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412954, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611d22-7085-11ea-acc6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96611d54-7085-11ea-a0e4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96611d86-7085-11ea-8198-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long can the virus stay on a surface ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long can the virus stay on a surface?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4129732, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412974, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412974, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611dcc-7085-11ea-bba7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96611dfe-7085-11ea-9c06-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96611e26-7085-11ea-ac18-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are 5 ways to keep your immune system healthy", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are 5 ways to keep your immune system healthy", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.412988, "sourceDate": 1585352964.412988, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.412988, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611e62-7085-11ea-8e60-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96611e8a-7085-11ea-890e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96611eb4-7085-11ea-a0db-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many days can you be contagious without showing symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many days can you be contagious without showing symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.413002, "sourceDate": 1585352964.413002, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.413002, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96611eee-7085-11ea-9868-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661508a-7085-11ea-a670-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96615118-7085-11ea-94ec-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How is the corona virus being spread", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How is the corona virus being spread", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4142962, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4142962, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4142962, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661517a-7085-11ea-828b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966151ac-7085-11ea-bee7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966151de-7085-11ea-970e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long before we have a vaccine for corona ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long before we have a vaccine for corona?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414312, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414312, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414313, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661521a-7085-11ea-846d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661529c-7085-11ea-9272-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966152cc-7085-11ea-84ac-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Huhu", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Huhu", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414335, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414336, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414336, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96615300-7085-11ea-83d4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96615334-7085-11ea-b80e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661535a-7085-11ea-bfda-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have symptoms , should I isolate myself completely alone ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have symptoms, should I isolate myself completely alone?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41435, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41435, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41435, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96615398-7085-11ea-9a5d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966153dc-7085-11ea-9086-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96615418-7085-11ea-bb06-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the incubation time of covid-19 by age", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the incubation time of covid-19 by age", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414371, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414371, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414371, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661545e-7085-11ea-9900-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96615490-7085-11ea-a161-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966154c2-7085-11ea-a0a3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "grated penis", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "grated penis", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414386, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414386, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414386, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966154f4-7085-11ea-8502-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96615526-7085-11ea-aab4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661554c-7085-11ea-b67d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When will Canada be on quarantine ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When will Canada be on quarantine?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4144042, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4144042, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4144042, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966155b4-7085-11ea-b762-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966155e4-7085-11ea-b752-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661560c-7085-11ea-becf-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have a fever", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have a fever", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414419, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414419, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414419, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96615648-7085-11ea-a421-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96615670-7085-11ea-b0b8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96615698-7085-11ea-b805-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how is going", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how is going", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414433, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414433, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414433, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966156d4-7085-11ea-b1c0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966156fa-7085-11ea-98dd-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661572e-7085-11ea-a304-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do I need to wear a mask ? I heard it 's worse if you touch your face", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do I need to wear a mask? I heard it's worse if you touch your face", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414447, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414447, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414447, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96615762-7085-11ea-a85b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96615788-7085-11ea-8d1c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966157ba-7085-11ea-bea2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long are we contagious when we have COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long are we contagious when we have COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414461, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4144619, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4144619, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966157ec-7085-11ea-a15a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96615814-7085-11ea-9271-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96615846-7085-11ea-875a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus survive on a wet surface ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus survive on a wet surface?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414477, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414477, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414477, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661588c-7085-11ea-8132-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966158be-7085-11ea-aee4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966158e6-7085-11ea-8153-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If you start showing flu symptoms should you consult a doctor or stay home ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If you start showing flu symptoms should you consult a doctor or stay home?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414492, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414492, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414492, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96615918-7085-11ea-8e2a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661594a-7085-11ea-bfd9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96615974-7085-11ea-b747-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I visit my family ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I visit my family?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414509, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414509, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414509, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966159c2-7085-11ea-b3b6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96615a08-7085-11ea-a381-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96615a30-7085-11ea-b30f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus live in my body if I catch it", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus live in my body if I catch it", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414525, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414525, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414525, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96615a6c-7085-11ea-bc69-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96615a94-7085-11ea-9fe5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96615ac6-7085-11ea-a4e7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are vaccines being tested ? It seems it 's early", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are vaccines being tested? It seems it's early", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414539, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41454, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41454, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96615af8-7085-11ea-8315-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96615b28-7085-11ea-b109-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96615b52-7085-11ea-8772-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it safe to go outside for a walk ( social distancing from others ) ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it safe to go outside for a walk (social distancing from others)?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414554, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414554, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414554, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96615b86-7085-11ea-8ab6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96615bb6-7085-11ea-84e3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96615bfa-7085-11ea-ad92-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should we let a visitor into a house if we try to isolate ourselves ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should we let a visitor into a house if we try to isolate ourselves?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414572, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414572, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414572, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96615c38-7085-11ea-a0cd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96615c7e-7085-11ea-ae1f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96615ca6-7085-11ea-8bb6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I go get tested for COVID ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I go get tested for COVID?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414588, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414588, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414588, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96615ce2-7085-11ea-a562-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96615d0a-7085-11ea-937b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96615d3a-7085-11ea-8b42-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What can you do ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What can you do?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414602, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414602, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414603, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96615d6e-7085-11ea-91e2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96615d98-7085-11ea-8839-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96615ddc-7085-11ea-8243-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "am I at risk", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "am I at risk", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414618, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414619, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414619, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96615e0c-7085-11ea-9079-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96615e40-7085-11ea-b754-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96615e68-7085-11ea-824c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Who is at risk ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Who is at risk?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414635, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414635, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414635, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96615eae-7085-11ea-94e4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96615ee2-7085-11ea-a1fe-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96615f12-7085-11ea-b3ea-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the Symptom for covid19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the Symptom for covid19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4146502, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4146502, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4146502, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96615f4c-7085-11ea-832e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96615f80-7085-11ea-91de-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96615fb4-7085-11ea-bfb0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how can I prevent to get infected ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how can I prevent to get infected?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414666, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414666, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414666, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96615fe4-7085-11ea-8a9a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96616018-7085-11ea-a45b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661603e-7085-11ea-96fd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can I protect myself ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can I protect myself?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41468, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41468, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41468, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616070-7085-11ea-b1e3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966160a2-7085-11ea-a759-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966160ca-7085-11ea-9120-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does it last ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does it last?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4146938, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4146938, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4146938, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616106-7085-11ea-9419-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661612e-7085-11ea-954a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96616162-7085-11ea-8e79-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is covid", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is covid", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414709, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414709, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414709, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616192-7085-11ea-97f2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966161c6-7085-11ea-bde4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966161ec-7085-11ea-a81a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What 's the difference between COVID-19 and CoronaVirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What's the difference between COVID-19 and CoronaVirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4147232, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4147232, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4147232, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616228-7085-11ea-b257-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96616250-7085-11ea-9dc1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96616282-7085-11ea-84f4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where should I be tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where should I be tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41474, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41474, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41474, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966162c8-7085-11ea-90c3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966162fa-7085-11ea-aded-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96616322-7085-11ea-a5ca-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many cases in Quebec", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many cases in Quebec", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4147542, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4147542, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414755, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661635e-7085-11ea-ac82-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966163a4-7085-11ea-8571-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966163cc-7085-11ea-9710-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When will primary schools start ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When will primary schools start?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4147708, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4147708, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4147708, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616408-7085-11ea-b680-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96616430-7085-11ea-9b57-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96616462-7085-11ea-b7b6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "when will germany reach the peak ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "when will germany reach the peak?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414786, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414786, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414786, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616494-7085-11ea-8a8f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966164ee-7085-11ea-af60-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96616528-7085-11ea-83ac-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should we fear a second wave of contagion if we end the means of containment too quickly ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should we fear a second wave of contagion if we end the means of containment too quickly?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414809, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414809, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414809, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661657a-7085-11ea-8205-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966165ac-7085-11ea-bfbe-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966165de-7085-11ea-b8bc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the contagion period ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the contagion period?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414824, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414824, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414824, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616610-7085-11ea-adda-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96616642-7085-11ea-bd01-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96616668-7085-11ea-8c9d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do you need an appointment ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do you need an appointment?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414838, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414838, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414838, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661669c-7085-11ea-b01e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966166cc-7085-11ea-88d1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966166f6-7085-11ea-aaae-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How are you ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How are you?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4148538, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4148538, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4148538, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616746-7085-11ea-a068-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96616778-7085-11ea-a89a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661679e-7085-11ea-9ccb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My throat hurts what should I do ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My throat hurts what should I do?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414869, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414869, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414869, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966167d2-7085-11ea-991e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96616806-7085-11ea-a684-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661682c-7085-11ea-9f22-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the 10 best foods to boost your immune system", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the 10 best foods to boost your immune system", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414884, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414885, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414885, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616874-7085-11ea-bd9d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966168a4-7085-11ea-bc98-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96616a1e-7085-11ea-8a7f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If you recover from the virus , can you still be a carrier", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If you recover from the virus, can you still be a carrier", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414933, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414933, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414933, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616a5c-7085-11ea-ae54-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96616a98-7085-11ea-a784-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96616aca-7085-11ea-a108-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How Can I get answer for my questions ? ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How Can I get answer for my questions ??", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4149508, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4149508, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4149508, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616b10-7085-11ea-aedd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96616b38-7085-11ea-8467-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96616b68-7085-11ea-9b3d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it better to avoid taking a walk when there are a lot of people outside ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it better to avoid taking a walk when there are a lot of people outside?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414965, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414965, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414965, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616b9c-7085-11ea-944c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96616bc6-7085-11ea-b188-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96616bf6-7085-11ea-b11c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I breastfeed my baby if I have covid 19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I breastfeed my baby if I have covid 19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414979, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414979, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414979, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616c28-7085-11ea-85de-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96616c6e-7085-11ea-ae4e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96616c98-7085-11ea-a4c6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the meaning of COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the meaning of COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.414998, "sourceDate": 1585352964.414998, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.414998, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616ce6-7085-11ea-a23d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96616d18-7085-11ea-ae0f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96616d40-7085-11ea-9c0f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why should I avoid contact with other people ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why should I avoid contact with other people?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415013, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415013, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415013, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616d74-7085-11ea-8fa8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96616da4-7085-11ea-ade5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96616dcc-7085-11ea-a982-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "where did it start", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "where did it start", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415027, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415027, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415027, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616e08-7085-11ea-a56b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96616e30-7085-11ea-9a1d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96616e62-7085-11ea-aff6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does it takes to get first symptom of Covid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does it takes to get first symptom of Covid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415041, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415041, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4150422, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616e94-7085-11ea-8d79-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96616eba-7085-11ea-9ba0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96616ef8-7085-11ea-a9e2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is the Covid 19 deadly ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is the Covid 19 deadly?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415057, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415057, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415057, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616f34-7085-11ea-b4b3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96616f5c-7085-11ea-a84c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96616f8c-7085-11ea-86fe-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415072, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415072, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415072, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96616fca-7085-11ea-8888-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96617024-7085-11ea-be17-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617058-7085-11ea-b839-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how long could the covid last ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how long could the covid last?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415092, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415092, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415092, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96617088-7085-11ea-a378-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966170ba-7085-11ea-bf9d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966170e2-7085-11ea-8097-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to take care of infected people", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to take care of infected people", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4151092, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4151092, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4151092, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96617134-7085-11ea-9fc9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96617164-7085-11ea-8999-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617198-7085-11ea-9ca7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will I die if I have COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will I die if I have COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415124, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415124, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415124, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966171c8-7085-11ea-806a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966171fa-7085-11ea-857c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617222-7085-11ea-81f3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long will it take for a vaccine to be produced ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long will it take for a vaccine to be produced?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415138, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415138, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415138, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661725e-7085-11ea-af39-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96617286-7085-11ea-8496-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966172b8-7085-11ea-b83c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I use Sudafed ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I use Sudafed?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415152, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4151528, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4151528, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966172fe-7085-11ea-8831-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96617330-7085-11ea-a5f1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617358-7085-11ea-97e7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Who are the people most at risk ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Who are the people most at risk?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41517, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41517, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4151711, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661739e-7085-11ea-ae7f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966173d0-7085-11ea-930f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966173f8-7085-11ea-972f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can you catch covid 19 after having had it before", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can you catch covid 19 after having had it before", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415185, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415185, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415185, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96617428-7085-11ea-8cde-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661745c-7085-11ea-a9d8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617486-7085-11ea-bf44-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long will it take to develop a vaccine ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long will it take to develop a vaccine?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4152, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4152, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4152, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966174c0-7085-11ea-a535-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966174fa-7085-11ea-9c8f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617524-7085-11ea-8e18-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Medicen corona virus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Medicen corona virus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415217, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415217, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415217, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96617574-7085-11ea-948a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966175a6-7085-11ea-8d2f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966175cc-7085-11ea-9bfa-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do I have to wear a face mask to protect myself from coronaviruses ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do I have to wear a face mask to protect myself from coronaviruses?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415232, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415232, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415232, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661760a-7085-11ea-b626-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96617634-7085-11ea-8ddf-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617664-7085-11ea-95b7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can I protect myself from obtaining COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can I protect myself from obtaining COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4152472, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4152472, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4152472, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96617698-7085-11ea-a7b3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966176c8-7085-11ea-b11e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966176f0-7085-11ea-bb85-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many questions do you want before being launched", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many questions do you want before being launched", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415261, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415261, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415261, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96617722-7085-11ea-b456-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966177b8-7085-11ea-9d9e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966177e2-7085-11ea-88ea-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there any treatment for covid 19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there any treatment for covid 19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415285, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415285, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415285, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661781c-7085-11ea-9858-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96617858-7085-11ea-9f7a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617880-7085-11ea-92b0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have some symptoms , what should I do ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have some symptoms, what should I do?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415301, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415301, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415301, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966178ba-7085-11ea-bf2e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966178e4-7085-11ea-9014-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617918-7085-11ea-9622-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are Dialogue services ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are Dialogue services?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415318, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415318, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415318, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661795c-7085-11ea-8e9b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96617998-7085-11ea-a039-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966179de-7085-11ea-8fcb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Am I going to die .", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Am I going to die.", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415338, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415338, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415338, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96617a24-7085-11ea-a0c8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96617a58-7085-11ea-b9c0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617a88-7085-11ea-898b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of the Corina virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of the Corina virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415353, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415353, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415353, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96617aba-7085-11ea-b61a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96617aec-7085-11ea-b632-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617b14-7085-11ea-bdcc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "You do n't answer the question ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "You don't answer the question?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415367, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415367, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415367, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96617b46-7085-11ea-9c46-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96617b8c-7085-11ea-8cbb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617bbe-7085-11ea-9194-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "a have a fever", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "a have a fever", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415384, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415384, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415384, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96617bfa-7085-11ea-b8d9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96617c22-7085-11ea-add6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617c54-7085-11ea-95b1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus survive on clothes ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus survive on clothes?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415398, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415398, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4153988, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96617c86-7085-11ea-8f16-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96617cb8-7085-11ea-9121-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617ce2-7085-11ea-9bab-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are people infected and then cured immunized against the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are people infected and then cured immunized against the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415413, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415413, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415413, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96617d12-7085-11ea-b567-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96617d46-7085-11ea-a43d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617d6c-7085-11ea-ac78-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is total containment planned in Canada ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is total containment planned in Canada?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415427, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4154282, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4154282, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96617db4-7085-11ea-9d44-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96617dda-7085-11ea-9b67-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617e0c-7085-11ea-9a85-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are the symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are the symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415444, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415444, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415444, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96617e52-7085-11ea-832f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96617e86-7085-11ea-b0de-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617eac-7085-11ea-aff1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does my employer have to pay me during the isolation ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does my employer have to pay me during the isolation?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415461, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415461, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415461, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96617ef4-7085-11ea-ac05-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96617f38-7085-11ea-ab7e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617f62-7085-11ea-8e50-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have symptoms where should I call ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have symptoms where should I call?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415477, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415477, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415477, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96617f9c-7085-11ea-a6b8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96617fc6-7085-11ea-9a2c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96617ff6-7085-11ea-bcb8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is social distancing ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is social distancing?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415491, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415491, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415492, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96618028-7085-11ea-8ccb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661805a-7085-11ea-960a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96618082-7085-11ea-b08d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I made love with a stranger is what I am at risk", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I made love with a stranger is what I am at risk", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415506, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415506, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415506, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966180b4-7085-11ea-92ca-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966180e6-7085-11ea-b9be-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661810c-7085-11ea-aa2f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what the corona verus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what the corona verus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41552, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41552, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41552, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661814a-7085-11ea-a2ad-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96618174-7085-11ea-8faf-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966181a4-7085-11ea-a1dd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How is COVID spread ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How is COVID spread?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415534, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4155352, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4155352, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966181d8-7085-11ea-b27c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966181fe-7085-11ea-85d1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96618230-7085-11ea-88e6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can my pet infect me with the virus that causes COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can my pet infect me with the virus that causes COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415552, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415552, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415552, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661828a-7085-11ea-a5ea-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966182ba-7085-11ea-ab91-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966182e4-7085-11ea-8017-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I go get tested if I have certain symptoms of seasonal flu ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I go get tested if I have certain symptoms of seasonal flu?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41557, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41557, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41557, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96618334-7085-11ea-a768-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96618370-7085-11ea-b1b9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966183ac-7085-11ea-a924-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can we be infected more than once with COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can we be infected more than once with COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4155872, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4155872, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4155881, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966183e8-7085-11ea-8ca7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661841a-7085-11ea-ba9b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96618442-7085-11ea-af62-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long will it take to get a vaccine ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long will it take to get a vaccine?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415602, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415602, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415602, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96618474-7085-11ea-888f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966184a6-7085-11ea-b5ef-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966184cc-7085-11ea-adc3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I accept packages from China", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I accept packages from China", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415616, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415616, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415616, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661850a-7085-11ea-ac56-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96618534-7085-11ea-aaef-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96618564-7085-11ea-8a67-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to distinguish the flu virus from Covid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to distinguish the flu virus from Covid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41563, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41563, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41563, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96618598-7085-11ea-8bea-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966185be-7085-11ea-a7bb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966185f0-7085-11ea-9ddc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How deadly is the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How deadly is the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415644, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415644, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415645, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96618622-7085-11ea-8de5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661864a-7085-11ea-a7ec-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661867a-7085-11ea-a18c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is having a dry throat a symptom ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is having a dry throat a symptom?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415658, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415659, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415659, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966186ae-7085-11ea-86fa-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966186d8-7085-11ea-9973-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96618712-7085-11ea-99ec-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there a cure available ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there a cure available?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4156768, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4156768, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4156768, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96618762-7085-11ea-9846-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96618794-7085-11ea-b977-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966187c6-7085-11ea-82f0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My throat seems to burn a little . Should i be worried ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My throat seems to burn a little. Should i be worried?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415692, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415692, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415692, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966187f8-7085-11ea-a095-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96618834-7085-11ea-855e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96618870-7085-11ea-bde4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long will it be necessary to stay at home ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long will it be necessary to stay at home?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415709, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415709, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415709, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966188a2-7085-11ea-9f00-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966188f4-7085-11ea-ba2d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661891a-7085-11ea-bda2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have a cold , can it be covid 19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have a cold, can it be covid 19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4157262, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4157262, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4157262, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661894c-7085-11ea-9034-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661897e-7085-11ea-9b6f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966189b0-7085-11ea-a34d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I be doing telework ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I be doing telework?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41574, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41574, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41574, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966189e2-7085-11ea-b5c9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96618a1e-7085-11ea-a709-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96618a50-7085-11ea-884d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I cough but I do n't have a fever . Do I have covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I cough but I don't have a fever. Do I have covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415757, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415757, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415757, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96618a82-7085-11ea-88ec-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96618ab4-7085-11ea-bff8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96618adc-7085-11ea-9e3f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of Covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of Covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4157708, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4157708, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4157708, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96618b18-7085-11ea-89f3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96618b40-7085-11ea-af78-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96618b68-7085-11ea-852e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415788, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415788, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415788, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96618bc2-7085-11ea-9531-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96618bf4-7085-11ea-97a4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96618c1c-7085-11ea-a8ef-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What type of drugs may I take if I have covid19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What type of drugs may I take if I have covid19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415803, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415803, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415803, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96618c58-7085-11ea-a24c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96618c9e-7085-11ea-9403-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96618cda-7085-11ea-b430-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where to get tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where to get tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415824, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415824, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415824, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96618d1e-7085-11ea-af5e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96618d52-7085-11ea-9813-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96618d7a-7085-11ea-931e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why do we have to stay in confinement ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why do we have to stay in confinement?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415838, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415838, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415838, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96618dac-7085-11ea-be39-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96618dde-7085-11ea-bde1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96618e06-7085-11ea-91ba-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have gastroenteritis if I go to the clinic , I 'm afraid of getting the virus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have gastroenteritis if I go to the clinic, I'm afraid of getting the virus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415852, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415852, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415852, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96618e42-7085-11ea-b1b4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96618e68-7085-11ea-9c91-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96618e9c-7085-11ea-9f5e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the origin of the pandemic ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the origin of the pandemic?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4158661, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4158661, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4158661, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96618ecc-7085-11ea-a21e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96618ef6-7085-11ea-9879-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96618f28-7085-11ea-ac8b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will the Olympic stadium be used to treat COVID19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will the Olympic stadium be used to treat COVID19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41588, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415881, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415881, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96618f5a-7085-11ea-81ba-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96618f8c-7085-11ea-aa98-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96618fb4-7085-11ea-8fae-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are the risks for someone aged 65 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are the risks for someone aged 65?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4158971, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4158971, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4158971, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96618ffa-7085-11ea-9216-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661902c-7085-11ea-9dd0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661905e-7085-11ea-9be8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are research fundings going to be cut as a result of the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are research fundings going to be cut as a result of the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415911, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415912, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415912, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96619090-7085-11ea-8820-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966190c2-7085-11ea-b282-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966190e8-7085-11ea-8424-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is sore throat a symptom of covid ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is sore throat a symptom of covid?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4159281, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4159281, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4159281, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661913a-7085-11ea-bc6a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661916c-7085-11ea-ac2c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661919e-7085-11ea-8396-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Test2", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Test2", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4159439, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4159439, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4159439, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966191d0-7085-11ea-9c79-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96619202-7085-11ea-b7d6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96619228-7085-11ea-baeb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "South korea", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "South korea", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415958, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415958, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415958, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661925c-7085-11ea-8cfb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661928c-7085-11ea-9e35-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966192b6-7085-11ea-9f1a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I get infected from food or grocery delivery ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I get infected from food or grocery delivery?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415972, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415972, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415972, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966192f4-7085-11ea-8c1d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661931a-7085-11ea-a892-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661934c-7085-11ea-b2a7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I fully recover from COVID-19 would I still be considered a carrier and transmit the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I fully recover from COVID-19 would I still be considered a carrier and transmit the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.415987, "sourceDate": 1585352964.415987, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.415987, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661937e-7085-11ea-a22f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966193b0-7085-11ea-b83d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966193d8-7085-11ea-9aee-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the risk for an asthmatic ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the risk for an asthmatic?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416003, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416003, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416003, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96619428-7085-11ea-8c11-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661945a-7085-11ea-9878-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96619482-7085-11ea-8947-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why is Covid-19 so contagious ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why is Covid-19 so contagious?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416018, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416018, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416018, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966194b4-7085-11ea-b03a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966194e6-7085-11ea-9c31-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661950c-7085-11ea-a4b1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why is Trudeau asleep ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why is Trudeau asleep?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4160352, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4160352, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4160352, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96619574-7085-11ea-8db4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966195ae-7085-11ea-90cb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966195e8-7085-11ea-95fb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are 8 best fruits to boost your immune system", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are 8 best fruits to boost your immune system", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416054, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416054, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416055, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96619626-7085-11ea-9151-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661964c-7085-11ea-84d2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96619680-7085-11ea-982f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I go for a run ? Does running / exercise compromise my immune system ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I go for a run? Does running / exercise compromise my immune system?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416069, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416069, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416069, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966196b4-7085-11ea-96c0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966196e4-7085-11ea-83c6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661970c-7085-11ea-b141-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When will covid end ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When will covid end?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4160829, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4160829, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4160829, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96619748-7085-11ea-b8fa-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96619770-7085-11ea-874b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966197a2-7085-11ea-b161-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I live in a condo building , can COVID circulate in the air through the units ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I live in a condo building, can COVID circulate in the air through the units?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416098, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416098, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416098, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966197d4-7085-11ea-9bec-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96619806-7085-11ea-98e0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661982e-7085-11ea-a42a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I get the virus by talking on the phone ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I get the virus by talking on the phone?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4161139, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4161139, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4161139, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661987e-7085-11ea-824b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966198c6-7085-11ea-b792-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966198ec-7085-11ea-8e3c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have a temperature and cough , what should I do ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have a temperature and cough, what should I do?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416131, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416131, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4161322, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96619928-7085-11ea-8eb9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661995a-7085-11ea-a84f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661999e-7085-11ea-b0c8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is coronavirus a new virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is coronavirus a new virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416149, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416149, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416149, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966199dc-7085-11ea-b2e9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96619a18-7085-11ea-a43a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96619a4a-7085-11ea-9857-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is the virus airborne", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is the virus airborne", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4161658, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4161658, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4161658, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96619a7a-7085-11ea-825c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96619aae-7085-11ea-bdf0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96619ad8-7085-11ea-bd75-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there more than one strain of COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there more than one strain of COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41618, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41618, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41618, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96619b12-7085-11ea-8556-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96619b3a-7085-11ea-9c1a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96619b6c-7085-11ea-b645-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long am I infectious for", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long am I infectious for", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416194, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416194, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416194, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96619b9e-7085-11ea-a8b2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96619bc6-7085-11ea-9c48-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96619bf8-7085-11ea-8cac-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I do n't have a fever , can I still have coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I don't have a fever, can I still have coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4162078, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416209, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416209, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96619c28-7085-11ea-ab9b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96619c5c-7085-11ea-a2cb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96619c86-7085-11ea-a5c9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is the appointment made with you ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is the appointment made with you?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416224, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416225, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416225, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96619cca-7085-11ea-83ee-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96619cfa-7085-11ea-921c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96619d24-7085-11ea-aa2f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What if I cough ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What if I cough?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416239, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416239, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416239, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96619d62-7085-11ea-a965-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96619d9c-7085-11ea-88b6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96619dcc-7085-11ea-9696-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will there be walk - in screening tests in Lanaudi\u00e8re ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will there be walk-in screening tests in Lanaudi\u00e8re?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4162571, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4162571, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4162571, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96619e0a-7085-11ea-bdf1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96619e3a-7085-11ea-9008-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96619e64-7085-11ea-9b65-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What should I do if I have symptoms of COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What should I do if I have symptoms of COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4162712, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4162712, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4162712, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96619e9e-7085-11ea-a485-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96619ec8-7085-11ea-bde2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96619efa-7085-11ea-b8a3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many infected person in south korea ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many infected person in south korea?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416288, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416288, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416288, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96619f40-7085-11ea-a815-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96619f74-7085-11ea-a5a1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96619f9a-7085-11ea-820d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is the phlegm color suggestive of coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is the phlegm color suggestive of coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416302, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416302, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416302, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96619fd8-7085-11ea-a63d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96619ffe-7085-11ea-ab3a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661a030-7085-11ea-8f96-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long will I be sick if I get the virus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long will I be sick if I get the virus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4163158, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416317, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416317, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661a062-7085-11ea-b818-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661a094-7085-11ea-acf2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661a0ba-7085-11ea-9c65-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I cough , is it covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I cough, is it covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416333, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416333, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416333, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661a102-7085-11ea-87c8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661a134-7085-11ea-832c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661a166-7085-11ea-ad85-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I go out for a walk if I have a fever ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I go out for a walk if I have a fever?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4163468, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4163468, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416348, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661a198-7085-11ea-bf5b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661a1c0-7085-11ea-9261-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661a1f4-7085-11ea-af04-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the treatments of COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the treatments of COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416362, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416362, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416362, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661a224-7085-11ea-99c0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661a258-7085-11ea-8fea-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661a29c-7085-11ea-b362-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Am I safe if I stay at home", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Am I safe if I stay at home", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416379, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416379, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416379, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661a2d8-7085-11ea-b15d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661a300-7085-11ea-a595-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661a334-7085-11ea-80e3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does recovery take on average ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does recovery take on average?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416394, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416394, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416394, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661a364-7085-11ea-96e2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661a398-7085-11ea-b501-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661a3be-7085-11ea-885a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does contamination by the virus last ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does contamination by the virus last?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416408, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416408, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416408, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661a3fa-7085-11ea-a2d1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661a422-7085-11ea-8dce-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661a454-7085-11ea-b0a1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long will it take before we can stop social distancing ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long will it take before we can stop social distancing?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416422, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416422, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416422, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661a486-7085-11ea-b8d0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661a4ae-7085-11ea-ac36-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661a4e2-7085-11ea-a17a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it airborne", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it airborne", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41644, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4164412, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4164412, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661a53a-7085-11ea-83c9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661a576-7085-11ea-98b7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661a59e-7085-11ea-b8ae-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "We hear that the spread will decrease in the summer but that it will resume and that there will be a second peak in the fall . What about", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "We hear that the spread will decrease in the summer but that it will resume and that there will be a second peak in the fall. What about", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416456, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416456, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416456, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661a5da-7085-11ea-9846-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661a602-7085-11ea-8533-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661a634-7085-11ea-854a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the% of the population affected by each country in the world ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the% of the population affected by each country in the world?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416471, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416471, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416471, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661a666-7085-11ea-9ac0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661a698-7085-11ea-8e8d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661a6c0-7085-11ea-b8aa-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why did n't you answer my first question ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why didn't you answer my first question?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416485, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416485, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416485, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661a6f4-7085-11ea-b67a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661a738-7085-11ea-8ed1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661a768-7085-11ea-848f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why is called COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why is called COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416502, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416502, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416502, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661a79c-7085-11ea-acaa-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661a7cc-7085-11ea-a7b9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661a7f6-7085-11ea-94e0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to minimize the risk of spread ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to minimize the risk of spread?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416516, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416516, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416516, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661a834-7085-11ea-9b8b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661a86e-7085-11ea-9da9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661a89e-7085-11ea-b397-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many people died in NYC", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many people died in NYC", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416533, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416533, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416533, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661a8dc-7085-11ea-be63-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661a906-7085-11ea-b887-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661a92c-7085-11ea-adda-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What if I have cough ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What if I have cough?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4165492, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4165492, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41655, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661a97a-7085-11ea-8d4c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661a9ae-7085-11ea-90b6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661a9f4-7085-11ea-87c1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Hello", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Hello", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416567, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416567, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416568, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661aa30-7085-11ea-9a65-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661aa62-7085-11ea-8478-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661aa8a-7085-11ea-846a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how old are you ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how old are you?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4165819, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4165819, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4165819, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661aaba-7085-11ea-93ca-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661ab02-7085-11ea-aaef-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661ab28-7085-11ea-8cf2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have a sore throat , do I have the Covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have a sore throat, do I have the Covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416598, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416598, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416598, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661ab66-7085-11ea-8c09-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661ab8c-7085-11ea-86e7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661abb6-7085-11ea-aeee-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it true that warm kills Coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it true that warm kills Coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4166121, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4166121, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416613, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661abf4-7085-11ea-a544-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661ac24-7085-11ea-8299-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661ac4c-7085-11ea-826f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have just returned from an uninfected country , should I be in quarantine ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have just returned from an uninfected country, should I be in quarantine?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416627, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416627, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416627, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661ac7e-7085-11ea-89bf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661acb0-7085-11ea-aebd-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661acd8-7085-11ea-91c9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms associated with covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms associated with covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416641, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416641, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416641, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661ad14-7085-11ea-a118-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661ad50-7085-11ea-9599-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661ad82-7085-11ea-9724-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long will containment last ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long will containment last?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4166589, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4166589, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4166589, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661adbe-7085-11ea-9a49-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661adf0-7085-11ea-a588-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661ae18-7085-11ea-83e7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I go outside and it sells very hard , is it that the virus can go in the wind or it goes deeper my clothes or my skin ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I go outside and it sells very hard, is it that the virus can go in the wind or it goes deeper my clothes or my skin?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416675, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416675, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416675, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661ae68-7085-11ea-b997-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661ae90-7085-11ea-9b45-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661aec2-7085-11ea-8e6d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Duration of symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Duration of symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4166899, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4166899, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4166899, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661aef4-7085-11ea-bf89-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661af26-7085-11ea-bd98-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661af4c-7085-11ea-93c9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does it give diarrhea ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does it give diarrhea?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416704, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416704, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416704, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661af80-7085-11ea-948b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661afb4-7085-11ea-93a3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661afda-7085-11ea-92ae-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how to make an appointment", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how to make an appointment", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416718, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416718, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416718, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661b018-7085-11ea-bf4d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661b03e-7085-11ea-8c13-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661b066-7085-11ea-afc1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do you have IT specialists on COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do you have IT specialists on COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4167318, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4167318, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4167318, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661b0a2-7085-11ea-b8ed-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661b0ca-7085-11ea-803b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661b0fa-7085-11ea-b132-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why are we talking about a social distance of 2 meters", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why are we talking about a social distance of 2 meters", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416747, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416747, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416747, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661b138-7085-11ea-b0e3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661b162-7085-11ea-b829-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661b19c-7085-11ea-a8c7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are there dangers for pregnant women ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are there dangers for pregnant women?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416764, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416764, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416764, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661b1d8-7085-11ea-9966-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661b214-7085-11ea-ba0f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661b250-7085-11ea-8569-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are we going to have trouble buying milk ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are we going to have trouble buying milk?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416783, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416783, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416783, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661b298-7085-11ea-b704-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661b2c8-7085-11ea-9a38-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661b2fa-7085-11ea-aba6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the difference between a pandemic and an epidemic ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the difference between a pandemic and an epidemic?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416797, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416797, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4167979, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661b32c-7085-11ea-8dd1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661b35e-7085-11ea-b36d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661b386-7085-11ea-87a2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where can I find most up to date numbers on cases and deaths ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where can I find most up to date numbers on cases and deaths?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416812, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416812, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416812, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661b3b8-7085-11ea-b33f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661b3e8-7085-11ea-bee8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661b412-7085-11ea-a0a1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what the name of the virus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what the name of the virus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416826, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416826, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416826, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661b446-7085-11ea-9dcb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661b476-7085-11ea-a975-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661b49e-7085-11ea-968b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I am 43 . What 's the chance of my survival if I get covid .", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I am 43. What's the chance of my survival if I get covid.", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4168398, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4168398, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4168398, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661b4da-7085-11ea-8fe3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661b502-7085-11ea-84e4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661b534-7085-11ea-ba29-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do you have muscle pain that prevents you from moving ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do you have muscle pain that prevents you from moving?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416854, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416854, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416855, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661b566-7085-11ea-b3d9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661b5a2-7085-11ea-bd77-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661b5d4-7085-11ea-87ac-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it true that gastrointestinal problems are also a symptom to be considered ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it true that gastrointestinal problems are also a symptom to be considered?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4168708, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4168708, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4168708, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661b606-7085-11ea-9779-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661b658-7085-11ea-8a71-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661b688-7085-11ea-933e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there a toll - free number for people who live alone to ask for help ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there a toll-free number for people who live alone to ask for help?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4168901, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4168909, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4168909, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661b6cc-7085-11ea-a6d8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661b700-7085-11ea-a4e9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661b734-7085-11ea-8f17-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Number of cases in Quebec ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Number of cases in Quebec?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416905, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416905, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4169059, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661b778-7085-11ea-bb60-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661b79e-7085-11ea-a002-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661b7d2-7085-11ea-a583-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "covid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "covid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416922, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416922, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416922, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661b806-7085-11ea-8380-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661b836-7085-11ea-85e7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661b85e-7085-11ea-971f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is Covid-19 more contagious than influenza ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is Covid-19 more contagious than influenza?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416936, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416936, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416936, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661b89a-7085-11ea-8af6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661b8c2-7085-11ea-9feb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661b8f4-7085-11ea-8515-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How does it take to recover from the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How does it take to recover from the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41695, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41695, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41695, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661b926-7085-11ea-a2e6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661b94c-7085-11ea-aeea-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661b980-7085-11ea-a07f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how long the covid can stay on a surface", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how long the covid can stay on a surface", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.416965, "sourceDate": 1585352964.416965, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.416965, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661b9b4-7085-11ea-bb97-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661b9e4-7085-11ea-9200-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661ba0c-7085-11ea-b763-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "should you avoid taking ibuprofen ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "should you avoid taking ibuprofen?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4169788, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4169788, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4169788, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661ba3e-7085-11ea-ae46-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661ba86-7085-11ea-b1e2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661bac0-7085-11ea-abdf-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Hello , what happens after corona ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Hello, what happens after corona?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4170098, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4170098, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4170098, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661bb7e-7085-11ea-b6db-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661bbb0-7085-11ea-a197-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661bbe2-7085-11ea-adda-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how to interact with people", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how to interact with people", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417025, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417025, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417025, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661bc14-7085-11ea-8965-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661bc50-7085-11ea-9ce9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661bc82-7085-11ea-b263-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My neighbor is coming back from a trip , what should I do ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My neighbor is coming back from a trip, what should I do?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417042, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417042, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417042, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661bcb4-7085-11ea-a1a9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661bce6-7085-11ea-87fa-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661bd0c-7085-11ea-bfb8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have a cold as I do to distinguish it from Cobid19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have a cold as I do to distinguish it from Cobid19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417056, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417056, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417056, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661bd40-7085-11ea-88e5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661bd74-7085-11ea-ab36-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661bd9a-7085-11ea-9587-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I ca n't leave my house , how can I get my food delivered ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I can't leave my house, how can I get my food delivered?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4170702, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4170702, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4170702, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661bdd8-7085-11ea-8383-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661bdfe-7085-11ea-ac3c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661be30-7085-11ea-808a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are we immune to Covid-19 if we have already caught it ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are we immune to Covid-19 if we have already caught it?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417085, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417085, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417085, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661be62-7085-11ea-8832-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661be94-7085-11ea-869d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661beda-7085-11ea-8ba7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many cases in India", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many cases in India", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417102, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417102, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417102, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661bf18-7085-11ea-97eb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661bf48-7085-11ea-a18c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661bf70-7085-11ea-afe2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have a court hearing date with people over 70 , will she have location ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have a court hearing date with people over 70, will she have location?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417119, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417119, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417119, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661bfb6-7085-11ea-9ea8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661bfe8-7085-11ea-abae-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661c01a-7085-11ea-807e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I wear mask", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I wear mask", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417134, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417134, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417134, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661c04c-7085-11ea-bd15-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661c07e-7085-11ea-9347-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661c0a6-7085-11ea-804e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus stay on our hair ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus stay on our hair?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4171479, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4171479, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4171479, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661c0e2-7085-11ea-be52-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661c10a-7085-11ea-8064-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661c13a-7085-11ea-b805-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What 's the current count in India", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What's the current count in India", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417162, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417162, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417163, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661c16e-7085-11ea-8c1d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661c198-7085-11ea-b64a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661c1c8-7085-11ea-aae6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does the virus really survive for several hours on the asphalt ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does the virus really survive for several hours on the asphalt?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417176, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417176, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417176, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661c1fa-7085-11ea-bb1c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661c222-7085-11ea-8fce-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661c254-7085-11ea-a236-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417191, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417191, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417191, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661c286-7085-11ea-a5f5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661c2b8-7085-11ea-a0c1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661c2f4-7085-11ea-98bf-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is the Asymptomatic Carrier a temporary status ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is the Asymptomatic Carrier a temporary status?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417208, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417208, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417208, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661c33a-7085-11ea-9dcc-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661c362-7085-11ea-9487-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661c394-7085-11ea-9483-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "At what temperature should we be worried about fever ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "At what temperature should we be worried about fever?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417224, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417224, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417224, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661c3d0-7085-11ea-a538-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661c402-7085-11ea-9ea3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661c434-7085-11ea-b375-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to treat me ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to treat me?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417239, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417239, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417239, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661c466-7085-11ea-81b7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661c4b6-7085-11ea-9ab2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661c4e8-7085-11ea-af08-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the first symptoms to appear ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the first symptoms to appear?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417257, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417257, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417257, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661c51a-7085-11ea-8971-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661c54c-7085-11ea-9fa1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661c574-7085-11ea-8e08-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is corona", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is corona", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4172711, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4172711, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4172711, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661c5a6-7085-11ea-9cc8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661c5d8-7085-11ea-8d9f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661c600-7085-11ea-bf8a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it safe to take medicines like mezavant or salofak", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it safe to take medicines like mezavant or salofak", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4172852, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4172852, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4172852, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661c634-7085-11ea-a915-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661c664-7085-11ea-ae6c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661c68c-7085-11ea-bda2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Who should I call to get help ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Who should I call to get help?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417299, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417299, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417299, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661c6be-7085-11ea-834d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661c6f0-7085-11ea-91e0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661c722-7085-11ea-a23b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What can I do to help ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What can I do to help?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417313, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417314, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417314, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661c754-7085-11ea-a0b5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661c79a-7085-11ea-96f8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661c7cc-7085-11ea-85ac-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how can I report a bar that remains open despite the ban ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how can I report a bar that remains open despite the ban?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417333, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417333, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417333, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661c81c-7085-11ea-97c9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661c846-7085-11ea-ba0f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661c876-7085-11ea-81cd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can my cat catch the Covid ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can my cat catch the Covid?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4173481, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4173481, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4173481, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661c8a8-7085-11ea-8e64-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661c8da-7085-11ea-9e10-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661c902-7085-11ea-bbab-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to deal with disinfection of day to day use objects ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to deal with disinfection of day to day use objects?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417362, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417362, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417362, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661c934-7085-11ea-8a3b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661c966-7085-11ea-a734-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661c98c-7085-11ea-aef7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the best way to curate information about COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the best way to curate information about COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417376, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417376, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417376, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661c9ca-7085-11ea-b4f6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661c9f4-7085-11ea-9b5b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661ca1a-7085-11ea-9089-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "PERU", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "PERU", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41739, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41739, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41739, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661ca58-7085-11ea-a453-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661ca7e-7085-11ea-9679-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661cab0-7085-11ea-9fda-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is the age range of the deceased ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is the age range of the deceased?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417404, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417405, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417405, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661cae2-7085-11ea-9cdb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661cb0a-7085-11ea-ba41-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661cb3a-7085-11ea-a6ea-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have French friends , should I avoid going to them ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have French friends, should I avoid going to them?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417418, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417419, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417419, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661cb6e-7085-11ea-8e73-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661cb9e-7085-11ea-a704-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661cbdc-7085-11ea-a953-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is covid very dangerous", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is covid very dangerous", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417438, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417438, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417438, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661cc2c-7085-11ea-838c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661cc5e-7085-11ea-84ac-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661cc90-7085-11ea-932d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "O que \u00e9 o covid19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "O que \u00e9 o covid19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417453, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417453, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417453, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661ccc2-7085-11ea-9f83-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661cd08-7085-11ea-933f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661cd30-7085-11ea-9f8a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I love you", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I love you", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417469, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417469, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417469, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661cd6c-7085-11ea-9731-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661cd94-7085-11ea-be1c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661cdd0-7085-11ea-8437-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how much fever should i tolerate before going to the doctor ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how much fever should i tolerate before going to the doctor?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417485, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417485, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417485, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661ce0c-7085-11ea-8f57-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661ce34-7085-11ea-8b0e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661ce66-7085-11ea-87d8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If someone survived COVID-19 ? Is he completely virus - free ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If someone survived COVID-19? Is he completely virus-free?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4175, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4175, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4175, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661ce98-7085-11ea-818b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661ceca-7085-11ea-a9f9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661cef4-7085-11ea-969d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the real symptoms of covid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the real symptoms of covid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417514, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417514, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417514, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661cf24-7085-11ea-bb26-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661cf58-7085-11ea-8ade-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661cf7e-7085-11ea-b49f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is a coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is a coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4175282, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4175282, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4175282, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661cfb0-7085-11ea-b8d6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661cff6-7085-11ea-9137-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661d028-7085-11ea-b2f8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Mortality rate", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Mortality rate", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417547, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417547, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417547, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661d078-7085-11ea-9e02-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661d09e-7085-11ea-8277-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661d0d2-7085-11ea-9bf2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "At what temperature does the virus survive ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "At what temperature does the virus survive?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417562, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417562, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417562, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661d106-7085-11ea-8e54-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661d136-7085-11ea-82e8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661d15e-7085-11ea-9000-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will the pandemic affect university research ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will the pandemic affect university research?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4175758, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4175758, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4175758, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661d190-7085-11ea-9d5b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661d1c2-7085-11ea-9d2f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661d1e8-7085-11ea-b1ea-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I do n't feel good", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I don't feel good", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41759, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41759, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41759, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661d226-7085-11ea-a838-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661d24c-7085-11ea-9e26-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661d276-7085-11ea-94d3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Have you had any contact with someone who has returned from abroad ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Have you had any contact with someone who has returned from abroad?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4176042, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4176042, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4176042, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661d2b4-7085-11ea-a295-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661d2ee-7085-11ea-8be6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661d31e-7085-11ea-b66a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How contagious is the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How contagious is the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417621, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417621, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417621, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661d352-7085-11ea-9a6e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661d386-7085-11ea-bd0e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661d3ac-7085-11ea-ac66-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the instructions to follow ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the instructions to follow?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417635, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417635, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417635, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661d3de-7085-11ea-87ca-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661d424-7085-11ea-9722-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661d458-7085-11ea-8876-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Duration of the pandemic", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Duration of the pandemic", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417653, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417653, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417653, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661d492-7085-11ea-ad5e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661d4c6-7085-11ea-9d47-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661d4ec-7085-11ea-9129-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should we wash the fruit and vegetable packaging brought back from the grocery store before storing them in our cupboards ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should we wash the fruit and vegetable packaging brought back from the grocery store before storing them in our cupboards?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417668, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417669, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417669, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661d534-7085-11ea-910c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661d564-7085-11ea-b198-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661d58c-7085-11ea-94f6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "As I am diabetic will I die ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "As I am diabetic will I die?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417686, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417686, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417686, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661d5e6-7085-11ea-be29-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661d60c-7085-11ea-9a9a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661d640-7085-11ea-928d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Given that the mild symptoms for COVID-19 may resemble the common cold , at what point in the expression of symptoms should you attempt to get tested for the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Given that the mild symptoms for COVID-19 may resemble the common cold, at what point in the expression of symptoms should you attempt to get tested for the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4177, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4177, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4177, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661d674-7085-11ea-82e1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661d6a4-7085-11ea-a8a0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661d6cc-7085-11ea-9696-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where to call for help getting my products delivered ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where to call for help getting my products delivered?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417717, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417717, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417717, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661d712-7085-11ea-8a96-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661d746-7085-11ea-9420-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661d7ee-7085-11ea-93df-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417752, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417752, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417752, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661d87a-7085-11ea-b1ee-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661d8d4-7085-11ea-acc9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661d924-7085-11ea-b1b3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I isolate myself voluntarily and be paid ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I isolate myself voluntarily and be paid?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417779, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417779, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417779, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661d988-7085-11ea-be06-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661d9d8-7085-11ea-96e4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661da28-7085-11ea-89ee-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does temperature has any effect on the virus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does temperature has any effect on the virus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4178061, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4178061, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4178061, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661da8c-7085-11ea-84ff-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661dabe-7085-11ea-822a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661daf0-7085-11ea-bae0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of covid ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of covid?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41782, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41782, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417821, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661db40-7085-11ea-9380-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661db74-7085-11ea-ac35-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661dba4-7085-11ea-af09-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many asymptomatic people are there likely to be ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many asymptomatic people are there likely to be?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417839, "sourceDate": 1585352964.417839, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.417839, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661dbd8-7085-11ea-ad93-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661dc08-7085-11ea-91ba-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661dc30-7085-11ea-9cf6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many cases are there currently in Quebec ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many cases are there currently in Quebec?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4178529, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4178529, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4178529, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661dc62-7085-11ea-b8ea-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661dc94-7085-11ea-91f6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661dcba-7085-11ea-baf9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can we get tested after having symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can we get tested after having symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41787, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41787, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41787, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661dd18-7085-11ea-9e56-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661dd3e-7085-11ea-8ca7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661dd86-7085-11ea-90c8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I be prescribed hydroxychloroquine with azithromycin if I have it ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I be prescribed hydroxychloroquine with azithromycin if I have it?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.417889, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41789, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41789, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661ddd4-7085-11ea-807c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661de10-7085-11ea-a68f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661de42-7085-11ea-a777-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "For how long COVID19 can stay alive on different surfaces ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "For how long COVID19 can stay alive on different surfaces?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4179058, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4179058, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4179058, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661de74-7085-11ea-a4e9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661dea6-7085-11ea-8092-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661decc-7085-11ea-8d1d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Sdfhhhh", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Sdfhhhh", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41792, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41792, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41792, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661df0a-7085-11ea-aa8c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661df34-7085-11ea-a830-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661df64-7085-11ea-a0c9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "We have a family sugar shack . Can we keep going ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "We have a family sugar shack. Can we keep going?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4179342, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4179351, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4179351, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661df98-7085-11ea-94f1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661dfdc-7085-11ea-b7c6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661e006-7085-11ea-9d2d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where should I go ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where should I go?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4179509, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4179509, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4179509, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661e040-7085-11ea-87d9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661e068-7085-11ea-a405-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661e09a-7085-11ea-9838-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What if i got fever", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What if i got fever", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4179652, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4179652, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4179661, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661e0cc-7085-11ea-9034-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661e0fe-7085-11ea-a2b7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661e126-7085-11ea-be5c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are the options to disinfect hand or surfaces other than soap and alcohol", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are the options to disinfect hand or surfaces other than soap and alcohol", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4179819, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4179819, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4179819, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661e176-7085-11ea-91c2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661e1a8-7085-11ea-93fb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661e1d0-7085-11ea-88e6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Covid", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Covid", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418015, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418015, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418015, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661e2ca-7085-11ea-a02e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661e392-7085-11ea-be47-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661e3e2-7085-11ea-a591-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What to do if we suspect a patient has COVID-19 Should we notify the local or national health department", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What to do if we suspect a patient has COVID-19 Should we notify the local or national health department", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4180522, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4180522, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4180522, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661e434-7085-11ea-b5f6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661e464-7085-11ea-8780-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661e498-7085-11ea-aa48-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long should I stay in quarantine ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long should I stay in quarantine?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418071, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418071, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418071, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661e4e6-7085-11ea-9cb2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661e536-7085-11ea-93ef-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661e568-7085-11ea-a873-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I 'm feeling dizzy with fever do I have corona ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I'm feeling dizzy with fever do I have corona?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418089, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418089, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418089, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661e59a-7085-11ea-baa2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661e5cc-7085-11ea-b63c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661e5fe-7085-11ea-80c5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How is it transmitted ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How is it transmitted?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4181042, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4181042, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4181042, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661e63a-7085-11ea-9071-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661e662-7085-11ea-95c5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661e694-7085-11ea-95f9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there a vaccine against the new coronavirus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there a vaccine against the new coronavirus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418118, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418119, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418119, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661e6c6-7085-11ea-8bcf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661e6f8-7085-11ea-aa14-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661e71e-7085-11ea-ac39-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How 's the condition in Singapore ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How's the condition in Singapore?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418133, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418133, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418133, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661e752-7085-11ea-abfd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661e78c-7085-11ea-a781-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661e7b6-7085-11ea-8c53-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I 'm sick , I 'm afraid to go see the doctor and catch the virus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I'm sick, I'm afraid to go see the doctor and catch the virus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418148, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418148, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418148, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661e7e8-7085-11ea-99cf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661e81a-7085-11ea-8026-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661e84c-7085-11ea-b8a7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are you sick ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are you sick?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418164, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418164, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418164, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661e892-7085-11ea-93bc-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661e8c6-7085-11ea-8be1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661e8f6-7085-11ea-a267-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Until when are the surgeries canceled ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Until when are the surgeries canceled?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4181812, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4181812, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4181812, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661e93a-7085-11ea-a8f9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661e96e-7085-11ea-891b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661e998-7085-11ea-baee-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418196, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418196, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418196, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661e9d2-7085-11ea-8662-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661e9fa-7085-11ea-93e2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661ea2c-7085-11ea-aee7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it possible to have Covid-19 if you only have one of the symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it possible to have Covid-19 if you only have one of the symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41821, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418211, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418211, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661ea5e-7085-11ea-ba73-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661ea86-7085-11ea-9257-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661eab8-7085-11ea-b1c2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I go to the ER or my physician directly if I 'm infected ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I go to the ER or my physician directly if I'm infected?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4182248, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4182248, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4182248, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661eae8-7085-11ea-8c4b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661eb1c-7085-11ea-a353-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661eb46-7085-11ea-a2d2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "or go for a test", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "or go for a test", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4182389, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4182389, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4182389, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661eb80-7085-11ea-a389-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661eba8-7085-11ea-968a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661ebda-7085-11ea-afa7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "when will the pandemic end ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "when will the pandemic end?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418253, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418253, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4182541, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661ec0c-7085-11ea-8ad0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661ec3e-7085-11ea-909d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661ec66-7085-11ea-9d34-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the 10 best ways to strengthen your immune system", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the 10 best ways to strengthen your immune system", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418268, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418268, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418268, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661ec98-7085-11ea-a94b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661ecca-7085-11ea-85de-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661ed06-7085-11ea-ae6b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can animals transmit COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can animals transmit COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418286, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418286, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418286, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661ed58-7085-11ea-9974-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661ed88-7085-11ea-9f34-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661edb0-7085-11ea-aa31-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are COVID-19 Symptoms Different in Children and Adults", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are COVID-19 Symptoms Different in Children and Adults", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4183009, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4183009, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4183009, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661edec-7085-11ea-a46f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661ee14-7085-11ea-af74-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661ee46-7085-11ea-8b41-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long has the virus been spreading in Canada ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long has the virus been spreading in Canada?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418315, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4183161, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4183161, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661ee78-7085-11ea-b765-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661eeb4-7085-11ea-8e86-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661eee6-7085-11ea-93f2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Once cured , is it possible to catch up if contact with sick people ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Once cured, is it possible to catch up if contact with sick people?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4183319, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4183328, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4183328, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661ef22-7085-11ea-8b29-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661ef54-7085-11ea-ab47-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661ef7a-7085-11ea-9993-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My husband comes back from a trip and lives with me . What should I do ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My husband comes back from a trip and lives with me. What should I do?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4183471, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4183471, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4183471, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661efb8-7085-11ea-92b1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661efe2-7085-11ea-8932-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661f012-7085-11ea-b252-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What can i do when social distancing", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What can i do when social distancing", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4183612, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4183621, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4183621, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661f046-7085-11ea-bad2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661f06c-7085-11ea-9cb6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661f09e-7085-11ea-b040-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Mortality rate today", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Mortality rate today", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418376, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418376, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418376, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661f0d0-7085-11ea-b23f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661f102-7085-11ea-94fb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661f128-7085-11ea-94be-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What should I do if I have symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What should I do if I have symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4183922, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4183922, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4183922, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661f17a-7085-11ea-842b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661f1ac-7085-11ea-acb8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661f1d4-7085-11ea-bbae-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are young people susceptible to corona virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are young people susceptible to corona virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418407, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418407, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418407, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661f210-7085-11ea-b729-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661f258-7085-11ea-9a5e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661f27e-7085-11ea-b65d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Hello , how long does the virus stay on a surface like a plastic wrap , a door handle , a car steering wheel , in the air ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Hello, how long does the virus stay on a surface like a plastic wrap, a door handle, a car steering wheel, in the air?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4184241, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4184241, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4184241, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661f2b0-7085-11ea-b8b8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661f2e2-7085-11ea-9418-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661f30a-7085-11ea-b5e3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the delay before the appearance of the first symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the delay before the appearance of the first symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418438, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418438, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418438, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661f346-7085-11ea-a34b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661f382-7085-11ea-b596-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661f3b4-7085-11ea-b8e8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How is it going to last ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How is it going to last?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4184551, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4184551, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4184551, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661f3e6-7085-11ea-82be-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661f418-7085-11ea-b443-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661f440-7085-11ea-9b62-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can my dog \u200b\u200bcarry the virus and give it to us ? If so", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can my dog \u200b\u200bcarry the virus and give it to us? If so", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4184692, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4184692, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4184692, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661f47a-7085-11ea-aaf1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661f526-7085-11ea-ae19-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661f5ba-7085-11ea-9295-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I stay quarantined ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I stay quarantined?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4185112, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4185112, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4185112, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661f61e-7085-11ea-8897-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661f65c-7085-11ea-a0a7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661f686-7085-11ea-96a3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What should I do if I am infected", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What should I do if I am infected", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418528, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418528, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418528, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661f6c0-7085-11ea-ab9a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661f6f4-7085-11ea-bfa7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661f724-7085-11ea-89cf-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is the severity of disease dependent on incubation period ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is the severity of disease dependent on incubation period?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418547, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418547, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418547, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661f788-7085-11ea-9bd1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661f7ba-7085-11ea-8519-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661f7e2-7085-11ea-946d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of corona virus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of corona virus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418565, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418565, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418565, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661f834-7085-11ea-aa2a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661f86e-7085-11ea-bd1b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661f898-7085-11ea-ac8e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many cases in Terrebonne ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many cases in Terrebonne?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41858, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41858, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41858, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661f8c8-7085-11ea-81f1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661f918-7085-11ea-9834-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661f954-7085-11ea-a794-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are the symtoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are the symtoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418599, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418599, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418599, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661f986-7085-11ea-986a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661f9b8-7085-11ea-a916-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661f9e2-7085-11ea-8bc0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is COVID-19 deadly ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is COVID-19 deadly?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418616, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418616, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418616, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661fa30-7085-11ea-960d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661fa62-7085-11ea-9c02-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661fa94-7085-11ea-9159-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I am older and have a chronic medical condition , which puts me at a higher risk of becoming seriously ill or even dying from COVID-19 . What can I do to reduce my risk of exposure to the virus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I am older and have a chronic medical condition, which puts me at a higher risk of becoming seriously ill or even dying from COVID-19. What can I do to reduce my risk of exposure to the virus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4186308, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4186308, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4186308, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661fac6-7085-11ea-8f83-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661faf8-7085-11ea-83a4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661fb1e-7085-11ea-815d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can unpackaged vegetables and fruits in grocery stores be a source of spread of the virus ? What steps should we take if we buy them ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can unpackaged vegetables and fruits in grocery stores be a source of spread of the virus? What steps should we take if we buy them?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418645, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418645, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418645, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661fb5c-7085-11ea-9c7b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661fb86-7085-11ea-a4b6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661fbb6-7085-11ea-9006-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it more likely to catch it because I live near a COVID testing center ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it more likely to catch it because I live near a COVID testing center?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4186602, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4186602, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4186602, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661fbe8-7085-11ea-8aa1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661fc1a-7085-11ea-acb4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661fc42-7085-11ea-b816-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where can I get tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where can I get tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418676, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418676, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418676, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661fc88-7085-11ea-be58-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661fcba-7085-11ea-80df-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661fcec-7085-11ea-aeef-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "where did the contagious woman arrested in limoilou walk ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "where did the contagious woman arrested in limoilou walk?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4186938, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4186938, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4186938, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661fd3a-7085-11ea-aaa2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661fd78-7085-11ea-a548-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661fd9e-7085-11ea-9719-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418709, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418709, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418709, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661fdd2-7085-11ea-bf24-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661fe06-7085-11ea-89b4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661fe2c-7085-11ea-bd27-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What do I have to expect after the disease ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What do I have to expect after the disease?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418723, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418723, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418723, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661fe68-7085-11ea-9431-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661fe90-7085-11ea-a131-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661fec2-7085-11ea-9ce6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do I have to wash my groceries and my errands once at home ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do I have to wash my groceries and my errands once at home?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418737, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418737, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418738, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661fef4-7085-11ea-b9b3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661ff1c-7085-11ea-9229-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661ff4c-7085-11ea-a5fd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many young adults are being hospitalized ? Like in percentage ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many young adults are being hospitalized? Like in percentage?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418752, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418752, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418752, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9661ff80-7085-11ea-a70e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9661ffb4-7085-11ea-8a38-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9661ffda-7085-11ea-bd2b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where are the cases of covid19 treated ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where are the cases of covid19 treated?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418766, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418766, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418766, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662001e-7085-11ea-914f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96620052-7085-11ea-8639-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620086-7085-11ea-a5a4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have fever 38 \u00b0 C. Is that corona virus symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have fever 38 \u00b0 C. Is that corona virus symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418784, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418784, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418784, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966200ca-7085-11ea-84b1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96620110-7085-11ea-9005-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620138-7085-11ea-93da-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If a person comes to visit us and they move into a house , what should be monitored or checked to limit the risk of contagion ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If a person comes to visit us and they move into a house, what should be monitored or checked to limit the risk of contagion?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4188008, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4188008, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4188008, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620174-7085-11ea-8922-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662019c-7085-11ea-82c8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966201d8-7085-11ea-93f7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it safe to get a new job that deals with the public ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it safe to get a new job that deals with the public?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418818, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418818, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418818, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620214-7085-11ea-a496-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96620250-7085-11ea-8c90-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620278-7085-11ea-95a1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "covid symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "covid symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4188359, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418837, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418837, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966202d2-7085-11ea-a0f5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96620306-7085-11ea-a8f8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620336-7085-11ea-a897-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I get infected after I healed from it ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I get infected after I healed from it?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4188511, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4188511, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418852, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620368-7085-11ea-990e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966203a4-7085-11ea-97a3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966203d8-7085-11ea-8051-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is the virus easier to catch than the common cold ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is the virus easier to catch than the common cold?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418868, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418868, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418868, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620408-7085-11ea-97c1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662043a-7085-11ea-98ff-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620462-7085-11ea-9202-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What should you do if you do nt have water and soap and sanitizer ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What should you do if you dont have water and soap and sanitizer?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4188821, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4188821, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4188821, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662049e-7085-11ea-b01b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966204da-7085-11ea-8ab6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620502-7085-11ea-91f8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does the government plan to decontaminate people with jets as we have seen in Asia ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does the government plan to decontaminate people with jets as we have seen in Asia?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4189, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4189, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4189, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620552-7085-11ea-98ce-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662057a-7085-11ea-b13a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966205ac-7085-11ea-a575-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many cases of the coronavirus are there in Montreal ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many cases of the coronavirus are there in Montreal?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418914, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418914, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418915, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966205de-7085-11ea-845b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662061a-7085-11ea-a0ae-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620658-7085-11ea-b03d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can someone who has had a coronavirus get infected again", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can someone who has had a coronavirus get infected again", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418932, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418932, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418932, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620692-7085-11ea-9e90-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966206ba-7085-11ea-bd94-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966206ec-7085-11ea-87b0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it dangerous to go for a walk ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it dangerous to go for a walk?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418946, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418947, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418947, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662071e-7085-11ea-9a6c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96620750-7085-11ea-9d46-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620778-7085-11ea-8f74-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the actual size of the Coved-19 ? comparative ...", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the actual size of the Coved-19? comparative...", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4189608, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4189608, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4189608, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966207a8-7085-11ea-a771-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966207dc-7085-11ea-8d27-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620806-7085-11ea-999b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many people died in Belgium ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many people died in Belgium?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4189749, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4189749, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4189749, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620836-7085-11ea-bd30-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96620868-7085-11ea-bd81-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620890-7085-11ea-a7a4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long can the symptoms last ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long can the symptoms last?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.418989, "sourceDate": 1585352964.418989, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.418989, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966208cc-7085-11ea-90db-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966208f4-7085-11ea-91f6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620926-7085-11ea-b9bd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the most common symptoms of COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the most common symptoms of COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419005, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419005, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419005, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662096c-7085-11ea-86a6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966209b4-7085-11ea-b525-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966209ee-7085-11ea-9121-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I am in isolation because I am back from France . Should my family also be in solitary confinement ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I am in isolation because I am back from France. Should my family also be in solitary confinement?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419024, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419024, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419024, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620a1e-7085-11ea-a3b4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96620a52-7085-11ea-ab7e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620a8c-7085-11ea-8537-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I ca n't leave my house , how can I get my medication delivered", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I can't leave my house, how can I get my medication delivered", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41904, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41904, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41904, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620aca-7085-11ea-ad29-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96620af4-7085-11ea-85a7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620b24-7085-11ea-91ea-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long do you expect these restrictive measures to last ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long do you expect these restrictive measures to last?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419054, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419054, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419054, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620b58-7085-11ea-8b7f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96620b7e-7085-11ea-9fb9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620bb0-7085-11ea-b49d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What do I do to pay my rent if I ca n't work ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What do I do to pay my rent if I can't work?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4190679, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4190679, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4190688, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620be2-7085-11ea-a758-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96620c0a-7085-11ea-b479-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620c3a-7085-11ea-89d1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can COVID-19 live on objects ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can COVID-19 live on objects?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419083, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419083, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419083, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620c6e-7085-11ea-8f95-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96620c9e-7085-11ea-a5a1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620cc8-7085-11ea-828b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I go for a walk", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I go for a walk", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4190972, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4190972, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4190972, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620cfa-7085-11ea-9ef2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96620d2c-7085-11ea-ad51-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620d54-7085-11ea-a419-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is the cov\u0131d-19 's symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is the cov\u0131d-19's symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419113, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419113, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419113, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620d9a-7085-11ea-a76c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96620de8-7085-11ea-a9a7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620e1c-7085-11ea-86ab-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus stay active on smooth surfaces ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus stay active on smooth surfaces?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4191308, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4191308, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4191308, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620e58-7085-11ea-b8d4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96620e80-7085-11ea-96f1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620ea8-7085-11ea-9b6f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "am i gon na die ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "am i gonna die?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4191449, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4191449, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419146, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620ee4-7085-11ea-808d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96620f18-7085-11ea-8e85-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620f3e-7085-11ea-a15e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What should I do if I think I or my child is infected with COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What should I do if I think I or my child is infected with COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4191601, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4191601, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4191601, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620f70-7085-11ea-a545-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96620fa2-7085-11ea-a429-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96620fca-7085-11ea-afbc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will Covid19 mutate to a different more virulent strain", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will Covid19 mutate to a different more virulent strain", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419174, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419174, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419174, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96620ffa-7085-11ea-912a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662102e-7085-11ea-96ad-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96621058-7085-11ea-9662-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the covid ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the covid?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419188, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419188, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419188, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621088-7085-11ea-8d8e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966210ba-7085-11ea-b237-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966210e2-7085-11ea-9953-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can my cat transmit the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can my cat transmit the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419202, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419202, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419202, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621114-7085-11ea-9f9e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621146-7085-11ea-aeb2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662116e-7085-11ea-b9c7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "who needs to be isolated ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "who needs to be isolated?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4192178, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4192178, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4192178, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966211b4-7085-11ea-a1e5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621218-7085-11ea-8b22-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96621254-7085-11ea-921d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there a vaccine for COVID ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there a vaccine for COVID?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4192388, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4192388, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4192388, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621286-7085-11ea-98b9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966212b8-7085-11ea-8444-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966212e2-7085-11ea-802a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "why do I have to stay dear to us", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "why do I have to stay dear to us", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419253, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419253, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419253, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662131c-7085-11ea-9e6c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621346-7085-11ea-ae9d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96621376-7085-11ea-b607-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where can I find current and credible information on COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where can I find current and credible information on COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4192698, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4192698, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4192698, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966213c6-7085-11ea-af46-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966213ee-7085-11ea-aa10-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662141e-7085-11ea-9d27-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do we have migraines as symptoms of COVID-19 , please ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do we have migraines as symptoms of COVID-19, please?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419285, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419285, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419285, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621452-7085-11ea-9001-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621486-7085-11ea-9269-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966214ac-7085-11ea-89a6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long will the pandemic last if people follow the confinement rules ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long will the pandemic last if people follow the confinement rules?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4192991, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4192991, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4192991, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966214de-7085-11ea-9c2c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621510-7085-11ea-a92c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96621538-7085-11ea-9984-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to clean porous surfaces like handbags , backpacks , reusable grocery bags ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to clean porous surfaces like handbags, backpacks, reusable grocery bags?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419313, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419313, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419313, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621574-7085-11ea-9f57-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966215b0-7085-11ea-8b65-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966215e2-7085-11ea-bcb5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How fast does it spread ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How fast does it spread?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4193332, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4193332, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419334, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662163a-7085-11ea-a420-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621678-7085-11ea-a3f0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966216a8-7085-11ea-8a87-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I follow the guidelines of universal protection against viruses , why should I isolate myself ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I follow the guidelines of universal protection against viruses, why should I isolate myself?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419349, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419349, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41935, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966216dc-7085-11ea-96e6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621706-7085-11ea-9d30-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96621736-7085-11ea-8895-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Forget it", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Forget it", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4193642, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4193642, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4193642, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621768-7085-11ea-9829-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662179a-7085-11ea-add8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966217c2-7085-11ea-8302-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are traditional disinfectants , such as Lysol and disinfectant wipes , effective in killing COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are traditional disinfectants, such as Lysol and disinfectant wipes, effective in killing COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4193778, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4193778, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4193778, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966217f4-7085-11ea-a27d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621826-7085-11ea-9b86-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662184c-7085-11ea-82fb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there antiviral therapy for COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there antiviral therapy for COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419392, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419392, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419392, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621880-7085-11ea-a67e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966218b4-7085-11ea-b51a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966218da-7085-11ea-900b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How much can the financial compensations related to the hours lost from work amount to ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How much can the financial compensations related to the hours lost from work amount to?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4194062, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4194062, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4194062, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662190c-7085-11ea-b33e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662193e-7085-11ea-a6d8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96621966-7085-11ea-a9e2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My partner went to Toronto last week , should he be in voluntary confinement ? What about me ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My partner went to Toronto last week, should he be in voluntary confinement? What about me?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41942, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41942, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41942, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621998-7085-11ea-9ce4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966219ca-7085-11ea-86f7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966219f4-7085-11ea-aad1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can you have COVID-19 without having a fever", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can you have COVID-19 without having a fever", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419434, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419434, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419434, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621a2e-7085-11ea-9f5b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621a58-7085-11ea-ba4d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96621a92-7085-11ea-8315-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What should I do if I start feeling sick with similar symptoms as in covid19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What should I do if I start feeling sick with similar symptoms as in covid19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4194539, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4194539, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4194539, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621aec-7085-11ea-a7cb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621b1e-7085-11ea-9890-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96621b46-7085-11ea-b560-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What can you use to disinfect surfaces ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What can you use to disinfect surfaces?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419468, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419468, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419468, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621b78-7085-11ea-9bde-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621ba8-7085-11ea-b1d0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96621bd2-7085-11ea-af5b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "treatment for covid 19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "treatment for covid 19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4194822, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4194822, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4194822, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621c06-7085-11ea-9e25-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621c36-7085-11ea-b7c1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96621c5e-7085-11ea-ad77-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many Canadians currently have corona virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many Canadians currently have corona virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4194958, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4194958, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4194958, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621c9a-7085-11ea-8bc2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621cd8-7085-11ea-8c21-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96621d08-7085-11ea-95ea-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What 's covid19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What's covid19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419513, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419513, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419513, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621d3a-7085-11ea-94fd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621d6c-7085-11ea-b600-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96621d94-7085-11ea-a243-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "systomps", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "systomps", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4195268, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4195268, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4195268, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621dd0-7085-11ea-bceb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621df8-7085-11ea-93a9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96621e28-7085-11ea-b7b8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long can we keep a protective mask ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long can we keep a protective mask?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419541, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419541, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419541, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621e5c-7085-11ea-88e7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621e98-7085-11ea-bfe8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96621eca-7085-11ea-90d6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Hello ,", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Hello,", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419561, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419561, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419561, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621f1a-7085-11ea-a7d9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621f4c-7085-11ea-87b1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96621f7e-7085-11ea-bc9c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how long does it take before you have symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how long does it take before you have symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419575, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4195762, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4195762, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96621fb0-7085-11ea-99a2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96621fe2-7085-11ea-9177-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662200a-7085-11ea-9b79-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is social distancing and why is it important", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is social distancing and why is it important", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.41959, "sourceDate": 1585352964.41959, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.41959, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96622046-7085-11ea-a9f8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96622082-7085-11ea-a5e8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966220b4-7085-11ea-bfac-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I go jogging during the period of voluntary isolation ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I go jogging during the period of voluntary isolation?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419607, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419607, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419607, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966220e6-7085-11ea-a03f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96622118-7085-11ea-b64f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96622140-7085-11ea-a9db-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the systematic symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the systematic symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4196212, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4196212, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4196212, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96622174-7085-11ea-afbc-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966221a4-7085-11ea-b386-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966221cc-7085-11ea-8403-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it true that the pandemic will ease during the summer ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it true that the pandemic will ease during the summer?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419635, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419635, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419635, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662221c-7085-11ea-b5a1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662224c-7085-11ea-83f8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96622276-7085-11ea-8514-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I go to the grocery store if I am 70 years old ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I go to the grocery store if I am 70 years old?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419652, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419652, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419652, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966222a8-7085-11ea-a438-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966222da-7085-11ea-9f63-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96622302-7085-11ea-8137-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is covid 19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is covid 19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419668, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419668, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419668, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96622352-7085-11ea-b284-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96622398-7085-11ea-87d7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966223ca-7085-11ea-a86f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Medicines or plants that help heal or prevent", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Medicines or plants that help heal or prevent", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4196858, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4196858, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4196858, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96622406-7085-11ea-bbd2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662242e-7085-11ea-8742-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96622458-7085-11ea-ace6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are grocery stores going to have to close like restaurants ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are grocery stores going to have to close like restaurants?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4197, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4197, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4197, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96622488-7085-11ea-a819-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966224ba-7085-11ea-b307-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966224e2-7085-11ea-b64f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How dangerous it is for pregnant womens ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How dangerous it is for pregnant womens?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419714, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419714, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419714, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96622514-7085-11ea-ae2f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96622546-7085-11ea-b47b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662256e-7085-11ea-8dcc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is pandemic", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is pandemic", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4197278, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4197278, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4197278, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966225a8-7085-11ea-8425-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966225d2-7085-11ea-bf6b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662260c-7085-11ea-a695-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can I get tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can I get tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419744, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419745, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419745, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662264a-7085-11ea-809a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96622690-7085-11ea-983b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966226b8-7085-11ea-854a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the age groups of people likely to die from COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the age groups of people likely to die from COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419761, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419761, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419761, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966226e8-7085-11ea-be54-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662271c-7085-11ea-be5c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96622746-7085-11ea-9dcc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What does it really mean to isolate yourself or self quarantine What should I do or not do", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What does it really mean to isolate yourself or self quarantine What should I do or not do", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419778, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419778, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419779, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966227a8-7085-11ea-846f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966227da-7085-11ea-b9cf-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662280c-7085-11ea-be5b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can I make the difference between a cold and covid19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can I make the difference between a cold and covid19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419795, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419795, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419795, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662283e-7085-11ea-926b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96622870-7085-11ea-bce4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96622898-7085-11ea-80c8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is the virus transmissible from humans to animals ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is the virus transmissible from humans to animals?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419809, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419809, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419809, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966228ca-7085-11ea-9b7d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966228fa-7085-11ea-892f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96622924-7085-11ea-bedc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can you catch the virus by eating fruit bought at the grocery store ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can you catch the virus by eating fruit bought at the grocery store?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4198232, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4198232, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4198232, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96622962-7085-11ea-8336-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96622988-7085-11ea-8902-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966229b0-7085-11ea-9892-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "A person close to me is returning from my trip . Do I also have to place myself in self - isolation ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "A person close to me is returning from my trip. Do I also have to place myself in self-isolation?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419837, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419837, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419837, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966229ec-7085-11ea-8c4d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96622a14-7085-11ea-a0db-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96622a3a-7085-11ea-8bcb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long is incubation period ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long is incubation period?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419851, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419851, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419851, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96622a78-7085-11ea-938e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96622a9e-7085-11ea-b11f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96622ad2-7085-11ea-86bc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of covid19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of covid19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4198651, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4198651, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419866, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96622b06-7085-11ea-9bf6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96622b2c-7085-11ea-ad60-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96622b5e-7085-11ea-94c1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have covid-19 , how long will I be contagious ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have covid-19, how long will I be contagious?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4198809, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4198809, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4198809, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96622ba4-7085-11ea-ab52-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96622bd8-7085-11ea-9f67-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96622bfe-7085-11ea-8119-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What should I do if I have symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What should I do if I have symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4198961, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4198961, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4198961, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96622c46-7085-11ea-84be-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96622e06-7085-11ea-ab7e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96622e42-7085-11ea-b4dd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have cough . Does that mean I might be infected ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have cough. Does that mean I might be infected?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4199538, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4199538, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4199538, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96622e74-7085-11ea-9b12-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96622ea6-7085-11ea-b22c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96622ed8-7085-11ea-b214-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How serious is COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How serious is COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419968, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419968, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419968, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96622f0a-7085-11ea-abbb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96622f3a-7085-11ea-a6b2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96622f64-7085-11ea-954b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should we be confined ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should we be confined?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4199831, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4199831, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4199831, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96622f98-7085-11ea-ac8b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96622fc8-7085-11ea-83c4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96622ff0-7085-11ea-a7db-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I continue to take walks with friends ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I continue to take walks with friends?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.419997, "sourceDate": 1585352964.419997, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.419997, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96623022-7085-11ea-92fe-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623086-7085-11ea-ad13-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966230b8-7085-11ea-a16b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I need to take a blood test . Is there a large risk for infection ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I need to take a blood test. Is there a large risk for infection?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420019, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420019, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4200199, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96623108-7085-11ea-8cf6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662313a-7085-11ea-8d8f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96623162-7085-11ea-b71c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the main symptoms of the disease ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the main symptoms of the disease?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420036, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420036, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420036, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966231a8-7085-11ea-8700-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966231da-7085-11ea-aa12-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662320c-7085-11ea-94ee-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "are you a doctor ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "are you a doctor?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42005, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4200509, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4200509, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662323e-7085-11ea-897d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623270-7085-11ea-b43e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96623298-7085-11ea-b449-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "can I go shopping at the SAQ ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "can I go shopping at the SAQ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420065, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420065, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420065, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966232ca-7085-11ea-b420-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966232fa-7085-11ea-9729-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96623324-7085-11ea-980e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long before we are healed", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long before we are healed", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420079, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420079, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420079, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96623358-7085-11ea-9447-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623388-7085-11ea-b4e7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966233b0-7085-11ea-a891-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the incubation period ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the incubation period?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4200928, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4200928, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4200928, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966233e2-7085-11ea-b46e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623414-7085-11ea-8908-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662343a-7085-11ea-8e34-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What 's corona virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What's corona virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4201071, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4201071, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4201071, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662346e-7085-11ea-bfae-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662349e-7085-11ea-9210-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966234c8-7085-11ea-bf40-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are the symptoms of coronavirus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are the symptoms of coronavirus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4201212, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4201212, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4201212, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966234fa-7085-11ea-9e96-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623540-7085-11ea-a8cc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662357a-7085-11ea-8da7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus live on surfaces", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus live on surfaces", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420141, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420141, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420141, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966235c2-7085-11ea-96e8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966235f4-7085-11ea-9662-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96623626-7085-11ea-9d30-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I invite friends over for dinner ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I invite friends over for dinner?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4201548, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420156, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420156, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96623658-7085-11ea-8ba0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662368a-7085-11ea-ac12-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966236b4-7085-11ea-9897-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus stay on surfaces ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus stay on surfaces?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42017, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42017, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42017, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966236e4-7085-11ea-b19c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662370c-7085-11ea-b28b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662373e-7085-11ea-b96e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus stay in the air ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus stay in the air?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420183, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420183, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4201841, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96623770-7085-11ea-be24-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623798-7085-11ea-b869-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966237ca-7085-11ea-b60c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is the virus manufactured or naturally occurring ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is the virus manufactured or naturally occurring?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420197, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420197, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420198, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966237fa-7085-11ea-a73f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623824-7085-11ea-af8f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96623858-7085-11ea-b3a2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can we eat raw vegetables and fruits ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can we eat raw vegetables and fruits?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420212, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420212, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420212, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96623888-7085-11ea-8da6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966238e2-7085-11ea-892e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96623914-7085-11ea-8afd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is auto isolation ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is auto isolation?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4202309, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4202309, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4202309, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96623950-7085-11ea-96d3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623978-7085-11ea-bd43-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966239a8-7085-11ea-ad8b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How is the virus spread ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How is the virus spread?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420248, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420248, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420248, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966239f0-7085-11ea-8020-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623a36-7085-11ea-b8c7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96623a68-7085-11ea-9b27-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What do we do about the mask shortage", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What do we do about the mask shortage", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420265, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420265, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420265, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96623a9a-7085-11ea-8f88-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623acc-7085-11ea-bc24-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96623afe-7085-11ea-82dc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I wear one .", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I wear one.", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420279, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420279, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42028, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96623b30-7085-11ea-9dbf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623b58-7085-11ea-8edd-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96623b8a-7085-11ea-bb48-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What if I have a cough and I have a fever ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What if I have a cough and I have a fever?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420293, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420293, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4202938, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96623bba-7085-11ea-b2a7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623be4-7085-11ea-b382-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96623c18-7085-11ea-a1b8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have temperature , what should I do ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have temperature, what should I do?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4203079, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4203079, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4203079, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96623c48-7085-11ea-a1dc-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623c70-7085-11ea-ab4c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96623ca2-7085-11ea-a491-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the death rate of covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the death rate of covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420321, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420321, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420322, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96623cd4-7085-11ea-b2f3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623d1a-7085-11ea-bf5e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96623d4c-7085-11ea-9171-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does the government provide financial assistance for the self - employed ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does the government provide financial assistance for the self-employed?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4203389, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4203389, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42034, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96623d88-7085-11ea-8edb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623db0-7085-11ea-9d3f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96623de2-7085-11ea-9451-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I practice social distancing ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I practice social distancing?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420355, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420355, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420355, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96623e28-7085-11ea-926d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623e5a-7085-11ea-a1e9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96623e82-7085-11ea-b2a9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When will the schools start again ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When will the schools start again?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4203699, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4203699, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4203699, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96623eb4-7085-11ea-b13a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623efa-7085-11ea-8741-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96623f22-7085-11ea-9718-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can an asymptomatic patient with Covid 19 be contagious after 14 days of quarantine ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can an asymptomatic patient with Covid 19 be contagious after 14 days of quarantine?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420386, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420386, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420386, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96623f5e-7085-11ea-abd4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96623f86-7085-11ea-96c3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96623fae-7085-11ea-81a5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how painful will it be if I got the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how painful will it be if I got the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4204001, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4204001, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4204001, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96623fe8-7085-11ea-9e4e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96624012-7085-11ea-bad2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96624046-7085-11ea-94b4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "test", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "test", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420414, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420414, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420414, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96624076-7085-11ea-8b8a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662409e-7085-11ea-89ca-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966240d0-7085-11ea-b2ae-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of covid 19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of covid 19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420428, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420429, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420429, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96624102-7085-11ea-9485-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662413e-7085-11ea-8b6c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662417a-7085-11ea-9911-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do I have to wash all my purchases at the grocery store ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do I have to wash all my purchases at the grocery store?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420446, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420446, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420446, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966241b6-7085-11ea-9296-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966241de-7085-11ea-bd19-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96624210-7085-11ea-aec9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus survive on different surfaces and in aerosol ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus survive on different surfaces and in aerosol?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42046, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42046, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42046, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96624242-7085-11ea-b39e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96624268-7085-11ea-90a0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662429c-7085-11ea-bb9d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are diabetics more at risk than others ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are diabetics more at risk than others?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420476, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420476, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420476, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966242e2-7085-11ea-8918-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662430a-7085-11ea-b15e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96624350-7085-11ea-b6ad-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long should I stay in confinement", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long should I stay in confinement", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4204931, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4204931, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4204931, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662438c-7085-11ea-9b30-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966243b4-7085-11ea-8634-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966243e6-7085-11ea-ad2c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it like regular flu ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it like regular flu?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420507, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420507, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420508, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96624418-7085-11ea-ac0a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96624440-7085-11ea-844a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96624474-7085-11ea-92b0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is total containment necessary for people undergoing chemotherapy treatment ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is total containment necessary for people undergoing chemotherapy treatment?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420522, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420522, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420522, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966244a4-7085-11ea-85b6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966244e8-7085-11ea-a07b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662451c-7085-11ea-8561-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What will be th impact on international students ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What will be th impact on international students?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4205399, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4205399, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4205399, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662456c-7085-11ea-9b30-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662459e-7085-11ea-bc16-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966245c6-7085-11ea-b464-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long am I contagious if I have covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long am I contagious if I have covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420556, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420556, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420556, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96624602-7085-11ea-916f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96624628-7085-11ea-a7ab-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662465c-7085-11ea-9101-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how can one fight the virus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how can one fight the virus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4205701, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4205701, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4205709, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662468c-7085-11ea-9b11-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966246b6-7085-11ea-bf2c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966246e8-7085-11ea-86fd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can humans be infected with a new animal - derived coronavirus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can humans be infected with a new animal-derived coronavirus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4205859, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420587, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420587, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662472e-7085-11ea-ae75-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96624762-7085-11ea-a799-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96624788-7085-11ea-9eee-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what should I do if I work and I am sick", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what should I do if I work and I am sick", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4206011, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4206011, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4206011, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966247c6-7085-11ea-ab12-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966247ec-7085-11ea-bd8a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96624814-7085-11ea-bdf5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How far do I have to stay from other people to follow government instructions ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How far do I have to stay from other people to follow government instructions?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420615, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420615, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420615, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96624850-7085-11ea-9d42-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96624878-7085-11ea-8e85-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966248a8-7085-11ea-9bb2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is canada quarantine policy ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is canada quarantine policy?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420629, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420629, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420629, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966248dc-7085-11ea-af1e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96624906-7085-11ea-bc26-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662494a-7085-11ea-8620-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can we still be a carrier of COVID-19 if we have had it and we have been cured ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can we still be a carrier of COVID-19 if we have had it and we have been cured?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420647, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420647, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420647, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96624990-7085-11ea-ba89-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966249cc-7085-11ea-9682-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966249fe-7085-11ea-8090-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How often should i take my temperature ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How often should i take my temperature?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420664, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420664, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420664, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96624a3a-7085-11ea-acd2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96624a62-7085-11ea-98ac-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96624a94-7085-11ea-9a00-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have just returned from my trip , I was alone , should everyone Chaz avoid contact with me at all costs", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have just returned from my trip, I was alone, should everyone Chaz avoid contact with me at all costs", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420678, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420678, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420678, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96624ac6-7085-11ea-a575-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96624aee-7085-11ea-8d11-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96624b1e-7085-11ea-9314-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What does assynptomatic mean", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What does assynptomatic mean", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420694, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420694, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420694, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96624b66-7085-11ea-8d29-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96624b8c-7085-11ea-9a63-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96624bc0-7085-11ea-8978-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are covid symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are covid symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4207091, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4207091, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4207091, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96624bf4-7085-11ea-938f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96624c24-7085-11ea-b1be-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96624c4c-7085-11ea-95a1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the danger for a newborn baby ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the danger for a newborn baby?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420725, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420725, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420725, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96624ca6-7085-11ea-a098-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96624ce2-7085-11ea-a0ad-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96624d14-7085-11ea-8116-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the Symptome", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the Symptome", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420743, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420743, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420743, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96624d50-7085-11ea-9b2b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96624d8c-7085-11ea-bb29-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96624dbe-7085-11ea-8204-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where is my nearest screening center ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where is my nearest screening center?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4207602, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4207602, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4207602, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96624dfa-7085-11ea-9389-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96624e22-7085-11ea-be5f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96624e4a-7085-11ea-a244-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the possible symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the possible symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420774, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420774, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420774, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96624e86-7085-11ea-9184-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96624eae-7085-11ea-8cc9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96624ee2-7085-11ea-864f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How it works ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How it works?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420788, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420788, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420788, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96624f12-7085-11ea-a6fd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96624f3a-7085-11ea-99d3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96624f6c-7085-11ea-a0b7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are you symtoms of covid ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are you symtoms of covid?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420804, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420804, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420804, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96624fb4-7085-11ea-b3d3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96624fe4-7085-11ea-a58a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662500c-7085-11ea-b5e3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how many people tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how many people tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420819, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420819, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420819, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662503e-7085-11ea-9820-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96625070-7085-11ea-af62-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96625098-7085-11ea-8211-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Covid19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Covid19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420833, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420833, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420833, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966250ca-7085-11ea-afdd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966250fa-7085-11ea-ad58-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96625124-7085-11ea-a7e2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Cual es la diferencia entre vacuna , tratamiento y cura del COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Cual es la diferencia entre vacuna, tratamiento y cura del COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4208472, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4208472, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4208472, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96625162-7085-11ea-a334-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966251a6-7085-11ea-8427-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966251d8-7085-11ea-a262-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to prevent the spread of COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to prevent the spread of COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420864, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420865, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420865, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662520a-7085-11ea-aa62-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96625234-7085-11ea-8a61-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96625264-7085-11ea-98a1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "After contracting COVID-19 and recovering , Is it still possible to infect other people ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "After contracting COVID-19 and recovering, Is it still possible to infect other people?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4208791, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4208791, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4208791, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96625298-7085-11ea-9591-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966252be-7085-11ea-90e9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966252f0-7085-11ea-9293-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where do coronaviruses come from", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where do coronaviruses come from", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420893, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420893, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420893, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96625322-7085-11ea-9f9a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96625354-7085-11ea-827c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662537a-7085-11ea-a845-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus survive outside the body ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus survive outside the body?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420908, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420908, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420908, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966253c2-7085-11ea-8dbc-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966253f4-7085-11ea-a3bf-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662541c-7085-11ea-924a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the main symptoms of COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the main symptoms of COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420923, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420923, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420923, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662544c-7085-11ea-9cab-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96625480-7085-11ea-9c90-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966254a8-7085-11ea-a8df-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of coronavirus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of coronavirus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4209359, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420937, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420937, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966254da-7085-11ea-a4c5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662550c-7085-11ea-ae0e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96625534-7085-11ea-bc98-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4209511, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4209511, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4209511, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96625566-7085-11ea-a1df-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966255c0-7085-11ea-bf46-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966255fa-7085-11ea-98eb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have injuries on my hands , am I more at risk of contracting the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have injuries on my hands, am I more at risk of contracting the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420971, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420971, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420971, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662562e-7085-11ea-9452-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96625662-7085-11ea-83ac-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96625688-7085-11ea-aeb1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If someone was infected once , can they be reinfected ? Can they still carry the virus and infect others ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If someone was infected once, can they be reinfected? Can they still carry the virus and infect others?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.420985, "sourceDate": 1585352964.420985, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.420985, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966256c6-7085-11ea-86d3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966256ec-7085-11ea-81b1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662571e-7085-11ea-8ab9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can we visit a newborn", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can we visit a newborn", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4209988, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96625750-7085-11ea-8866-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96625782-7085-11ea-ba07-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966257a8-7085-11ea-8828-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does the amount of virus one is exposed to change the severity of the symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does the amount of virus one is exposed to change the severity of the symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421015, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421016, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421016, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966257f0-7085-11ea-a65c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96625822-7085-11ea-a222-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662584a-7085-11ea-8dbc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there a vaccine currently being tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there a vaccine currently being tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4210298, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4210298, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4210298, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662587a-7085-11ea-8b20-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966258ae-7085-11ea-a14e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966258d8-7085-11ea-aecf-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the% of the population affected by each province in Quebec ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the% of the population affected by each province in Quebec?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4210439, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4210439, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4210439, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96625912-7085-11ea-bbc2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662593a-7085-11ea-a5f5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96625962-7085-11ea-bdef-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are we going to limit the number of items per person at the grocery store to prevent them from running out ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are we going to limit the number of items per person at the grocery store to prevent them from running out?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421058, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421058, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421058, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662599e-7085-11ea-9730-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966259c6-7085-11ea-a50c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966259ee-7085-11ea-bf7f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "does wearing mask protect me from covid 19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "does wearing mask protect me from covid 19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4210718, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4210718, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4210718, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96625a28-7085-11ea-b4f9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96625a7a-7085-11ea-a912-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96625ab6-7085-11ea-abe4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How dangerous is it for me ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How dangerous is it for me?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421092, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421092, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421092, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96625ae8-7085-11ea-b147-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96625b1a-7085-11ea-a601-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96625b42-7085-11ea-89cd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does the Coronavirus go to the wash ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does the Coronavirus go to the wash?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4211059, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4211059, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4211059, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96625b7e-7085-11ea-8c3b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96625bba-7085-11ea-adb0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96625bec-7085-11ea-a638-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I felt sick", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I felt sick", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4211252, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4211252, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4211252, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96625c34-7085-11ea-844f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96625c64-7085-11ea-8b14-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96625c98-7085-11ea-bd22-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I cross someone on the street , how are the chance to catch the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I cross someone on the street, how are the chance to catch the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42114, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42114, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42114, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96625cc8-7085-11ea-9c21-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96625cfa-7085-11ea-bacc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96625d22-7085-11ea-bb2f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My spouse is a confirmed case , should I call immediately 1", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My spouse is a confirmed case, should I call immediately 1", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421154, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421154, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421154, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96625d54-7085-11ea-a86c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96625d86-7085-11ea-aafc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96625dc2-7085-11ea-bbf2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What COVID-19 stands for ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What COVID-19 stands for?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42117, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421171, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421171, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96625e08-7085-11ea-9213-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96625e30-7085-11ea-986c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96625e62-7085-11ea-b7d6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the main synptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the main synptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421186, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421186, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421186, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96625e94-7085-11ea-9f75-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96625ec6-7085-11ea-adac-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96625f0c-7085-11ea-922c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the security measures to minimize the risk COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the security measures to minimize the risk COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421203, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421203, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421203, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96625f3e-7085-11ea-8548-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96625f70-7085-11ea-ba75-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96625f98-7085-11ea-969d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long after the infection do the first symptoms develop ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long after the infection do the first symptoms develop?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421217, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421217, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421217, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96625fca-7085-11ea-8139-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96625ffa-7085-11ea-8aa0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96626024-7085-11ea-93cd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is covid ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is covid?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421233, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421233, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421233, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96626068-7085-11ea-a7a8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662609c-7085-11ea-bf61-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966260c6-7085-11ea-b4ce-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the incubation time of the virus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the incubation time of the virus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421247, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421247, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421247, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96626100-7085-11ea-a453-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96626128-7085-11ea-9e3d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96626150-7085-11ea-a037-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many cases are there in the us", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many cases are there in the us", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421261, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421261, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421261, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662618c-7085-11ea-b513-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966261b4-7085-11ea-b144-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966261dc-7085-11ea-9078-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If infected , Should i just rest at home for 14 days and I 'll be okay ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If infected, Should i just rest at home for 14 days and I'll be okay?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421275, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421275, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421275, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96626218-7085-11ea-8a6a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96626240-7085-11ea-97a5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96626268-7085-11ea-b144-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "is covid-19 dangerous", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "is covid-19 dangerous", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421293, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421293, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421293, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966262c2-7085-11ea-93c2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96626308-7085-11ea-827a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96626330-7085-11ea-afcb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What should i do if i am short of breath ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What should i do if i am short of breath?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421309, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421309, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421309, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96626362-7085-11ea-ae6f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96626394-7085-11ea-b733-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966263ba-7085-11ea-8864-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will we really be able to revive as before the pandemic ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will we really be able to revive as before the pandemic?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421323, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421323, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421323, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966263f8-7085-11ea-9e7e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662641e-7085-11ea-9fb3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96626452-7085-11ea-ab5b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it safe to order food ( take - out ) ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it safe to order food (take-out)?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4213388, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4213388, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4213388, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96626498-7085-11ea-855a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966264c0-7085-11ea-bf4d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966264f4-7085-11ea-8dc3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the advice surrounding outdoor exercise / sport ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the advice surrounding outdoor exercise / sport?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421354, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421354, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421354, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96626524-7085-11ea-a2e3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96626558-7085-11ea-a9ea-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662657e-7085-11ea-8204-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how to get info for screening", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how to get info for screening", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4213681, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4213681, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4213681, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966265ba-7085-11ea-982a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966265e2-7085-11ea-a1d2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662660a-7085-11ea-97c4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why Covid 19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why Covid 19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4213839, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4213839, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4213839, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96626650-7085-11ea-b7af-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662668c-7085-11ea-9d68-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966266be-7085-11ea-9c6c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how i can test if i have the diease ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how i can test if i have the diease?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4214, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4214, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4214, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96626706-7085-11ea-acfc-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96626736-7085-11ea-9d6e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96626768-7085-11ea-8af3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will people on LTD ( Long Term Disability ) drill receive their payments ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will people on LTD (Long Term Disability) drill receive their payments?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421417, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421417, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421417, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662679a-7085-11ea-8fc7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966267d8-7085-11ea-afe4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966267fe-7085-11ea-b9bb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "will the virus continue to spread for a long time ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "will the virus continue to spread for a long time?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4214342, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4214342, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4214342, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662684c-7085-11ea-ba09-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96626876-7085-11ea-97f7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966268a8-7085-11ea-8372-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When should I go to the ER ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When should I go to the ER?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421449, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421449, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421449, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966268da-7085-11ea-a62f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662690c-7085-11ea-bcfa-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96626934-7085-11ea-94d7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can humans get the new coronavirus from cats and dogs", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can humans get the new coronavirus from cats and dogs", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4214652, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4214652, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4214652, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662697a-7085-11ea-a22c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966269ac-7085-11ea-a9d8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966269d4-7085-11ea-9156-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long can the virus live on the skin ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long can the virus live on the skin?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421479, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421479, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421479, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96626a10-7085-11ea-9f7b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96626a4c-7085-11ea-a069-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96626a7e-7085-11ea-a09b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I travel ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I travel?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421498, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421498, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421498, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96626acc-7085-11ea-98f8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96626b00-7085-11ea-a5d6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96626b34-7085-11ea-b4db-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "why do I have to be in confinement", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "why do I have to be in confinement", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421514, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421514, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421514, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96626b64-7085-11ea-9e81-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96626c4a-7085-11ea-9040-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96626c7a-7085-11ea-b7d5-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what has caused it", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what has caused it", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4215481, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4215481, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4215481, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96626cb8-7085-11ea-bdb0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96626ce8-7085-11ea-8bef-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96626d12-7085-11ea-85ad-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Must the fever - symptom related to COVID-19 be a continuous fever , or is it possible that the fever is short - lived ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Must the fever-symptom related to COVID-19 be a continuous fever, or is it possible that the fever is short-lived?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4215622, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4215622, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4215622, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96626d4c-7085-11ea-8456-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96626d76-7085-11ea-bdc6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96626d9e-7085-11ea-9ee4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What to do if I cough", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What to do if I cough", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421576, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421576, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421576, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96626dda-7085-11ea-9a28-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96626e02-7085-11ea-adb8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96626e52-7085-11ea-8206-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My parents are old , can I visit them to help them ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My parents are old, can I visit them to help them?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421597, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421597, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421597, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96626ea2-7085-11ea-88d4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96626ed4-7085-11ea-8b27-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96626f06-7085-11ea-8e32-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can I protect myself when I am caring for someone who may have COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can I protect myself when I am caring for someone who may have COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421611, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421612, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421612, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96626f38-7085-11ea-aea0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96626f68-7085-11ea-b854-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96626f92-7085-11ea-88a9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how can I help to prevent spread of corona virus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how can I help to prevent spread of corona virus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421626, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421626, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421626, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96626fc6-7085-11ea-b39f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96626fec-7085-11ea-afdc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662701e-7085-11ea-9f64-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can you get covid19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can you get covid19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42164, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42164, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42164, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96627050-7085-11ea-81a5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627082-7085-11ea-a57c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966270a8-7085-11ea-8eeb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is the cough still dry ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is the cough still dry?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421654, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421654, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421654, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966270dc-7085-11ea-a44c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662710c-7085-11ea-9b25-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96627136-7085-11ea-8598-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long will we have to stay inside ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long will we have to stay inside?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421668, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421668, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421668, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96627168-7085-11ea-9b24-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662719a-7085-11ea-b0ee-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966271c2-7085-11ea-b3ed-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it necessary to clean all the groceries brought home ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it necessary to clean all the groceries brought home?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4216828, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4216828, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4216828, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966271fe-7085-11ea-9c69-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627246-7085-11ea-8303-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96627276-7085-11ea-969c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have a lot of stress regarding COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have a lot of stress regarding COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4217012, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4217012, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4217012, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966272ba-7085-11ea-9c6f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966272f8-7085-11ea-ac77-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96627334-7085-11ea-8b5a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I get the virus from a stray cat ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I get the virus from a stray cat?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421719, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421719, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421719, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96627370-7085-11ea-bd6b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627398-7085-11ea-abe5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966273ca-7085-11ea-b716-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have headaches , am I sick ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have headaches, am I sick?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4217331, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4217331, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4217339, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966273fa-7085-11ea-afe5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627424-7085-11ea-ab52-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96627458-7085-11ea-bd1e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it dangerous for me ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it dangerous for me?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421748, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421748, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421748, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96627488-7085-11ea-9048-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966274ba-7085-11ea-b98a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966274e2-7085-11ea-95d1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I have dinner with friends ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I have dinner with friends?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421762, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421762, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421762, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96627514-7085-11ea-b62b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627546-7085-11ea-8f92-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662756e-7085-11ea-b563-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the dangers for people over 70 years old ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the dangers for people over 70 years old?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4217758, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4217758, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4217758, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966275a8-7085-11ea-8d4a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966275dc-7085-11ea-a51e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96627606-7085-11ea-bc4b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do you have a sore throat ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do you have a sore throat?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421791, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421791, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421791, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96627636-7085-11ea-b22c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662767a-7085-11ea-a8ec-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966276b8-7085-11ea-89ec-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How does it spread ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How does it spread?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4218109, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4218109, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4218109, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966276fe-7085-11ea-aebf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627730-7085-11ea-8902-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96627762-7085-11ea-958f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If anyone is infected , was it contagious before having symptoms ? How long before ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If anyone is infected, was it contagious before having symptoms? How long before?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421825, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421825, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4218261, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96627794-7085-11ea-924d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966277ba-7085-11ea-86ea-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966277ee-7085-11ea-8fdb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long can the virus stay on the hair of animals ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long can the virus stay on the hair of animals?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42184, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42184, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42184, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662781e-7085-11ea-ac6f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627852-7085-11ea-9dee-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662787a-7085-11ea-8ddf-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I go to the hospital if I have temperature ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I go to the hospital if I have temperature?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421854, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421854, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421854, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966278b6-7085-11ea-89fc-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966278de-7085-11ea-9de8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96627906-7085-11ea-9df7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I am taking a drug that suppresses my immune system . Should I stop taking it to make it less likely that I will get sick from coronavirus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I am taking a drug that suppresses my immune system. Should I stop taking it to make it less likely that I will get sick from coronavirus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421868, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421868, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421868, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96627942-7085-11ea-ac9f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627988-7085-11ea-b0c0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966279b0-7085-11ea-8a8a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have asthma . How at risk am I about the possibility of complications ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have asthma. How at risk am I about the possibility of complications?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421885, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421885, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421885, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966279ec-7085-11ea-ab04-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627a14-7085-11ea-bda5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96627a46-7085-11ea-b027-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many people are infected in Quebec ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many people are infected in Quebec?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4219, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4219, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4219, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96627a78-7085-11ea-b876-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627aa8-7085-11ea-aeb6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96627ad2-7085-11ea-837f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I go walking outside ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I go walking outside?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4219148, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4219148, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4219148, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96627b18-7085-11ea-8aa2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627b54-7085-11ea-871b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96627ba4-7085-11ea-81fe-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I would like to see a map with the infected", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I would like to see a map with the infected", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421935, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421936, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421936, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96627be2-7085-11ea-9618-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627c12-7085-11ea-9a27-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96627c3a-7085-11ea-9c05-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the multiplication coefficient of the virus on an experimental slide in the laboratory ? Example 1x10 / 24 hours , logarithmic scale , ...", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the multiplication coefficient of the virus on an experimental slide in the laboratory? Example 1x10 / 24 hours, logarithmic scale, ...", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4219499, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4219499, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4219499, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96627c6c-7085-11ea-827c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627c9e-7085-11ea-a753-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96627cc6-7085-11ea-aaa4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I am continuing ... should I place myself in voluntary isolation ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I am continuing ... should I place myself in voluntary isolation?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421964, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421964, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421964, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96627cf8-7085-11ea-87ae-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627d3e-7085-11ea-b4cb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96627d70-7085-11ea-a7cb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will herd immunity be the only means of eradicating COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will herd immunity be the only means of eradicating COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4219809, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4219809, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4219809, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96627da2-7085-11ea-9191-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627dca-7085-11ea-983d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96627dfa-7085-11ea-a4fc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how does it get transmited", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how does it get transmited", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.421994, "sourceDate": 1585352964.421995, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.421995, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96627e2e-7085-11ea-b5d1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627e58-7085-11ea-aa24-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96627e88-7085-11ea-a2a2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there an orientation for the personnel working in open area", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there an orientation for the personnel working in open area", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422009, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422009, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422009, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96627eba-7085-11ea-80b3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627eec-7085-11ea-8036-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96627f14-7085-11ea-ae8c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does vitus live on surfaces ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does vitus live on surfaces?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422025, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422025, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422025, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96627f5a-7085-11ea-a4ad-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96627fa8-7085-11ea-a22d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96627fdc-7085-11ea-88bc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is COVID-19 's definition ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is COVID-19's definition?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4220428, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4220428, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4220428, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662800c-7085-11ea-8714-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628040-7085-11ea-b2b8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96628068-7085-11ea-a20e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What kind of medication can I take if I have the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What kind of medication can I take if I have the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422057, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422057, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422057, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966280a4-7085-11ea-8469-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966280cc-7085-11ea-aa74-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966280f4-7085-11ea-b36f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many cases in Montreal", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many cases in Montreal", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422071, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422071, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422071, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628130-7085-11ea-bd5b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628158-7085-11ea-a831-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96628180-7085-11ea-9973-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "C dangerous for someone hasmatic", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "C dangerous for someone hasmatic", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422085, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422085, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422085, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966281ba-7085-11ea-a21f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966281e4-7085-11ea-ba44-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662820c-7085-11ea-a126-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What do I do if I suspect I 'm infected ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What do I do if I suspect I'm infected?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4220989, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4220989, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4220989, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628248-7085-11ea-ac67-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628270-7085-11ea-b49c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96628298-7085-11ea-9bdd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What more cancer patients need to know about coronavirus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What more cancer patients need to know about coronavirus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422113, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422113, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422113, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966282d4-7085-11ea-933a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662831a-7085-11ea-ab39-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662834c-7085-11ea-8d3a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus survive on various surfaces ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus survive on various surfaces?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422133, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422133, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422133, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628392-7085-11ea-bf82-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966283c6-7085-11ea-9e7c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966283f6-7085-11ea-9393-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I feel lonely from isolation .", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I feel lonely from isolation.", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422147, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422148, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422148, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628428-7085-11ea-830c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628450-7085-11ea-98d3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96628482-7085-11ea-b528-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What to do if i am infected ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What to do if i am infected?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422164, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422164, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422164, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966284c8-7085-11ea-8549-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966284fa-7085-11ea-b372-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96628522-7085-11ea-9fed-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422178, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422178, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422178, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662855e-7085-11ea-b730-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628586-7085-11ea-b3f8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966285ae-7085-11ea-bf83-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why corona is so dangerous", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why corona is so dangerous", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422192, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422192, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422192, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966285e8-7085-11ea-88a7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628612-7085-11ea-9c05-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662863a-7085-11ea-bceb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how many deaths are in Italy as of March 21", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how many deaths are in Italy as of March 21", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422206, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422206, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422206, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628676-7085-11ea-9c4c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662869e-7085-11ea-80ce-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966286c6-7085-11ea-90b2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is your name ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is your name?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42222, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42222, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42222, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628702-7085-11ea-be82-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628728-7085-11ea-adcb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96628766-7085-11ea-b290-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how many people die for cover ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how many people die for cover?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42224, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42224, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42224, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966287c0-7085-11ea-ac59-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628810-7085-11ea-a87f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96628838-7085-11ea-8f6a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My spouse has symptoms . Should I get tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My spouse has symptoms. Should I get tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422257, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422257, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422257, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628874-7085-11ea-a60b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662889c-7085-11ea-94be-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966288cc-7085-11ea-9b27-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can you see friends if you stick to the social distancing guidelines ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can you see friends if you stick to the social distancing guidelines?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422271, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422271, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422271, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628900-7085-11ea-8173-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628928-7085-11ea-b1c7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662895a-7085-11ea-ab78-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How do I get to the hospital if I do n't have a car ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How do I get to the hospital if I don't have a car?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422285, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422285, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422285, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662899e-7085-11ea-ae01-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966289d2-7085-11ea-8e15-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966289fa-7085-11ea-b258-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have symptoms , but I have n't traveled . Should I get tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have symptoms, but I haven't traveled. Should I get tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422302, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422302, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422302, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628a2c-7085-11ea-b9fd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628a5e-7085-11ea-96b2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96628a86-7085-11ea-9170-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Quebec cases", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Quebec cases", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422316, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422316, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422316, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628ab8-7085-11ea-bc9f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628ae8-7085-11ea-a473-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96628b26-7085-11ea-8eae-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to reduce the risk ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to reduce the risk?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4223318, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422333, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422333, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628b62-7085-11ea-a93f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628b94-7085-11ea-b364-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96628bc6-7085-11ea-bf5a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is Covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is Covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422349, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422349, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422349, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628c0c-7085-11ea-ab0b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628c3e-7085-11ea-a68e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96628c66-7085-11ea-90db-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is most usual symptom of Covid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is most usual symptom of Covid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422364, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422364, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422364, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628c98-7085-11ea-96ba-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628cca-7085-11ea-8d12-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96628cf4-7085-11ea-935f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If a person contracts Covid-19 and they breastfeed , what should they do ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If a person contracts Covid-19 and they breastfeed, what should they do?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422378, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422378, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422378, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628d24-7085-11ea-9a68-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628d58-7085-11ea-95f1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96628d7e-7085-11ea-bd3a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it true that 75 % of the population will be infected anyway ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it true that 75% of the population will be infected anyway?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4223921, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4223921, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4223921, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628dba-7085-11ea-95b5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628e00-7085-11ea-9cf5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96628e34-7085-11ea-8a71-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42241, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42241, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42241, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628e64-7085-11ea-bb10-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628e9e-7085-11ea-8cc8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96628ee6-7085-11ea-a415-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is COVID-19 sexually transmitted ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is COVID-19 sexually transmitted?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422427, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422428, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422428, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628f18-7085-11ea-849c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628f4a-7085-11ea-916b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96628f74-7085-11ea-a123-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are the symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are the symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422442, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422442, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422442, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96628fa4-7085-11ea-a1b2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96628fd8-7085-11ea-8abc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96628ffe-7085-11ea-bff9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can we cure covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can we cure covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422456, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422456, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422456, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96629030-7085-11ea-9822-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96629062-7085-11ea-8149-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662908a-7085-11ea-b1fa-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus survive on glass", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus survive on glass", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422472, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422472, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422472, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966290d0-7085-11ea-bdc2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96629102-7085-11ea-97ae-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96629128-7085-11ea-81c1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it ok to go outside to get fresh air ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it ok to go outside to get fresh air?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422486, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422486, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422487, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96629166-7085-11ea-8458-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662918c-7085-11ea-97a2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966291c0-7085-11ea-9a55-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the origin of COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the origin of COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4225001, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422501, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422501, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966291f4-7085-11ea-8780-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96629224-7085-11ea-aa71-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662924c-7085-11ea-bb8a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how to get an appointment", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how to get an appointment", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422515, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422515, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422515, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662927e-7085-11ea-92f4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966292b0-7085-11ea-bb57-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966292d8-7085-11ea-87d0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long until an infected person shows symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long until an infected person shows symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422529, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422529, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422529, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662930a-7085-11ea-b373-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662933a-7085-11ea-b904-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96629378-7085-11ea-927a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "i m sneezing , should i be worried ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "im sneezing, should i be worried?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422546, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422546, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422546, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966293be-7085-11ea-8aad-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966293e6-7085-11ea-9bbb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96629418-7085-11ea-b490-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is going to happen to us ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is going to happen to us?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42256, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42256, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42256, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662944a-7085-11ea-9530-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96629474-7085-11ea-b3a5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966294a4-7085-11ea-9421-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Corona virus characteristics", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Corona virus characteristics", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4225762, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4225762, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4225762, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966294e8-7085-11ea-93f3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662951c-7085-11ea-82e6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96629546-7085-11ea-8524-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how many death in italy ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how many death in italy?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422591, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422591, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422591, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96629576-7085-11ea-a9a2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966295a8-7085-11ea-9aee-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966295d0-7085-11ea-903a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it safe to jog / run outside ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it safe to jog / run outside?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422605, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422605, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422605, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662960c-7085-11ea-a320-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96629648-7085-11ea-9325-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96629670-7085-11ea-96fc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Covid ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Covid?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422621, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422621, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422621, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966296ac-7085-11ea-ae82-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966296e8-7085-11ea-826b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96629742-7085-11ea-aaf0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have fever , should I go out ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have fever, should I go out?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422642, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422642, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422642, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662977e-7085-11ea-82b2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966297a6-7085-11ea-a25a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966297d8-7085-11ea-b416-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what 's is COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what's is COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422656, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422656, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422656, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662980a-7085-11ea-8f05-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96629834-7085-11ea-a455-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662985a-7085-11ea-ae34-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus stay in paper money and coins ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus stay in paper money and coins?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4226701, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4226701, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4226701, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96629898-7085-11ea-b92e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966298be-7085-11ea-8221-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966298f0-7085-11ea-ac83-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "when will it get over", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "when will it get over", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422687, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422687, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422687, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96629936-7085-11ea-b448-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96629968-7085-11ea-8226-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96629990-7085-11ea-9fa0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the rates of hospitalization and the need for intensive care", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the rates of hospitalization and the need for intensive care", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4227011, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4227011, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4227011, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966299cc-7085-11ea-8e6e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966299f4-7085-11ea-8b2b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96629a26-7085-11ea-9c97-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the side - effects of hydroxychloroquine for treating COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the side-effects of hydroxychloroquine for treating COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422715, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422716, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422716, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96629a58-7085-11ea-8b88-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96629a80-7085-11ea-8f7e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96629ab4-7085-11ea-9cae-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can animals ( wild or domestic ) contract the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can animals (wild or domestic) contract the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422731, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422731, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422731, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96629af8-7085-11ea-9b37-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96629b34-7085-11ea-a6ca-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96629b66-7085-11ea-aa76-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is wearing a mask required for all ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is wearing a mask required for all?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422747, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422747, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422747, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96629b98-7085-11ea-933b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96629bc0-7085-11ea-9ea7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96629bf4-7085-11ea-bc87-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does it stays on fabric", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does it stays on fabric", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422761, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422761, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422761, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96629c24-7085-11ea-866e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96629c4c-7085-11ea-95c5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96629c7e-7085-11ea-856f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "COVID-19 stands for what ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "COVID-19 stands for what?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422776, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422776, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422776, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96629cb0-7085-11ea-8915-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96629ce2-7085-11ea-8db5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96629d0a-7085-11ea-8b6b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Use of zinc , or ciclesonide", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Use of zinc, or ciclesonide", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422792, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422792, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422792, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96629d50-7085-11ea-abe4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96629d82-7085-11ea-828b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96629da8-7085-11ea-a12c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the progress of the development of the vaccine ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the progress of the development of the vaccine?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422806, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422806, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422806, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96629de6-7085-11ea-9f37-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96629e0c-7085-11ea-a45e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96629e40-7085-11ea-b0b8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When should you consult ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When should you consult?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422823, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422823, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422823, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96629e90-7085-11ea-a20e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96629ee2-7085-11ea-a6bf-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96629f08-7085-11ea-b95d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will my surgery be canceled ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will my surgery be canceled?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422841, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422841, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422841, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96629f46-7085-11ea-8cbf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96629f6c-7085-11ea-a0e2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96629f94-7085-11ea-8895-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How does Facebook help find the vaccine ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How does Facebook help find the vaccine?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422855, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422855, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422855, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96629fd0-7085-11ea-b26a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96629ff8-7085-11ea-99b7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662a028-7085-11ea-9e14-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can a student like me be paid to visit the elderly and be paid ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can a student like me be paid to visit the elderly and be paid?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422872, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422872, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422872, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662a07a-7085-11ea-8305-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662a0ac-7085-11ea-b2a1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662a0d4-7085-11ea-88ec-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have a temperature and cough what should I do", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have a temperature and cough what should I do", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4228868, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4228868, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4228868, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662a106-7085-11ea-b778-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662a138-7085-11ea-a5e8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662a162-7085-11ea-8935-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are healthcare workers exposed to a new coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are healthcare workers exposed to a new coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422903, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422903, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422903, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662a1a6-7085-11ea-9d1d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662a1d8-7085-11ea-903e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662a20a-7085-11ea-b438-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it useful to wear a mask ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it useful to wear a mask?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4229171, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4229171, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4229178, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662a23a-7085-11ea-95dc-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662a264-7085-11ea-bdf9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662a298-7085-11ea-8105-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of vivid 19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of vivid 19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422934, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422935, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422935, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662a2e6-7085-11ea-9a89-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662a322-7085-11ea-8c1b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662a34a-7085-11ea-a406-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are flights still possible between Montreal and Paris ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are flights still possible between Montreal and Paris?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4229498, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4229498, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4229498, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662a37a-7085-11ea-a84d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662a3ae-7085-11ea-a3f6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662a3d8-7085-11ea-8734-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Wear a mask for groceries ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Wear a mask for groceries?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4229639, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4229639, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4229639, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662a412-7085-11ea-a38c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662a43a-7085-11ea-9064-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662a462-7085-11ea-8a21-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I be tested at auto service ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I be tested at auto service?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4229782, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4229782, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4229782, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662a49e-7085-11ea-a487-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662a4ee-7085-11ea-9eb5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662a51e-7085-11ea-a3e8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have a headache and an itchy throat . Am I at risk ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have a headache and an itchy throat. Am I at risk?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.422997, "sourceDate": 1585352964.422997, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.422997, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662a552-7085-11ea-aff3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662a586-7085-11ea-ba88-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662a5ac-7085-11ea-803c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are there healthy carriers , ie those who carry the virus without having symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are there healthy carriers, ie those who carry the virus without having symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4230132, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4230132, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423014, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662a5fa-7085-11ea-ad0c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662a62e-7085-11ea-b68f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662a658-7085-11ea-92a6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I had the virus and I am cured of it , am I immunized ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I had the virus and I am cured of it, am I immunized?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423028, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423028, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423028, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662a692-7085-11ea-89a4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662a6ba-7085-11ea-b375-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662a6f6-7085-11ea-9f02-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there a vaccine against coronaviruses ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there a vaccine against coronaviruses?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4230452, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4230452, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4230452, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662a73a-7085-11ea-b27c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662a76e-7085-11ea-8162-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662a798-7085-11ea-a942-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does the virus make your stomach ache ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does the virus make your stomach ache?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42306, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42306, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42306, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662a7d2-7085-11ea-8678-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662a7fa-7085-11ea-928b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662a82c-7085-11ea-9054-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how to prepare for spread of covid 19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how to prepare for spread of covid 19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423075, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423075, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423075, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662a85e-7085-11ea-820d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662a890-7085-11ea-a0ef-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662a8b8-7085-11ea-9335-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is SARS - CoV-2 What is COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is SARS-CoV-2 What is COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4230888, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4230888, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4230888, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662a8e8-7085-11ea-a274-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662a91c-7085-11ea-a514-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662a946-7085-11ea-8f47-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can hot or cold temperatures kill the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can hot or cold temperatures kill the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423103, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423103, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423103, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662a980-7085-11ea-ba1d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662a9c6-7085-11ea-9216-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662a9ee-7085-11ea-a079-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is sore throat a sign of COVID-19 infection ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is sore throat a sign of COVID-19 infection?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423124, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423124, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423124, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662aa52-7085-11ea-856a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662aa86-7085-11ea-a81b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662aac0-7085-11ea-a50c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are covid-19 symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are covid-19 symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423142, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423142, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423143, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662ab06-7085-11ea-819a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ab38-7085-11ea-9659-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662ab62-7085-11ea-9301-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are the main symptoms of coronavirus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are the main symptoms of coronavirus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423157, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423157, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423157, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662aba6-7085-11ea-9809-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662abd8-7085-11ea-af96-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662ac00-7085-11ea-a28c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will the school closings last longer ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will the school closings last longer?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4231732, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4231732, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4231732, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662ac3a-7085-11ea-b38f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ac64-7085-11ea-920b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662ac98-7085-11ea-b88f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is my age", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is my age", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423187, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423187, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423188, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662acc8-7085-11ea-96b8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662acf0-7085-11ea-b6c7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662ad22-7085-11ea-9145-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long should I stay at home if I have symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long should I stay at home if I have symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423202, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423202, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423202, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662ad54-7085-11ea-8bc4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ad86-7085-11ea-bd1d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662adae-7085-11ea-8ff9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What products should I use to remove COVID from surfaces ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What products should I use to remove COVID from surfaces?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423216, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423216, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423216, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662ade2-7085-11ea-bc3a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ae12-7085-11ea-b537-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662ae3a-7085-11ea-b015-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the Coronavirus stay on clothes ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the Coronavirus stay on clothes?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423232, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423232, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423232, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662ae8a-7085-11ea-883a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662aec6-7085-11ea-85cd-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662af02-7085-11ea-97eb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is working outside and avoiding contact safe ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is working outside and avoiding contact safe?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42325, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423251, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423251, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662af3e-7085-11ea-a0f4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662af70-7085-11ea-85f6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662af98-7085-11ea-8287-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Once the number of new cases has leveled off or decreased for how long will it be necessary to keep social distance ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Once the number of new cases has leveled off or decreased for how long will it be necessary to keep social distance?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423265, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423265, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423265, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662afca-7085-11ea-9066-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662b010-7085-11ea-93ef-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662b038-7085-11ea-a900-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What types of drugs and health products should I have on hand for an extended stay at home", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What types of drugs and health products should I have on hand for an extended stay at home", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423281, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423281, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423281, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662b074-7085-11ea-bb09-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662b09c-7085-11ea-bc54-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662b0cc-7085-11ea-ab91-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is thyme essential oil useful ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is thyme essential oil useful?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423296, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423296, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423296, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662b100-7085-11ea-b377-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662b134-7085-11ea-98e2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662b15a-7085-11ea-bdc4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many tests are run per day in the US ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many tests are run per day in the US?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42331, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42331, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42331, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662b18c-7085-11ea-883a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662b1be-7085-11ea-b907-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662b1e6-7085-11ea-9e7f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the first symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the first symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4233239, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4233239, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4233239, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662b222-7085-11ea-9a97-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662b254-7085-11ea-b232-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662b27a-7085-11ea-b768-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When can I end my self - isolation or self - quarantine", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When can I end my self-isolation or self-quarantine", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42334, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42334, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423341, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662b2c2-7085-11ea-8636-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662b308-7085-11ea-a31e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662b358-7085-11ea-90f0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does Covid 19 stay in the air and how long ? ? ? ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does Covid 19 stay in the air and how long ????", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423361, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423361, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423361, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662b394-7085-11ea-94de-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662b3da-7085-11ea-81ef-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662b402-7085-11ea-8b9a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I infect someone if I do n't have symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I infect someone if I don't have symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423378, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423378, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423378, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662b43e-7085-11ea-88f5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662b466-7085-11ea-915f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662b498-7085-11ea-bb47-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "was the virus created by humans", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "was the virus created by humans", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423393, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423393, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423393, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662b4ca-7085-11ea-a564-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662b4fa-7085-11ea-bc6f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662b524-7085-11ea-802b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I do n't have a car but I should get tested , how to get to the testing center without risking contaminating someone ' a ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I don't have a car but I should get tested, how to get to the testing center without risking contaminating someone 'a?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423407, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423407, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423407, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662b558-7085-11ea-8c7e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662b588-7085-11ea-9ebf-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662b5b0-7085-11ea-87f9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have been in isolation for 10 days and my parents too , should we visit each other ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have been in isolation for 10 days and my parents too, should we visit each other?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423421, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423421, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423421, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662b5ec-7085-11ea-811e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662b614-7085-11ea-8efa-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662b646-7085-11ea-9f45-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is corona virus in Nigeria ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is corona virus in Nigeria?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423435, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423436, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423436, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662b678-7085-11ea-9cc2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662b6a8-7085-11ea-a7da-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662b6d2-7085-11ea-8986-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is stomach ache a symptom", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is stomach ache a symptom", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42345, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42345, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42345, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662b706-7085-11ea-a9e0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662b736-7085-11ea-a800-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662b75e-7085-11ea-9f50-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What can I do to prepare myself if a member of the household becomes ill ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What can I do to prepare myself if a member of the household becomes ill?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423466, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423466, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423466, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662b7ae-7085-11ea-86e5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662b7f4-7085-11ea-8c4b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662b826-7085-11ea-9e59-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can you tell me where is the nearest test point ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can you tell me where is the nearest test point?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4234838, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4234838, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4234838, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662b862-7085-11ea-bba8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662b88a-7085-11ea-9f31-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662b8ba-7085-11ea-97cb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does the virus spread by rain ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does the virus spread by rain?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423499, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423499, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423499, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662b8ee-7085-11ea-846b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662b91e-7085-11ea-8d20-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662b948-7085-11ea-a1e2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long does the virus remain active and alive after attacking a human body ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long does the virus remain active and alive after attacking a human body?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4235132, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4235132, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4235132, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662b97a-7085-11ea-aab1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662b9ac-7085-11ea-b77d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662b9d4-7085-11ea-8eaf-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "testt", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "testt", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423527, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423527, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423527, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662ba10-7085-11ea-9b80-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ba38-7085-11ea-94e4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662ba68-7085-11ea-8c8c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are cov19 symptoms", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are cov19 symptoms", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423541, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423541, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423541, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662ba9c-7085-11ea-a530-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662bac6-7085-11ea-a2c1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662baf6-7085-11ea-bb06-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the type of structure of Covid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the type of structure of Covid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423556, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423556, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423556, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662bb28-7085-11ea-ba2f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662bb6e-7085-11ea-8ad7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662bb9e-7085-11ea-a02e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Am I immune for a long time after being infected and healed ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Am I immune for a long time after being infected and healed?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423576, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423576, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423576, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662bbf0-7085-11ea-b6ec-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662bc22-7085-11ea-b017-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662bc54-7085-11ea-b2a9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How to test the maximum of people ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How to test the maximum of people?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423593, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423593, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423593, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662bc9a-7085-11ea-b8a0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662bccc-7085-11ea-9e5d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662bcf4-7085-11ea-be18-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will I be able to travel soon", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will I be able to travel soon", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423607, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423607, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423607, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662bd30-7085-11ea-a02b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662bd58-7085-11ea-9191-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662bd8a-7085-11ea-a8d2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I catch covid19 a second time", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I catch covid19 a second time", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4236212, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423622, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423622, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662bdba-7085-11ea-b0e1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662bde4-7085-11ea-b50d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662be18-7085-11ea-a22f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Who should be tested for the covid ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Who should be tested for the covid?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423636, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423636, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423636, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662be48-7085-11ea-b443-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662be7a-7085-11ea-b015-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662bea2-7085-11ea-8422-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Has community transmission started ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Has community transmission started?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42365, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42365, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42365, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662bed4-7085-11ea-9d69-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662bf06-7085-11ea-84b2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662bf38-7085-11ea-870d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the barrier gestures ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the barrier gestures?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423664, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4236648, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4236648, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662bf68-7085-11ea-9caf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662bf9c-7085-11ea-ade2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662bfd8-7085-11ea-a181-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I 'm pregnant and need to take blood tests next week . I have an appointment at the clinic , should I Go there or is it safer to postpone ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I'm pregnant and need to take blood tests next week. I have an appointment at the clinic, should I Go there or is it safer to postpone?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4236841, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4236841, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4236841, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662c034-7085-11ea-a0f6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662c064-7085-11ea-8d5d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662c08c-7085-11ea-8dde-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "The flu kills more people than COVID-19 , at least so far . Why are we so concerned about COVID-19 ? Should n't we be focusing more on preventing deaths from the flu", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "The flu kills more people than COVID-19, at least so far. Why are we so concerned about COVID-19? Shouldn't we be focusing more on preventing deaths from the flu", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423699, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423699, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423699, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662c0c8-7085-11ea-b6b7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662c106-7085-11ea-b813-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662c12c-7085-11ea-9c09-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does wearing gloves protect me ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does wearing gloves protect me?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423715, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423715, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423715, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662c168-7085-11ea-9323-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662c190-7085-11ea-ac60-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662c1b8-7085-11ea-94a6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the average duration of symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the average duration of symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423729, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423729, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423729, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662c1f4-7085-11ea-a674-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662c23a-7085-11ea-8fc8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662c262-7085-11ea-88f1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how many new cases", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how many new cases", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423746, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423746, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423746, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662c29e-7085-11ea-9216-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662c2c6-7085-11ea-9a21-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662c2f8-7085-11ea-85ba-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there an estimate as to how long the crisis will last ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there an estimate as to how long the crisis will last?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42376, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423761, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423761, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662c328-7085-11ea-8968-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662c35c-7085-11ea-9796-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662c386-7085-11ea-8c34-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are bats the animal source of coronavirus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are bats the animal source of coronavirus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423775, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423775, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423775, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662c3b6-7085-11ea-b254-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662c3fa-7085-11ea-aa10-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662c438-7085-11ea-a597-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long will the pandemic last ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long will the pandemic last?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423794, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423794, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423794, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662c47e-7085-11ea-9bfe-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662c4a6-7085-11ea-bed8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662c4d8-7085-11ea-ae97-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Survival time by age", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Survival time by age", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423808, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423808, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423809, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662c50a-7085-11ea-9a9f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662c534-7085-11ea-a269-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662c564-7085-11ea-937e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "The incubation time is 14 or 20 days ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "The incubation time is 14 or 20 days?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423823, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423823, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423823, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662c598-7085-11ea-9026-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662c5dc-7085-11ea-ac58-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662c60c-7085-11ea-b228-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What does Corona and Covid mean ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What does Corona and Covid mean?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42384, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42384, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42384, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662c640-7085-11ea-8cfc-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662c674-7085-11ea-a3b1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662c69a-7085-11ea-a18c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I have COVID-19 what are the symptoms that should cause me to go to the hospital ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I have COVID-19 what are the symptoms that should cause me to go to the hospital?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423854, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423854, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423854, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662c6cc-7085-11ea-940c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662c6fe-7085-11ea-9984-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662c726-7085-11ea-b0d3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the current situation of COVID-19 infections ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the current situation of COVID-19 infections?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423871, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423871, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423871, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662c776-7085-11ea-93b2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662c7b4-7085-11ea-a9f0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662c7da-7085-11ea-9fd9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423886, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423886, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423886, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662c80c-7085-11ea-83a1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662c83e-7085-11ea-a9bd-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662c866-7085-11ea-bfda-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I take the metro ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I take the metro?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423902, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423902, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423902, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662c8ac-7085-11ea-bea6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662c8de-7085-11ea-beb2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662c906-7085-11ea-84c6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the difference between isolation and containment ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the difference between isolation and containment?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423916, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423916, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423916, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662c942-7085-11ea-9634-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662c968-7085-11ea-8e49-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662c99c-7085-11ea-aea4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What should I eat or drink to avoid or to battle COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What should I eat or drink to avoid or to battle COVID-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423931, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423931, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423931, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662c9cc-7085-11ea-b9d8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ca00-7085-11ea-a40e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662ca28-7085-11ea-89dc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the case fatality rate ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the case fatality rate?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423945, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423945, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423945, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662ca5a-7085-11ea-80ed-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ca8c-7085-11ea-b635-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662cab4-7085-11ea-bb77-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what to do when symptoms occur ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what to do when symptoms occur?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423959, "sourceDate": 1585352964.423959, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.423959, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662caf0-7085-11ea-95b4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662cb18-7085-11ea-8825-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662cb4a-7085-11ea-be2f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the best strategy to protect yourself from the coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the best strategy to protect yourself from the coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.423973, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4239738, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4239738, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662cb7a-7085-11ea-a06d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662cba4-7085-11ea-be13-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662cbd8-7085-11ea-87a6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does the virus survive the cold ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does the virus survive the cold?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4239879, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4239879, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4239879, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662cc08-7085-11ea-89bf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662cc4c-7085-11ea-a0cc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662cc80-7085-11ea-ba47-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many death in Quebec ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many death in Quebec?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424007, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424007, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424007, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662ccc6-7085-11ea-bd4c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ccf8-7085-11ea-8d1c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662cd1e-7085-11ea-a478-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Impact of covid", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Impact of covid", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424021, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424021, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424021, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662cd70-7085-11ea-b795-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662cda2-7085-11ea-a1ff-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662cdca-7085-11ea-b894-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Could a mutation in Covid-99 delay the arrival of a vaccine ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Could a mutation in Covid-99 delay the arrival of a vaccine?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424038, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424038, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424038, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662ce06-7085-11ea-9185-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ce2e-7085-11ea-b390-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662ce58-7085-11ea-b5be-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what is self monitoring ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what is self monitoring?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424052, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424052, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424052, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662ce92-7085-11ea-b0cf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ceba-7085-11ea-a115-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662cf00-7085-11ea-9c2b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it people around me at risk ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it people around me at risk?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4240692, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4240692, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4240692, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662cf34-7085-11ea-bd76-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662cf64-7085-11ea-8ed5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662cf8c-7085-11ea-8747-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Has the virus evolved", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Has the virus evolved", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424083, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424083, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424083, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662cfc8-7085-11ea-9484-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662cff0-7085-11ea-aa73-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662d022-7085-11ea-92f3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When will the situation be under control ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When will the situation be under control?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4241002, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4241002, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4241002, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662d074-7085-11ea-ad8b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662d0b8-7085-11ea-8bd3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662d0e8-7085-11ea-bf6c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how many people positive with Covid-19 in the world ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how many people positive with Covid-19 in the world?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424119, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424119, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424119, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662d130-7085-11ea-9cf8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662d162-7085-11ea-9700-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662d18a-7085-11ea-bce0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What treatments are available to treat coronaviruses", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What treatments are available to treat coronaviruses", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4241338, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4241338, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4241338, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662d1c6-7085-11ea-8eaf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662d202-7085-11ea-93cb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662d234-7085-11ea-ae20-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "where can I test for covid", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "where can I test for covid", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424151, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424151, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424151, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662d266-7085-11ea-afd8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662d298-7085-11ea-b0a4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662d2c0-7085-11ea-bedf-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When will be done ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When will be done?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424165, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424165, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424165, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662d2f4-7085-11ea-a8b2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662d324-7085-11ea-a5dc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662d34c-7085-11ea-8662-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How does COVID-19 affect asymptomatic people 's lungs ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How does COVID-19 affect asymptomatic people's lungs?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4241788, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4241788, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4241788, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662d37e-7085-11ea-b52d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662d3b0-7085-11ea-97cf-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662d3d8-7085-11ea-9a5e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are headaches a symptom ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are headaches a symptom?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424193, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424195, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424195, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662d41e-7085-11ea-8047-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662d45a-7085-11ea-bf1f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662d48c-7085-11ea-b7bb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What should I do if I have fever ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What should I do if I have fever?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424211, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424211, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424211, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662d4be-7085-11ea-8b80-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662d4f0-7085-11ea-bf28-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662d518-7085-11ea-ac4f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should we wear a mask ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should we wear a mask?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424237, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424237, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424237, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662d5cc-7085-11ea-bae3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662d5fe-7085-11ea-8d6c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662d630-7085-11ea-8b95-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "where can I get tested", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "where can I get tested", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4242518, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4242518, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424253, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662d662-7085-11ea-be1c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662d68a-7085-11ea-8a28-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662d6ba-7085-11ea-abfc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do we need to take showers more often ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do we need to take showers more often?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424267, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424267, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424267, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662d6ee-7085-11ea-9f38-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662d71e-7085-11ea-90ab-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662d748-7085-11ea-959b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I cough and have a fever . Can I go to the emergency room ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I cough and have a fever. Can I go to the emergency room?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4242811, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4242811, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4242811, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662d77a-7085-11ea-852d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662d7ac-7085-11ea-8a72-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662d7d4-7085-11ea-9fa7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is pregnant woman considered more at risk ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is pregnant woman considered more at risk?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424295, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424295, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424295, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662d806-7085-11ea-b977-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662d84c-7085-11ea-8e2a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662d888-7085-11ea-b4e8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of SARS - COV-2", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of SARS-COV-2", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424315, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424315, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424315, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662d8d8-7085-11ea-8224-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662d90a-7085-11ea-a852-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662d934-7085-11ea-9c8e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do I have to declare my state of health confidentially ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do I have to declare my state of health confidentially?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42433, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42433, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42433, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662d964-7085-11ea-b847-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662d998-7085-11ea-b0ce-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662d9be-7085-11ea-a51f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have fever , what should I do ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have fever, what should I do?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4243462, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4243462, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4243462, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662da0c-7085-11ea-a340-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662da40-7085-11ea-8b94-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662da68-7085-11ea-94f7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many people are infected in my region / in region X ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many people are infected in my region / in region X?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424361, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424361, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424361, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662da9a-7085-11ea-94c5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662dacc-7085-11ea-8dcd-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662daf4-7085-11ea-8d66-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is the cough dry or oily ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is the cough dry or oily?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424375, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424375, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424375, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662db26-7085-11ea-b807-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662db58-7085-11ea-af90-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662db80-7085-11ea-b785-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How do I distinguish between the flu and coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How do I distinguish between the flu and coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4243891, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4243891, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4243891, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662dbb4-7085-11ea-a87a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662dbe4-7085-11ea-9747-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662dc0c-7085-11ea-b735-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I traveled from Vancouver to quebec city , do i need to quaratine ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I traveled from Vancouver to quebec city, do i need to quaratine?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424403, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424403, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424403, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662dc3e-7085-11ea-b613-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662dc70-7085-11ea-a77b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662dca2-7085-11ea-bcf3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Suite ,", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Suite,", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42442, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42442, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42442, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662dcf4-7085-11ea-b946-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662dd24-7085-11ea-8934-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662dd4c-7085-11ea-ba9d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My parents are in quarantine and I live with them , do I have to go into quarantine too ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My parents are in quarantine and I live with them, do I have to go into quarantine too ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424435, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424435, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424435, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662dd88-7085-11ea-8cce-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ddb0-7085-11ea-8cd7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662ddd8-7085-11ea-9d84-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have fever", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have fever", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424449, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424449, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424449, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662de14-7085-11ea-95fd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662de3a-7085-11ea-91f6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662de64-7085-11ea-9338-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What If I returned from international travel a day before the advisory came into effect ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What If I returned from international travel a day before the advisory came into effect?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424465, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424465, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424465, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662deb4-7085-11ea-869d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662dedc-7085-11ea-817d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662df0c-7085-11ea-b937-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do I need to be seen by a doctor", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do I need to be seen by a doctor", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42448, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42448, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42448, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662df40-7085-11ea-bf93-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662e080-7085-11ea-bbfe-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662e0b4-7085-11ea-805f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I am a nurse and have a cold , should I place myself in confinement", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I am a nurse and have a cold, should I place myself in confinement", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424522, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424522, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424522, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662e0ee-7085-11ea-8824-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662e118-7085-11ea-bbdd-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662e148-7085-11ea-8d2a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the real mechanisms of virus transmission ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the real mechanisms of virus transmission?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4245372, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4245372, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4245372, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662e17a-7085-11ea-8de5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662e1b6-7085-11ea-a580-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662e1f4-7085-11ea-b0cd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the estimated population that will be infected by the covid-19 virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the estimated population that will be infected by the covid-19 virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424555, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424555, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424555, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662e22e-7085-11ea-97b1-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662e262-7085-11ea-9ca7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662e288-7085-11ea-ae03-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does everyone that contracts the virus show symptoms ? Or will only certain people show symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does everyone that contracts the virus show symptoms? Or will only certain people show symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4245691, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4245691, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4245691, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662e2c6-7085-11ea-a559-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662e30a-7085-11ea-9fc2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662e33a-7085-11ea-9ccc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do we have a vaccine for Coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do we have a vaccine for Coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424587, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424587, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424587, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662e36e-7085-11ea-9964-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662e39e-7085-11ea-8203-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662e3c8-7085-11ea-8b1c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have a dry cough . Should I be tested for COVID19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have a dry cough. Should I be tested for COVID19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424603, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424603, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424603, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662e40c-7085-11ea-a645-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662e454-7085-11ea-8bf2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662e47a-7085-11ea-ae7d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I am starting to breath heavily , should I get it checked out ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I am starting to breath heavily, should I get it checked out?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424619, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424619, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424619, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662e4b8-7085-11ea-93c4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662e4e2-7085-11ea-aada-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662e512-7085-11ea-9f59-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the source of the disease ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the source of the disease?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424633, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4246342, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4246342, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662e546-7085-11ea-9215-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662e576-7085-11ea-8c13-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662e59e-7085-11ea-aa51-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should children wear masks to protect themselves from covid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should children wear masks to protect themselves from covid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424649, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42465, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42465, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662e5e4-7085-11ea-ac08-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662e61e-7085-11ea-9153-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662e652-7085-11ea-a9de-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Define covid 18", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Define covid 18", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4246662, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4246662, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4246662, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662e686-7085-11ea-bcfd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662e6b6-7085-11ea-8cd8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662e6de-7085-11ea-87c9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does covid transfer through air ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does covid transfer through air?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42468, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42468, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42468, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662e710-7085-11ea-951a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662e742-7085-11ea-9657-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662e768-7085-11ea-8be0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I catch the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I catch the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424694, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424694, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424694, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662e79c-7085-11ea-8167-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662e7d8-7085-11ea-ab4f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662e800-7085-11ea-8a55-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I go for walking !", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I go for walking!", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4247098, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4247098, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4247098, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662e846-7085-11ea-9f3a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662e86e-7085-11ea-92a3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662e89e-7085-11ea-a485-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How are you", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How are you", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424725, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424725, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424725, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662e8d2-7085-11ea-8f01-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662e906-7085-11ea-b98b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662e92c-7085-11ea-928b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many deaths in Canada because of COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many deaths in Canada because of COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4247391, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4247391, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4247391, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662e95e-7085-11ea-8d87-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662eaee-7085-11ea-96f2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662eb1e-7085-11ea-8ae7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can we contract covid-19 several times ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can we contract covid-19 several times?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424788, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424789, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424789, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662eb52-7085-11ea-ba39-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662eb86-7085-11ea-b31e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662ebac-7085-11ea-a0ab-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Or can I get tested ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Or can I get tested?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424802, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424803, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424803, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662ebde-7085-11ea-8b45-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ec06-7085-11ea-be56-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662ec38-7085-11ea-81d7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is liquid soap better than bar soap for protection ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is liquid soap better than bar soap for protection?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4248168, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4248168, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4248168, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662ec68-7085-11ea-94d4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ec9c-7085-11ea-8057-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662ecc6-7085-11ea-8462-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Quelkea are the complications of the disease ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Quelkea are the complications of the disease?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424831, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424831, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424831, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662ecf6-7085-11ea-9605-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ed28-7085-11ea-91e0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662ed6e-7085-11ea-9b14-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is sore throats a symptom", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is sore throats a symptom", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42485, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42485, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42485, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662edbe-7085-11ea-9778-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ede6-7085-11ea-a3a1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662ee18-7085-11ea-a942-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is self - isolation ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is self-isolation?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4248672, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4248672, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4248672, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662ee5e-7085-11ea-8ef5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ee9a-7085-11ea-867b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662eecc-7085-11ea-9515-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "the dangerous covid 19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "the dangerous covid 19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424882, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424883, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424883, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662eefe-7085-11ea-8230-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ef30-7085-11ea-a420-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662ef58-7085-11ea-b74b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When should we be worried ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When should we be worried?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424897, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424897, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424897, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662ef8a-7085-11ea-8807-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662efba-7085-11ea-8daa-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662efe4-7085-11ea-89a0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it sexually transmissible ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it sexually transmissible?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424911, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424911, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424911, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662f01e-7085-11ea-b5a9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662f05c-7085-11ea-bc7b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662f08c-7085-11ea-9c70-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "After my 14 days in quarantine", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "After my 14 days in quarantine", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424928, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424928, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424928, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662f0c0-7085-11ea-94d9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662f0f4-7085-11ea-a029-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662f11a-7085-11ea-956d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "are hospital bed saturated in province of quebec", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "are hospital bed saturated in province of quebec", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424942, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424942, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424942, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662f14c-7085-11ea-a7ab-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662f17e-7085-11ea-a910-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662f1a6-7085-11ea-8e76-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are the hardware stores open in Montreal ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are the hardware stores open in Montreal?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424958, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424958, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424958, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662f200-7085-11ea-b22a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662f234-7085-11ea-b20e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662f25a-7085-11ea-99bf-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is the virus as virulent in countries near the equator ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is the virus as virulent in countries near the equator?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424974, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424974, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4249752, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662f298-7085-11ea-aab7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662f2c8-7085-11ea-b2fd-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662f2f0-7085-11ea-96c3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When should we call 15 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When should we call 15?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.424991, "sourceDate": 1585352964.424991, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.424991, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662f340-7085-11ea-8de7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662f374-7085-11ea-9126-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662f39a-7085-11ea-a92d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there treatment for a new coronavirus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there treatment for a new coronavirus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4250062, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4250062, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4250062, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662f3d8-7085-11ea-b885-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662f3fe-7085-11ea-aa81-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662f430-7085-11ea-a79c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how many cases in quebec", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how many cases in quebec", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42502, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42502, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42502, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662f462-7085-11ea-9819-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662f48a-7085-11ea-b8c6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662f4ba-7085-11ea-84f1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long on average does the person get healed ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long on average does the person get healed?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425035, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425035, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425035, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662f4ee-7085-11ea-9a8b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662f51e-7085-11ea-a8ff-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662f548-7085-11ea-b7f2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is covid19 present in the air ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is covid19 present in the air?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425049, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425049, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425049, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662f586-7085-11ea-ba34-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662f5ac-7085-11ea-b61e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662f5de-7085-11ea-b0a1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms for corona virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms for corona virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425065, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425065, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425065, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662f624-7085-11ea-b824-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662f662-7085-11ea-bdbc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662f6b0-7085-11ea-a68b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "is vomiting one of the symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "is vomiting one of the symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425087, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425087, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425088, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662f700-7085-11ea-8d1a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662f734-7085-11ea-99ba-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662f75a-7085-11ea-a1b9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where are the testing centers located in Mtl ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where are the testing centers located in Mtl?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425102, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425102, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425102, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662f798-7085-11ea-b19d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662f7be-7085-11ea-9ef0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662f7e6-7085-11ea-bb97-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the half - life of coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the half-life of coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4251158, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4251158, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4251158, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662f822-7085-11ea-b21a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662f84a-7085-11ea-a527-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662f874-7085-11ea-95fa-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can we emphasize that by increasing the number of tests , we should expect an increase in positive cases .", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can we emphasize that by increasing the number of tests, we should expect an increase in positive cases.", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42513, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42513, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42513, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662f8ae-7085-11ea-9442-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662f8d8-7085-11ea-93ba-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662f908-7085-11ea-8bfb-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If man develops immunity to covid-19 , how long does it last", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If man develops immunity to covid-19, how long does it last", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425144, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425144, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4251451, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662f93a-7085-11ea-a0c5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662f962-7085-11ea-98f4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662f994-7085-11ea-ae46-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Who can I make the difference between a cold and covid19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Who can I make the difference between a cold and covid19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425159, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425159, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425159, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662f9c6-7085-11ea-9d06-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662f9f8-7085-11ea-a1e7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662fa1e-7085-11ea-bc94-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I refuse to go to work because of the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I refuse to go to work because of the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425175, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425175, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425175, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662fa66-7085-11ea-9404-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662fa98-7085-11ea-b2c1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662fad4-7085-11ea-821b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can the Covid survive in the air ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can the Covid survive in the air?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4251919, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4251919, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4251919, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662fb10-7085-11ea-95f7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662fb4c-7085-11ea-8f8c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662fb74-7085-11ea-b92d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the most common symptoms in COViD-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the most common symptoms in COViD-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4252071, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4252071, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4252071, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662fbb0-7085-11ea-97f2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662fbd8-7085-11ea-8a09-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662fc0a-7085-11ea-b4f0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where can I find more information on known coronaviruses", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where can I find more information on known coronaviruses", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425222, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425222, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425222, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662fc3a-7085-11ea-b637-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662fc64-7085-11ea-941d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662fc98-7085-11ea-9ef9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Do we have the right to visit someone at their home ? Being two or three people together for dinner ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Do we have the right to visit someone at their home? Being two or three people together for dinner?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425236, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425236, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425236, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662fcc8-7085-11ea-839a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662fcfa-7085-11ea-9d7d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662fd22-7085-11ea-af06-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How many times a day should I wash my hands ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How many times a day should I wash my hands?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42525, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42525, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42525, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662fd54-7085-11ea-9f38-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662fd86-7085-11ea-b15b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662fdae-7085-11ea-902d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is the question : are you traveling , is", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is the question: are you traveling, is", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4252641, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4252641, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4252641, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662fde8-7085-11ea-9532-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662fe12-7085-11ea-8405-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662fe3a-7085-11ea-9322-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of Coronavirus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of Coronavirus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42528, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42528, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425281, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662fe8a-7085-11ea-9996-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662fed0-7085-11ea-8a1a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662ff18-7085-11ea-8ff8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how many people died in canada ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how many people died in canada?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425301, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425301, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425302, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662ff5c-7085-11ea-b97d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9662ff8c-7085-11ea-949d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9662ffb6-7085-11ea-a83c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is covid 29", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is covid 29", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425316, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425316, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425317, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9662fff4-7085-11ea-a05b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96630038-7085-11ea-a485-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96630062-7085-11ea-86e8-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What should I use to disinfect grocery bags and grocery items ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What should I use to disinfect grocery bags and grocery items?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425333, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425333, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425333, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9663009c-7085-11ea-af67-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966300c6-7085-11ea-b67b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966300f6-7085-11ea-af45-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does the virus get milder due to coevolution ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does the virus get milder due to coevolution?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425347, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425347, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425348, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96630128-7085-11ea-8c55-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96630150-7085-11ea-9002-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96630182-7085-11ea-8819-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How does it die in asymptomatic people ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How does it die in asymptomatic people?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4253619, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4253619, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4253619, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966301b4-7085-11ea-ac1e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966301e6-7085-11ea-90fc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9663020c-7085-11ea-9404-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What 's happen for country near the Ecuador with a lot of hot ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What's happen for country near the Ecuador with a lot of hot?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425376, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425376, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425376, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96630240-7085-11ea-b9a3-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96630274-7085-11ea-8d9b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9663029a-7085-11ea-a3c4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I had a fever two weeks ago is it possible that it is covid-19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I had a fever two weeks ago is it possible that it is covid-19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4253922, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4253922, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4253922, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966302e8-7085-11ea-a2de-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96630312-7085-11ea-9993-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96630346-7085-11ea-ad09-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "what are the 3 symptoms of covid-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "what are the 3 symptoms of covid-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425407, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425407, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425407, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96630376-7085-11ea-8c44-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966303a8-7085-11ea-9e53-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966303e4-7085-11ea-9c73-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If my partner returns from travel and quarantines for 14 days , should I do the same ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If my partner returns from travel and quarantines for 14 days, should I do the same?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4254239, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4254239, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4254239, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9663041e-7085-11ea-89e7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9663045c-7085-11ea-a7da-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96630486-7085-11ea-9a72-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I transmit the virus by thought ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I transmit the virus by thought?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425439, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425439, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425439, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966304b6-7085-11ea-9453-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9663068c-7085-11ea-bb47-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966306c8-7085-11ea-9529-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I bring the neighbors into my house ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I bring the neighbors into my house?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425497, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425497, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425497, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96630706-7085-11ea-a298-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9663072c-7085-11ea-a22d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9663075e-7085-11ea-b3dd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the essential services ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the essential services?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4255118, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4255118, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4255118, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96630790-7085-11ea-9a2c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966307c2-7085-11ea-bf2e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966307fe-7085-11ea-b2ed-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What should i know about effective hand washing to protect against corona", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What should i know about effective hand washing to protect against corona", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425529, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425529, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425529, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9663083a-7085-11ea-a1fe-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96630876-7085-11ea-bdf7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "9663089e-7085-11ea-a0d9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When will the schools reopen ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When will the schools reopen?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425544, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425544, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425544, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966308da-7085-11ea-afda-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9663091e-7085-11ea-8c89-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96630948-7085-11ea-aa2c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I stay home ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I stay home?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4255629, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4255629, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4255629, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9663098c-7085-11ea-8165-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966309c0-7085-11ea-8d7e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966309f4-7085-11ea-9c6c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Does soap really kill the virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Does soap really kill the virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425577, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4255779, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4255779, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96630a24-7085-11ea-948a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96630a4c-7085-11ea-9295-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96630a7e-7085-11ea-ba67-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how to prevent ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how to prevent?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425592, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425592, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425592, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96630ab0-7085-11ea-823e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96630ae2-7085-11ea-9c60-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96630b28-7085-11ea-bcf4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Anything else ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Anything else?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4256089, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4256089, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4256089, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96630b5a-7085-11ea-b733-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96630b8c-7085-11ea-be37-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96630bb4-7085-11ea-a5b7-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Go nuance !", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Go nuance!", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425623, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425623, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425623, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96630bf0-7085-11ea-adb0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96630c18-7085-11ea-8124-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96630c4a-7085-11ea-9bc2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "how I cure korona verus", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "how I cure korona verus", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4256399, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4256399, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4256399, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96630c9a-7085-11ea-a035-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96630ccc-7085-11ea-8f47-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96630cfe-7085-11ea-9977-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are there rarer symptoms of corona virus ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are there rarer symptoms of corona virus?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4256551, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425656, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425656, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96630d30-7085-11ea-a085-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96630d62-7085-11ea-95c0-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96630d8a-7085-11ea-bb79-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long will it take before I get my results ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long will it take before I get my results?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425672, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425672, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425672, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96630dd0-7085-11ea-8b4e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96630e02-7085-11ea-9753-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96630e34-7085-11ea-810f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I feel I have fever , what should I do ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I feel I have fever, what should I do?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4256861, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4256861, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425687, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96630e66-7085-11ea-87c2-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96630e8c-7085-11ea-82c2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96630ec0-7085-11ea-8b94-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the mortality rate ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the mortality rate?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4257002, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4257011, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4257011, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96630ef4-7085-11ea-bac9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96630f38-7085-11ea-b9bf-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96630f68-7085-11ea-8460-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can Antibiotics Be Used To Treat COVID-19", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can Antibiotics Be Used To Treat COVID-19", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4257169, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425718, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425718, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96630f9c-7085-11ea-a099-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96630fc6-7085-11ea-9b5c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96631014-7085-11ea-8cc0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why do I have to isolate myself ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why do I have to isolate myself?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425735, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425735, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425736, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96631050-7085-11ea-99be-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96631082-7085-11ea-8323-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966310a8-7085-11ea-a560-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Could everyone be tested even without symptoms ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Could everyone be tested even without symptoms?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42575, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42575, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42575, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966310dc-7085-11ea-aec9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9663110c-7085-11ea-bdc3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96631136-7085-11ea-aca3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I was in contact with a person who had coronavirus , what should I do ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I was in contact with a person who had coronavirus, what should I do?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425764, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425764, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425764, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96631174-7085-11ea-b77f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9663119a-7085-11ea-bfa6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966311c2-7085-11ea-9b7a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of covid19 ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of covid19?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.42578, "sourceDate": 1585352964.42578, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.42578, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96631208-7085-11ea-9ccb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "9663123a-7085-11ea-b780-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96631262-7085-11ea-9856-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can I get help ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can I get help?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.4257941, "sourceDate": 1585352964.4257941, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.4257941, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "9663129e-7085-11ea-b903-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966312c6-7085-11ea-9887-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "966312f8-7085-11ea-b7a2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "As a foreign student , will health insurance cover expenses in the event of illness ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "As a foreign student, will health insurance cover expenses in the event of illness?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425809, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425809, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425809, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "96631328-7085-11ea-93f9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "96631352-7085-11ea-af41-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96631386-7085-11ea-a2f6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can soap keep the COVID-19 virus on the surface ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can soap keep the COVID-19 virus on the surface?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "", "sourceName": "translatedDialogueMDquestions", "dateScraped": 1585352964.425823, "sourceDate": 1585352964.425823, "lastUpdateTime": 1585352964.425823, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "966313b6-7085-11ea-b06f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "966313e8-7085-11ea-a2cc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "96631424-7085-11ea-941f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "should I wear a mask ?", "answerText": "", "hasAnswer": false, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "should I wear a mask?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "", "answerLinks": {}}}
